Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
* The sun'll come out tomorrow
* Bet your bottom dollar
that tomorrow
* There'll be sun
* Just thinkin' about tomorrow
* Clears away the cobwebs
and the sorrow
* Till there's none
* When I'm stuck with a day
* That's gray and lonely
* I just stick out my chin
* And grin
* And say
* Oh
* The sun'll come out tomorrow
* So you gotta hang on
till tomorrow
* Come what may
* Tomorrow, tomorrow
* I love ya, tomorrow
* You're only a day away
* Tomorrow, tomorrow
* I love ya, tomorrow
* You're only a day
* Away
ANNIE:
* Maybe far away
* Or maybe real nearby
* He may be
pouring her coffee
* She may be
straightenin' his tie
* Maybe in a house
* All hidden by a hill
* She's sittin' playin' piano
* He's sittin' payin' a bill
* Betcha they're young
* Betcha they're smart
* Bet they collect things
* Like ashtrays and art
* Betcha they're good
* Why shouldn't they be?
* Their one mistake
* Was giving up me
* So maybe now it's time
* And maybe when I wake
* They'll be there
calling me, "Baby"
* Maybe
(WHINING)
(WHINING CONTINUES)
Annie.
Annie!
Shh.
It's okay.
Everything's gonna
be all right.
(WHIMPERING)
There, there.
It was only a dream, Molly.
It's all right.
How am I supposed to get
any sleep around here?
It was only a dream.
Everything's all right.
Molly shouldn't be
in this room.
She's a baby.
Ow!
She cries all the time.
She wets the bed.
I do not!
You're the one who
shouldn't be in here!
Brat! Stop!
We're going to
get in trouble.
Go, Duffy! Go!
Oh, my goodness!
(GIRLS SCREAMING)
Cut it out!
I mean it!
Do you want
Miss Hannigan
to come in here?
Go back to bed!
Now.
Or you'll have me
to deal with.
Aw, blow it out
your old wazoo.
Close your eyes.
Think about your folks.
You're the only one
who really has folks.
Mine are dead.
Think about the folks
who want to adopt you
because they want
a little girl
with brown hair
and brown eyes.
* Betcha he reads
* Betcha she sews
* Maybe she's made me
* A closet of clothes
* Maybe they're strict
* As straight as a line
* Don't really care
* As long as they're mine
Oh, my goodness.
* So maybe now this prayer's
* The last one of its kind
* Won't you please
come get your baby... *
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
Did I hear singing in here?
All right.
Fine.
Since we're all
so wide awake!
(GIRLS MUMBLING)
Get up!
Get out of bed!
Clean up
this mess!
Get dressed!
And this room had better be
regulation before breakfast,
my little pig droppings,
or kill, kill, kill!
But it's in the
middle of the night.
(SQUEAKY VOICE) "But it's
in the middle of the night."
And if this
floor don't shine
like the top of
the Chrysler Building,
your backsides will,
you understand?
ALL: (IN UNISON)
Yes, Miss Hannigan.
What do we say, Annie?
I love you,
Miss Hannigan.
Why any kid would want to
be an orphan is beyond me.
MISS HANNIGAN: Ow!
(GIRLS SCREAMING)
* It's the hard-knock life
for us
* Instead of treated
* We get tricked
* Instead of kisses
* We get kicked
* It's the hard-knock life
* Got no folks
to speak of so
* It's a hard-knock row
we hoe
* Cotton blankets
* Instead of wool
* Empty bellies
* Instead of full
* It's the hard-knock life
(WHISTLE BLOWS)
(EXCITED SHOUTS)
* Don't it feel like
the wind is always howling?
* Don't it seem like
there's never any light?
* Once a day
don't you want to
throw the towel in?
* It's easier than
puttin' up a fight
(SNARLING)
* No one's there when
your dreams at night
get creepy
* No one cares if you
grow or if you shrink
(CRYING)
* No one dries when
your eyes get red and weepy
* From the crying you would
think this place would sink
Oh.
* Oh
* Empty-belly life
* Rotten, smelly life
* Full-of-sorrow life
* No-tomorrow life
* Santa Claus
we never see
What's that?
* Who's he?
* No one cares
for you a smidge
(WHISTLE BLOWING)
* When you're
in an orphanage
* It's the hard-knock life
(IMITATING MISS HANNIGAN)
You'll stay up till this dump
shines like the top of
the Chrysler Building!
Kill, kill!
* Yank the whiskers
from her chin
Little pig droppings.
* Jab her with a safety pin
Rotten orphans.
* Make her drink
a Mickey Finn
Nobody loves you.
ALL:
I love you,
Miss Hannigan.
Get to work!
(IMITATING CRINGING)
Strip that bed!
Scrub that floor!
Polish my shoes!
(WHISTLE BLOWING)
And I mean,
start now!
* It's the hard-knock life
for us
Laundry.
* It's the hard-knock life
for us
* No one cares
for you a smidge
* When you're
in an orphanage
* It's the hard-knock life
* The hard-knock
* Life
GIRL: Get out of here.
MOLLY: We better
get out of here or
we're gonna get killed.
Cover me up good.
DUFFY: All you
ever do is run away.
Oh, my goodness!
(MOLLY CRYING)
She'll put you in the
cellar with the ghosts.
You'll just
get whipped again.
You're gonna
get us in trouble.
ANNIE:
Molly, shut up!
I'm gonna tell.
ANNIE: And I'm gonna
rearrange your teeth!
(WHISTLE BLOWING)
ANNIE:
Stomp on her foot.
What are you all just
standing around here for?
You're supposed
to clean the bathroom and
the kitchen before lunch,
my little pig droppings.
And if you
skip the corners,
there will be no lunch.
And we're not having
hot mush today.
ALL: Yay!
(WHISTLE BLOWS)
We're having cold mush.
(ALL GROANING DISGUSTEDLY)
What?
ALL:
We love you,
Miss Hannigan.
Wonderful.
Where's Annie?
She had to
go bathroom.
(SQUEAKY VOICE)
"She had to go
bathroom."
BUNDLES: Miss Hannigan!
Oh.
Mr. Bundles.
GIRLS: Mr. Bundles.
MISS HANNIGAN: Mr. Bundles.
BUNDLES: Miss Hannigan!
MAN: Raspberries, oranges...
Miss Hannigan!
(CHILDREN CHATTERING)
Yoo-hoo.
It's time
for a tumble
with a bundle.
Not today,
Miss Hannigan.
I'm behind, I...
Ooh! My schedule,
I mean.
Schedules.
What are schedules in
the storms of passion,
Mr. Bundles?
Just so much flotsam
and jetsam.
(MISS HANNIGAN LAUGHING)
BUNDLES: Oh,
Miss Hannigan, please!
(HORN HONKING)
Mr. Bundles.
What are you
doing out here?
Helping you.
It's heavy today.
Yeah, it's a lot
heavier than usual...
Shh!
Annie.
It shouldn't be.
What's in there?
Miss Hannigan.
Mr. Bundles.
Miss Hannigan?
Oh, yes?
You're my kind of woman,
Miss Hannigan.
Oh, yes. Yes.
Till next month,
Miss Hannigan.
I'll be right here.
(WHISTLE BLOWS)
(CHILDREN LAUGHING)
(PEOPLE CHATTERING)
ANNIE:
Mr. Bundles,
I'm in here.
Thank you,
Mr. Bundles.
Good luck.
WOMAN: I'm going to miss you.
(HUMMING)
(WHISTLING)
(WHISTLING FASTER)
CHILDREN:
Row boat, row boat.
(CHATTERING LOUDLY)
(HENS CLUCKING)
(SIGHS)
(DOG BARKING)
(WOMAN ARGUING LOUDLY)
(BOYS LAUGHING)
(DOG WHINING)
BOY 1: Get his tail!
Poor dog.
Leave him alone!
What's he ever
done to you?
Amscray!
BOY 2: Come on.
All right,
who's next?
(GRUNTS)
BOY 3:
Quick as lightning!
Anybody else?
BOY 3: Scram, man!
BOY 2: Let's go!
Then get lost!
BOY 1:
Get a move on!
BOY 4: Let's hotfoot it!
BOY 3: That's your
mom calling you.
Shake a leg! Come on!
Let's go! Come on!
Hey, you're all right.
I didn't do nothing
any decent person
wouldn't have done.
Dumb dog.
* Dumb dog
* Why are you
following me?
* I ain't got
a crumb, dog
* How about
lettin' me be?
* I ain't gonna
feed you
* Ain't got a scrap
for you
* Need you?
* Don't give a rap
for you, dumb dog
* Dumber than
they come, dog
* You're the most
presumin' dog
* That a human could know
Hey, mister.
That's my dog.
Oh, yeah?
Where's his license?
Where's his leash?
He's no more your dog
than I am your father.
I left his license
at home by mistake.
Please don't take him
to the pound, please.
My father's blind.
This dog leads him
to work.
If he can't get to work,
we're gonna all of us
starve, sir.
And what's his name?
My father's name?
The dog's name.
Oh, the dog's name.
Uh, his name's Sandy.
Right! That's it!
Sandy.
Call him.
Call him?
Go over there
and call him.
You mean,
by his name?
By his name.
The dog's name.
Sandy.
Come here, Sandy.
Sandy!
Come here, Sandy!
Come here, boy.
Here, Rover.
Hey,
Rin Tin Tin.
WOMAN: Louder.
Come here.
Come to Daddy.
ANNIE: Sandy!
Come here, Sandy!
Rin Tin Tin,
come here.
Sandy!
Come here, Sandy.
Come here.
Good old Sandy!
You got yourself
a dog, kid.
Now go home and get him
a collar and leash.
Yes, sir.
(WOMEN CHATTERING)
(CAR HORN HONKING)
Hey, you kids,
get out of there!
(DOORBELL RINGS)
Miss Hannigan!
(SHOUTING) What?
Annie!
Look what I found
under a paving stone,
Miss Hannigan.
Oh, Annie!
Annie, my little peach fuzz,
are you all right?
I was worried sick.
(MOUTHING)
I knew you would be.
A big-hearted woman
like you.
How can I ever
thank you enough?
I'm sure we could think of
something if we could get
our heads together.
Kissy, kissy, kissy.
Kill...
Kill!
(WHISTLE BLOWS)
ALL:
We love you,
Miss Hannigan.
Sure.
Oh, my goodness!
(GIRLS EXCLAIMING)
GIRL: Annie,
where'd you get him?
He smells.
What's his name, Annie?
Guess.
Uh, Fifi?
That ain't a name
for this mutt.
(ALL LAUGHING)
* So how about Champion?
* Champion
you're anything but
* We could
call him Tiger
* But there's
no bite in him
* Tiger
(BLOWS RASPBERRY)
* Kittens would
frighten him
* Rover
When you think it over
Shh!
* Rover is the perfect name
For this dumb-looking dog
Rover!
(BARKING)
GIRLS: Come here, Rover.
Come on, doggie.
* Sandy, Sandy's
his name if you please
* If you don't believe me
* Ask any one of the fleas
* Residing on Sandy
* True,
he ain't pedigreed
* Sandy, there
ain't no better breed
* And he really
comes in handy
* Especially when
you're all alone
in the night
* And you're small
and terribly frightened
* It's Sandy
* Sandy,
who'll always be
* There
She's coming.
GIRL: Hide him.
Use that material.
Come on. Hurry!
Hide him quick!
Oh, my goodness!
Hurry! Hurry!
I love you,
Miss Hannigan.
And you will love
the paddle closet,
Annie.
And this
will love
the sausage factory.
GIRLS: No, Miss...
What?
ALL:
We love you,
Miss Hannigan.
Shut up.
MAN: Apples, a nickel.
Apples here.
Yes, ma'am.
Here you go.
Thank you very much.
God bless you.
Apples here.
Big, delicious apples.
Apples.
(CROWD CHATTERING)
BOY: My daddy's gonna buy
one of those.
WOMAN 1: What's she wearing?
(PEOPLE EXCLAIMING)
WOMAN 2: Beautiful!
(CROWD CHATTERING)
(BELL RINGS)
MISS HANNIGAN:
All right! All right!
Yeah?
Miss Hannigan,
I'm Grace Farrell.
The New York Board
of Orphans sent me.
Oh!
Well, my goodness,
won't you come in?
Thank you.
Right this way.
Well...
Welcome. Welcome
to our happy home.
GIRL 1: Get off
my foot, Molly!
Thank you.
Ladies.
GIRL 2: Smell that perfume.
What did you say
your name was?
Uh, Grace Farrell.
Grace. Aptly named.
GIRL 3: I bet she wants
a girl to clean her house.
I bet
it's gonna be me.
I'm here
to inquire
about an orphan.
Wait, Grace,
I can explain
the whole thing.
You see,
what happened was,
the child actually
bribed Mr. Bundles
to smuggle her
out of here in
a laundry basket.
I know I should've
called Mr. Donatelli,
but the plain truth
of the matter is
I just saw red,
so I called the cops
instead.
Anyway, she's back.
Everything's fine.
All's well that ends well,
don't you know?
No harm, no foul, huh,
my little scissors legs?
Miss Hannigan,
what are you
talking about?
Hold it, sister.
Are you peddling
beauty products?
Because I don't need
no beauty products.
If that's what you're doing,
you can just peddle yourself
right on out of here, sweetie.
Miss Hannigan,
I am the private secretary
to Oliver Warbucks.
The Oliver Warbucks?
Oliver Warbucks,
the millionaire?
No.
Oliver Warbucks,
the billionaire.
(THUDS)
Holy Mary,
Mother of God.
Mr. Warbucks
would like to
invite an orphan
to spend a week
with him in his home.
(DOOR CREAKS OPEN)
I'm here to select one.
Well, that's just wonderful.
What kind
of an orphan did
he have in mind?
Oh, well, um...
Friendly.
Intelligent.
M, I,
double S, I,
double P, I.
And happy.
(ANNIE LAUGHING LOUDLY)
(GRACE LAUGHING)
Oh!
How old?
(CLEARING THROAT) Well,
age doesn't really matter.
MISS HANNIGAN: Uh-huh.
Seven?
Seven.
GRACE: Eight?
Eight.
Nine?
Nine.
GRACE: Ten?
Yes, ten's fine.
Ten's just fine.
Ten? Ten.
GRACE: (LAUGHING)
Oh, I'm so sorry.
I almost forgot.
Mr. Warbucks prefers
redheaded children.
10-year-old
redhead, huh?
Yes.
Nope. Sorry.
Ain't got it.
Well,
what about
this child?
Annie?
Yes.
(LAUGHING)
You wouldn't...
You don't want Annie.
Well, why not?
She's, uh...
She's a drunk.
Oh,
fiddle-faddle,
Miss Hannigan.
Annie, how would you
like to spend a week with
Mr. Warbucks at his house?
Oh, boy!
I would love to.
I would really,
really love to!
Hey, wait a minute.
Just slow down,
hold on there.
You can have any orphan
in the whole orphanage
except Annie.
Well, why?
Because she's got it
coming to her
and I don't mean a week
in the lap of luxury.
This brat's got to learn
to know her place.
Her place?
And Annie's entirely
too cheeky.
Well, Mr. Warbucks
likes cheeky orphans.
Tough!
I assume that
your resistance
has something to do
with Mr. Donatelli and
the Board of New York
Orphans.
Don't assume nothing,
sweetheart.
Well, Mr. Warbucks
and Mr. Donatelli
are like that.
Is that a fact?
Yes, that's a fact.
And it's also a fact that
he was out at the house
just the other day
and he was saying
how many people he had
lined up for your job.
Is that a fact?
That's a fact.
It's an awful
time to be out of work,
isn't it, Miss Hannigan?
Just terrible.
Leaping lizards!
"Leaping lizards!"
Come along, Annie.
Mr. Warbucks'
limousine is waiting.
My dog.
What?
Here, Sandy.
Come here.
He's really nice.
Really, really good.
He never jumps up
on people.
Oh, no! Oh!
Annie, he's a very,
very sweet dog,
but really, I don't think
it'll work. Mr. Warbucks...
Then I'm not coming.
What?
She's going to send him
to the sausage factory.
She said so herself.
I'm not zoned for dogs.
We'll take the dog.
Oh, boy.
Bye, Annie!
I'll be back.
I'll bring
everybody presents.
GIRLS: Bye! Bye! Bye, Annie!
Bye, Annie! So long!
Bye! Bye, Annie!
Bye!
Bye, Molly! See you soon.
Bye, Pepper! Bye, Duffy!
(GIRLS SHOUTING GOODBYE)
Is this a train station?
Are we going on a train?
No, dear, this is
Mr. Warbucks' house.
(SANDY BARKING)
Leaping lizards.
(WHIMPERING)
Wow!
Annie,
this is Punjab.
Punjab and the Asp are
Mr. Warbucks' bodyguards.
Come along, dear.
Let's get you settled.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(BOOK THUDS)
(SNEEZES)
Been to the zoo,
Miss Farrell?
Not recently, Drake.
Has the organ been tuned?
Yes, miss.
Pool heated?
Tennis court net up?
Uh, yes, Miss Farrell.
French doors fixed?
Yes, Miss Farrell.
GRACE: Elevator oiled?
MAN: Yes, ma'am.
Typewriter repaired?
Yes.
Second teletype installed?
(SNEEZES)
Are you allergic
to dogs, Drake?
No, filth.
Is dinner under way,
Mrs. Pugh?
Yes, miss.
I'm preparing
his favorite.
Texas grapefruit,
Virginia ham,
Idaho potatoes,
Wisconsin cheese,
Washington apples
and baked Alaska...
I have an announcement
to make, everybody.
I have an announcement.
This is Annie.
And she'll be staying
with us for a week.
STAFF: Hello, miss.
GRACE: And this
is her dog, Sandy.
ANNIE: Who'll be
staying with me.
(STAFF CHUCKLING)
May I take your
sweater, miss?
Will I get it back?
Of course, miss.
(ALL LAUGHING)
Now, Annie.
What would you
like to do first?
The windows.
Then the floors.
That way if I drip...
(ALL LAUGHING)
No, no, Annie.
You don't understand.
You don't
have to do any cleaning
while you're here with us.
I won't?
How am I gonna
earn my keep?
Why, you're our guest,
Annie.
* Cecile will pick out
all your clothes
Blue is her best color.
No, red, I think.
* Your bath is
drawn by Mrs. Greer
Soap. No, bubbles,
I think.
* Annette comes in
to make your bed
The silk?
No, the satin
sheets, I think.
* I think I'm gonna
like it here
(CAMERA CLICKS)
(GRUNTS)
Oh!
* The swimming pool
is down the stairs
Inside the house?
Oh, boy!
* The tennis court
is in the rear
I never even
picked up a racket.
What?
* Have an instructor
here at noon
Oh, and get that
Don Budge fellow,
if he's available.
* I think I'm gonna
like it here
* When you wake
* Ring for Drake
* Drake will
bring your tray
* When you're through
* Mrs. Pugh
comes to take it away
GRACE: Annie!
Annie!
Come on, Annie.
* No need to pick up any toys
That's okay.
I haven't got any anyway.
* No finger
will you lift
* My dear
* We have
but one request
* Please put us to the test
* I know I'm gonna
like it here
(MAIDS CHATTERING)
* Used to room
* In a tomb
* Where I'd sit and freeze
* Get me now
* Holy cow!
* Could someone
pinch me, please?
(DRAKE MUTTERING)
Hold still!
You mutt!
(ORGAN NOTE PLAYS)
(ORGAN NOTES PLAYING OFF-KEY)
Hey, Annie!
Got something for you.
Here you are, Annie.
* We've never
had a little girl
* I'm very, very
very glad to volunteer
* I'm glad
she's glad
to volunteer
* We hope you understand
* Your wish is our command
* I know I'm gonna like it
* We know you're gonna like it
* Here
(SIREN BLARING)
It's Mr. Warbucks.
Don't worry, now.
(SANDY BARKING)
Welcome home, sir.
Did the painting arrive?
Yes, they're just
uncrating it, sir.
Hmm...
I don't like it.
Send it back.
Any messages?
Yes, President Roosevelt
called three times, sir.
This morning.
He said it was very urgent.
Everything's urgent
to a Democrat.
What else?
Mr. Rockefeller,
Mr. Vanderbilt,
Mr. Du Pont,
Mr. Carnegie...
Wait! There's
something interesting
in that woman's smile.
I might
learn to like her.
Hang her in my bathroom.
Mr. Warbucks,
I'd like you...
No time for dinner tonight.
So tell Mrs. Pugh to send up
an American cheese sandwich
at midnight.
Come along,
Miss Farrell,
let's get started.
(YELLS)
Oh, no! No!
What the devil's
going on here?
Oh, Mr. Warbucks, this is
the press representative!
Your image!
Oh!
Uh-huh.
Oh, yes.
(LAUGHS)
Pick him up, Punjab.
Get him another camera.
(SNIFFING)
Why do I smell wet dog?
Because we gave
Sandy a bath.
What's this?
This is Annie, sir.
This is the orphan
who will be staying
with us for a week.
Orphan? What are
you talking about?
Well, they wanted to take
photographs of you sharing
your home, sir,
with an orphan.
Don't you remember, sir?
It's only for a week.
This doesn't
look like a boy.
Orphans are boys.
Oh, you didn't say
you wanted a boy, sir.
You just said an orphan,
so I got a girl.
I want a boy!
I've got an interesting
smile too, sir.
Don't you think maybe you
could learn to like me,
too, sir?
Hang me
in the bathroom?
Take them back now.
Oh, oh, sir,
she just got here.
That's okay,
Miss Farrell.
We'll be okay.
It was really nice
meeting you, anyhow.
I sure do
like your place.
Thank you, Annette.
Annie.
I've really had
a swell time already.
The Asp drove us here in
a car the size of a train,
Mr. Warbucks.
And Punjab put
a spell on Sandy.
And we made
Drake sneeze.
And I played
your pipe organ.
And Sandy got
a bubble bath.
And, well,
I've had enough fun
to last me for years.
It's a really swell
idea to have an orphan
for a week, Mr. Warbucks.
A really terrific idea.
Even if it's only
for your image,
even if I'm not
the orphan,
I'm glad
you're doing it.
I'm glad you approve.
Let's get to work!
Are you sure
you need a boy, sir?
It's only for a week.
Couldn't she stay?
WARBUCKS: Whatever!
But just for the week!
MAN ON RADIO: Know what?
What?
I love you.
I know.
Kiss me
as only you can.
Oh, you devil.
(GIRLS LAUGHING)
Oh, get away!
* Little girls, little girls
* Everywhere I turn
* I can see them
* Little girls, little girls
* Night and day I eat,
sleep and breathe them
* I'm an ordinary woman
with feelings
* I'd like a man
to nibble on my ear
* But I'll admit
no man has bit
* So how come
I'm the mother
of the year?
* How I hate little
shoes and little socks
* And each little...
DOLL: Mama.
* Bloomer
* I'd have cracked
years ago
* If it weren't
for my sense of humor
(DOLL CRIES)
* Some women are drippin'
with diamonds
with pearls
* Lucky me, lucky me
* Look at what
I'm drippin' with
* Little girls
(GASPS)
(GIRLS LAUGHING)
(GLASS CLINKS)
Ow.
Ah.
(GLASS CLINKS)
* Little cheeks, little teeth
* Everything around me is
* Little
* If I wring little necks
Surely I would get
* An acquittal
* Someday
I'll step on their freckles
* Some night
I'll straighten their curls
* Send a flood
Send the flu
* Anything that you can do
to little, little, little
* Little, little
Little, little
* Little girls
(LAUGHING)
(HICCUPPING)
* Someday
I'll land in
the nuthouse
* With all the nuts
and the squirrels
(LAUGHING SHRILLY)
* There I'll stay tucked away
* Till the prohibition of
* Little
* Girls
(SCREAMS)
(IMITATES ROOSTER CROWING)
Rooster.
Sis.
You're supposed
to be in jail.
They let me out early.
On account of
his good behavior.
I want you to meet
a little friend of mine.
Lily St. Regis.
Named from the hotel.
Room service.
Sis, this very afternoon
I put me 10 on the nose
of a beautiful horse at 8-1.
Sure enough, the scum-bum
took off and whipped the pack.
No kidding.
Thing is,
I got delayed.
And the joint was closed
before I could cash in.
80 bucks, sis, first thing
in the morning, guaranteed.
All I need is
a finnif to tide me over.
Not even a nickel
for the subway.
Oh, come on, sis.
I'll bet you
Miss Sticky-fingers here can
loan you a lousy five bucks.
I beg your pardon,
I'm sure, but I don't stoop
to what you're incinerating.
Give me back
my goods, toots.
(CLEARS THROAT)
Okay, Rooster.
If I loan you five bucks,
will you take this dumb
hotel
and just
get the heck
out of here?
I'm sorry, sis.
Lily.
Not even a nickel
for the subway.
You and her
have the same
mother?
(HICCUPS)
Rooster!
* Bet you he reads
* Bet you she sews
* Maybe she's made me
* A closet of clothes
* Maybe they're strict
* As straight as a line
* Don't really care
* As long as they're mine
* So maybe now this prayer's
* The last one of its kind
* Won't you please
come get your baby?
* Maybe
This room's bigger
than Grant's tomb.
(WHIMPERING)
Me, too.
(VASE CRASHES)
Come on, Sandy!
Come on!
WARBUCKS:
In conclusion,
because your country
has raised its voice
loud and clear for
freedom and democracy,
I will extend to you
a credit line
for the acquisition of 35
of my new fighter-bombers.
That will come complete with
a year supply of spare parts,
ammunition and advisors.
(SHOUTING)
What's this?
Sandy's not used to
sleeping in a room
all by himself.
He gets lonesome.
Oh. Where were we?
(STUTTERING) "Ammunition
and advisors," sir.
Are you getting
a lot done?
(SANDY BARKING)
I'd get a lot more done
if certain people...
(TYPEWRITER CLACKING)
If Franklin
Delano Roosevelt
would leave me alone.
Six calls
since I got home.
What's he want?
WARBUCKS: He wants
my support
for the New Deal.
It's laughable.
He is our president, sir.
Hmm.
Punjab!
Remove this animal
and its young mistress
along with it.
WARBUCKS: Dear Richie.
(GLASS SHATTERING)
This letter will
serve as confirmation
of all the correspondence
concerning the details
of your extended deferment.
The entire account...
(LOUD EXPLOSION)
...on or before
September the 1st.
If you cannot
meet that deadline,
(GRUNTING)
you'll have to be charged
the current rate of interest.
That is, 6%.
Cordially, et cetera.
Oh, P.S.
(MAN SINGING INDISTINCTLY)
I've just remembered,
one of my companies is
developing a bomb-proof glass
which may be
of interest to
your shipping line
if the present international
situation should deteriorate.
MAN: * Rise up,
ye victims of... *
What was that all about?
Well done, Sandy.
Was that man
trying to kill you?
That will be all,
Miss Farrell.
Yes, sir.
Come along, dear.
Who would want to
kill Mr. Warbucks?
The Bolsheviks, dear.
He's living proof that the
American system really works
and the Bolsheviks
don't want anybody
to know about that.
The Bolsheviks?
Leaping lizards!
(SANDY BARKING)
Get your blasted dog
out of my pool!
He thought you were drowning,
Mr. Warbucks.
He was trying
to save your life.
Come on, Sandy, come on.
Go on, you mutt.
Get out of here!
Come on, Sandy.
Yeah!
Like my suit?
What? Oh, yes.
Miss Farrell
picked it out.
I never thought
I'd get used to a girl.
Girls are easier to
get used to than boys.
Look how used to
Miss Farrell you are.
She does all the work
around here,
and you don't even
know her first name.
I do. It's Grace.
She thinks you're
the greatest thing
since sliced bread.
I beg your pardon?
I know it's none
of my business,
but you never
notice anything.
Sliced bread.
(PHONE RINGING)
WARBUCKS: Wilhelm,
how are you?
Please offer your son
my congratulations on
his engagement.
Hold on, Wilhelm.
Buy copper!
Yes.
And tell the crown prince
that my yacht in Monte Carlo
is entirely
at his disposal
for the honeymoon.
Hold on, Wilhelm.
More copper!
Don't encourage her,
Punjab!
I'm sorry, sir.
Maybe I should
take her out.
Good idea.
Where do you
want to go?
To Washington,
to meet
President Roosevelt.
How about a movie?
Pepper went
to a movie once,
before she came
to the orphanage,
and she said
it was swell.
And Miss Hannigan
goes all the time.
Splendid! Take her to
the Radio City Music Hall.
Aren't you gonna take me?
(SCOFFS) Me?
Annie, you may think
that Miss Farrell does
all the work around here,
but it's not
entirely true.
I'm a busy man.
A very busy man.
I know.
I didn't mean to get
in the way, Mr. Warbucks.
Nobody has to
take me anywhere.
I'll go practice
my backhand.
Pepper lies a lot.
She probably hasn't
been to a movie, either.
Actually,
I think it's better
when you don't know
what you're missing.
Punjab,
buy out the 8:00 show.
Let's all go
to the movies.
(BOTH GIGGLING)
You know, you should
leave your hair down.
It looks so pretty.
Oh, no, no, Annie.
I couldn't.
I just couldn't.
Miss Hannigan says
a man don't look at
your brains.
Oh, really?
My goodness!
Come on, Annie.
Let's go
to the movies.
Let's go see the stars.
Yeah.
* Cowboy heroes
Cops and robbers
* Glamour and strife
* Bigger than life
* Sitting in the darkness
* What a world to see
* Let's go
to the movies
* Annie, wait and see
* Bette Davis
is probably lying
* And Greta Garbo
is probably crying
* While Robert Taylor is
locked in her dying embrace
* Chico and Groucho
and Chaplin and Lloyd
are all super
* Sweet Mickey Mouse
Shirley Temple
* And dear Jackie Cooper
* Let's go
to the movies
BOTH: * Let's go see the stars
* Fred and Ginger
Spinning madly
* Anything you can imagine
* Songs and romance
* Life is a dance
* Sitting in the darkness
* Popcorn on your knee
* Give the maid
the night off
Turn the kitchen
light off!
* Let's go to the movies,
Annie
* You and me
* Welcome to the movies
* Welcome to the stars
* Welcome to this
grand illusion
* All of it's yours
* Right through these doors
* Every plot's a dilly
* This we guarantee
* Welcome to the movies
* Wait and see
* Let's go to the movies
* Let's go see the stars
* Headlines holler
* Big Depression
* What do we care?
* Movies are there
* Only happy endings
Boy gets girl
* That's our recipe
* Welcome to our lovely
* M-O-V-I-E
* We love to go to RKO
* Columbia, Universal
* Jack Warner
and Sam Goldwyn
* And MGM and Zanuck
* Here's to
* Dreams of glory
* Casts of thousands
* Bigger than life
* Only happy endings
* That's our recipe
* So welcome to the movies
* Wait
* And
* See
For the Lady
of the Camellias.
And they're almost
twice as large as usual.
I shall have
twice as many
as usual tomorrow.
Twice as ma...
Oh, don't listen
to her, Barjon.
I know what
those things cost.
Aren't you willing
to listen to her
when she orders her caps
and dresses from you?
They're an investment.
You won't be
young forever.
It's high time you settle
something about your future.
And I know
the very man for you.
MARGUERITE: Really?
WOMAN: Yes, really.
No one has
ever loved you
as I love you.
Well, it might be true.
But what can I do about it?
You should go away
and not see me anymore.
But don't go in anger.
Now,
why don't you laugh
at yourself a little,
as I laugh at myself,
and come talk to me
once in a while
in a friendly way.
ARMAND: That's too much
and not enough.
Believe in love,
Marguerite.
So you do love him?
Dare to tell me
that you love him,
and you're free
of me forever.
I love him.
Come in.
Come in here,
all of you.
See this woman?
You know her.
Then listen to what
I'm going to say.
Armand.
I accepted her favors
because I thought
she loved me.
I let her make
sacrifices for me
when there were others
who had more to give.
But bear witness,
I owe her nothing.
Take it.
Go on. Take it.
Buy camellias.
Buy diamonds,
horses and carriages.
Buy moonlight.
Buy a grave!
MAN: I congratulate you,
monsieur.
You know how to treat
a woman as she deserves.
Like the cheat this one is.
Marguerite.
(WEAKLY) Armand.
Marguerite!
Oh, it's you.
ARMAND: I've been
down in the street
half the night,
walking back and forth
under your window,
just as I did
when I first knew you,
wanting to come up,
but not daring to.
I felt so guilty.
Don't think such things,
Marguerite.
Even if we can't go
to the country today,
think of how happy
we were once,
and how happy
we shall be again.
Think of the day you found
the four-leaf clover,
and of all the good luck
it's going to bring us.
Think of the vows we heard
Nichette and Gustave make.
And that we're going to make,
to each other.
This is for life,
Marguerite.
No.
No, don't leave me!
Marguerite, come back.
(SNIFFLING)
Could you get her nightgown?
It's behind the bathroom door.
Certainly.
Miss Farrell...
No, no, no.
It's all right.
How did you
learn that?
Learn what?
That.
What?
You put her to bed.
Well,
you put her
to bed, too.
I did?
Yes, you did.
Good heavens.
(CHUCKLES)
That was a wonderful evening
you gave her last night, sir.
Just wonderful.
I gonna have to close
a factory in Pittsburgh,
Miss Farrell.
About Annie...
What about Annie?
Could we keep her?
You haven't seen
that horrible orphanage.
I can't bear to send her
back there. I can't.
Get a hold of yourself,
Miss Farrell.
What's come over you?
She wouldn't be a bother.
I'd take care of her.
You have
plenty of room here.
The staff adores her.
We could take her on as
your ward, couldn't we?
Absolutely not.
I'm a businessman.
I love money.
I love power.
I love capitalism.
I do not now,
and never will,
love children.
Watching you with her
last night, I thought maybe...
Grace.
Yes?
I just noticed
something.
Yes?
You're awfully pretty
when you argue with me.
Thank you, sir, but...
Oliver.
Do you really
just love money and
power and capitalism?
You know they're never
going to love you back.
Your teeth
are crooked.
I'll have them fixed.
I like them crooked.
I'll leave them.
Thank you.
I could
have the papers
signed this morning.
Grace.
Oliver.
It means a great deal
to you, doesn't it?
Yes, it means
a great deal to me.
I'll do it myself.
Oh, I could
just kiss you!
Grace.
Yes?
Get her a little gift.
That's a good idea.
Something from Tiffany's.
A new locket.
Oh, and you, you be careful
when you go to that orphanage.
That woman's got
claws and fangs.
* We got Annie
* We've got Annie?
* Yeah
* She's like
a shine on your shoes
* Or hearing the blues
that's great
* Makes you relax
* Like a big tax rebate
* We got Annie
STAFF: * We got Annie
* And Benny Goodman's
got swing
* Bing is the king,
by far
* Mutt has got Jeff
* And Eleanor, FDR
* We got Annie
* We've got Annie
(FINGER SNAPPING)
* We got Annie
* Annie
GIRLS: It's a hard-knock life
for us.
(WHISTLE BLOWS)
It's a hard-knock life
for us.
(WHISTLE BLOWS)
No one cares for you
a smidge
when you're in an orphanage.
(WHISTLE BLOWS)
What are you doing?
Why aren't you
marching in line
with the rest of them?
Duffy,
come here.
Come on.
You're hiding something
from Miss Hannigan
behind your back,
aren't you, Duffy?
No.
Let me have it.
(SCREAMING)
(GIRLS LAUGHING)
Get inside!
(GIRLS SCREAMING)
(DOORBELL RINGING)
(CROWD CHATTERING)
WOMAN: I think I seen
his picture in the paper
with President Roosevelt.
Hannigan,
I presume?
Yes.
I want to talk
to you about Annie.
You want to return her
and forget it,
or trade up?
I want to adopt her.
Would you excuse me
for a moment?
(MISS HANNIGAN SCREAMING)
Would you care to
step into my office?
Well, thank you.
Hi, sweetie.
What's she... Ow!
Ah, you little cutie.
Up, up, up,
up, up.
This way.
(GIRLS CHATTERING)
Welcome.
Miss Hannigan...
Mr. Warbucks,
do you know something?
For a Republican, you
are sinfully handsome.
Thank you.
Why, I just go absolutely
weak in the knees
over men like you.
My God!
Is that thing real?
Just sign the papers.
Wouldn't you like
to see the bedroom,
my little billiard ball?
Sign.
I make
a very dry martini.
Right here.
* I make
a very wet souffle
Just your name.
* Don't be so mean,
you mean old meanie.
Come, my dear.
* Let's you and me make
* Why shouldn't we make hay?
I have an appointment
at 1:00.
This way.
* You ever been
to Bonus Ayrees?
Where?
* I hunger
for the Argentein
Argentine.
* Let's me and you
fill up our diaries
What? Stop!
* Buy me a ruby
No!
* Why shouldn't you
be mine?
* Come
* I got your number
* Close
* You like to rumba
* Madam, while
* I'll call you Ollie
* We pry
* My hot tamale
* Through this
* And now I got ya
* File from
* My cucaracha
* My private eye
(EXCLAIMING)
* You spend your evenings
in the shanties
You had me followed?
* Imbibing quarts
of bathtub gin
Bronchitis.
* And here
you're dancing
in your scanties
Great gams.
* With some old geezer
called Little Caesar
He's an uncle.
* You lock the orphans
in the closet
They love it.
* You hock their
Christmas souvenirs
Drink?
* You steal the funds
you should deposit
It's fresh.
* You make them grovel
* While you buy lavalieres
* You'll
* Must you upset me?
* Sit out
* Why don't you pet me?
* This century
* It's you I crave now
* Let's misbehave now
* In some deep
* You wanna smoochie
* Dark
* My little poochie
* Penitentiary
Jail?
Sign!
* I guess
I'll never know the feeling
* You'll rot in jail
* Of running fingers
through your hair
* In Sing-Sing
* I guess this means
no Bonus Ayrees
* Will you sign?
* Well, I don't need you
* That's fine
* So just forget me
* The dotted line
* Forget my sweetness
* Don't whine
* Forget you met me
* You can't decline
* Today is sorta
* Just sign
* My bread-and-Waterloo
* Sign
Well, why didn't you
say so in the first place,
swine?
Women! Does it take this long
to get to Tiffany's and back?
(CAR PULLING UP)
Where is she?
I hear the car, sahib.
It's probably
not the right car.
It's the Duesenberg.
Miss Farrell
took the Duesenberg.
What took you
so long?
What's happening
around here?
Where's Annie?
She's taking her
karate lesson
with the Asp.
GRACE: Oh, Oliver,
don't be nervous.
Nervous?
I'm not nervous.
No, you give it
to her.
No, no, Oliver,
it was your idea.
She likes you better
than she likes me.
Oliver, will you
pull yourself together.
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
Oh, Mr. Warbucks, want to see
what the Asp taught me today?
(GRUNTING)
(SCREAMS)
To the couch, Punjab,
if you please.
Oh, gee,
I didn't think
it would work.
Well, now you
know it does, ha.
Should I call a doctor?
Oh, it'll be fine.
Punjab.
Thank you.
(SIGHS)
We'll leave
you two alone.
Annie, I wanna talk to you
about something very serious.
You don't want me
anymore, right?
On the contrary, I do.
Good Lord!
Annie, can we have
a man-to-man talk?
Sure.
What I'm proposing would
involve a long-term, uh,
well, agreement.
Actually,
maybe you ought to
know more about me
before you
make up your mind.
Okay.
Let's, uh,
let's go for a walk.
Okay.
I was born in Liverpool
in a railroad switch-house.
My younger brother
died of pneumonia
because we didn't have
money for medicine.
Well, I decided then and there
that one day I would be rich,
very, very rich.
Good idea.
In those days,
America was the
land of opportunity.
I signed on a ship as
cabin boy when I was 12.
By the time I was 21,
I'd made my first million.
In the next 10 years,
I turned that into
100 million.
Wow.
Hmm.
In those days,
that was a lot of money.
I was ruthless,
hurt a lot of people.
Making money was all I ever
gave a damn about, up to now.
Let's go inside.
Okay.
It's occurred to me
that no matter how
many houses I have,
how many Rembrandts,
how many Duesenbergs,
that unless I have
someone to share it with,
well, I might as well be
back in Liverpool, broke.
Annie, do you understand
what I'm trying to say?
Sure.
Good.
Kind of.
Kind of?
I guess not.
Damn!
Oh, excuse me.
You've given me so much
already, Mr. Warbucks.
I got the papers signed
today. It's official.
What is?
It's so pretty, but...
Let me put it on you.
No.
It's a really
swell locket,
Mr. Warbucks.
But if it's
all the same to you,
I'll keep my old one.
It isn't
all the same to me.
Your old one's broken.
This one's engraved.
You didn't even look at it.
"To Annie, with love,
from Daddy Warbucks."
Mr. Warbucks,
when my folks left
me at the orphanage
10 years ago,
they left a note
saying that
they'd come back to get
me as soon as they could.
And they kept
the other half
of this old locket
so I'd know them
when they came.
I'm gonna find them
someday, Mr. Warbucks.
I'm gonna
have a regular
mother and father,
like a regular kid.
I am.
I don't mean to
hurt your feelings.
You've been
nicer to me than anybody
in the whole wide world,
but I've been
dreaming of my folks
for as long
as I can remember,
and I just
got to find them.
And I'll help you.
Grace, get me
J. Edgar on the phone!
Drake, get me
the chief of police!
Asp, get me
Walter Winchell!
Punjab!
Get me William
Randolph Hearst!
And Saunders,
get me a drink.
Six, seven, eight, you're on.
* I-O-D
* E-N-T
* Iodent
* Hey, hobo man
* Hey, dapper Dan
* You both got your style
* But, brother,
you're never fully dressed
* Without a smile
(SHOES TAPPING)
* Your clothes may be
* Beau Brummelly
* They stand out a mile
* But, brother,
you're never fully dressed
* Without a smile
* Aha, the lovely
Boylan sisters
* Doot didoot doot doot
* Doot didoot
Doot doot doot
MAN: * Who cares
* What they're wearing
* On Main Street
or Savile Row
* It's what you wear
from ear to ear
* Ear to ear
* And not
from head to toe
* That matters
* Doot didoot
Doot doot... *
Tonight, as a special
heart-tugging treat
from that old
heart-tugger himself,
yours truly, Bert Healy,
I'd like
to introduce
a little orphan.
A little orphan
named Annie.
(FOOTSTEPS)
WACKY: Hey!
Who's that who just walked
into our Red Network studios?
Bert Healy?
Well, Wacky, it's none other
than the Wall Street tycoon,
Oliver Warbucks!
(APPLAUSE)
"Thank you, Bert Healy.
It's swell..."
Swell? Do I say...
"Swell to be
on the Iodent Hour."
I understand you're conducting
a coast-to-coast search
for Annie's parents.
Yeah, I told you that
before we went on the air...
Oh, yes!
"Bert Healy.
"I am now conducting
a coast-to-coast
"nationwide search
for Annie's parents.
"Drop page.
"Warbucks continues.
"Furthermore, tonight
I am offering a cash reward
"to Annie's parents,
$50,000 cash."
Oh, Mr. Warbucks!
Oh, boy.
50,000 smackers!
So Annie's parents,
if you're listening,
please contact
Oliver Warbucks...
"Warbucks interrupts!
"At my house, Bert Healy,
987 Fifth Avenue,
New York City."
"Thank you,
Bert Healy,
"and thank you,
all-new Iodent,
"the toothpaste
with miracle K-64
"to fight hali..."
Hali...
Tosis!
"For letting me
talk to you this evening.
"Good night, Bert Healy,
"and good night
for the Red Network.
"Drop page!"
Did I just do a commercial?
Let's get out of here.
I've never endorsed
a product in all my career.
* Doot doot
Didoot doot doot
* Doot didoot doot
Doot doot doot doo *
So for all of you,
our smiles family,
this is Bert Healy
saying...
(GIRLS GIGGLING)
* Hey, hobo man
* Hey, dapper Dan
* You both got your style
(MOUTHING)
* But, brother,
you're never fully dressed
* Without a smile
(FEET TAPPING)
* Your clothes may be
* Beau Brummelly
* They stand out a mile
* But, brother,
you're never fully dressed
* Without a smile
(TAPPING)
* Who cares
* What they're wearing
* On Main Street
or Savile Row
* It's what you wear
from ear to ear
* And not from head to toe
* That matters
Ah, the lovely
Boylan sisters.
* I-O-D
* E-N-T
* Doot didoot
Doot doot
Doot doot doot
* So, senator
So, janitor
* So long for a while
* Remember you're
never fully dressed
* Without a smile
* Oh, you're never fully
dressed without a smile
* You're never fully dressed
without a smile
* Who cares
what they're wearing
* On Main Street
or Savile Row
* It's what you wear
from ear to ear
* Ear to ear
* And not from head to toe
* That matters
* So, senator
So, janitor
* So long for a while
* Remember you're never
fully dressed
* Though you may
wear the best
* You're never
fully dressed
* Without a smile
* You're never
fully dressed
* Oh! You're
never fully dressed
* Oh! You're never
fully dressed
* Without a...
Do I hear
happiness in here?
They never miss.
(CROWD YELLING)
MAN:
Everybody's going to
get their chance here.
Annie! Annie,
it's your mama!
Annie, here I come!
Annie, darling!
We've got to get her
out of here, Mr. Warbucks.
We can't expose
her to this.
Get the autocopter ready.
Wow!
Annie, guess what?
Mr. Warbucks is gonna
take you to Washington
to see the president!
Oh, boy!
(GRACE LAUGHING)
Marvelous!
Aren't Republicans
ostentatious?
Franklin, behave.
It's astonishing
that he's here at all.
(ROOSEVELT LAUGHING)
What do you call
this thing, Oliver?
It looks like great fun.
WARBUCKS: An autocopter.
Don't need an airport,
just a back yard.
They say it can
land on a dime,
whatever that may be.
I appreciate
you coming down.
It means a great deal.
Means nothing.
Means only that
Annie wanted
to meet you.
It's nice to meet you,
Mr. President Roosevelt.
It's my pleasure,
Annie.
And thank you for
bringing the old goat.
We'll make a New Dealer
of him yet.
Inconceivable.
Don't mind him, Oliver.
Come along, Annie.
My Uncle Theodore,
Teddy Roosevelt,
used to
teach his children
to walk on stilts.
Well, I can't teach
you to walk on stilts,
but I can
teach you to roll
in a chair with wheels.
My own private
roller coaster.
The New Deal,
in my opinion,
is badly planned,
badly organized
and badly administered.
You don't think your
programs through, Franklin.
You don't think
what they're gonna do to
the economy in the long run.
People don't eat
in the long run.
People can't feed
their children.
The lucky ones end up
in orphanages.
ELEANOR: The older ones
are abandoned to steal,
to starve.
The business of this
country is business.
You have to organize...
Take them
off the dole and
put them to work.
That is precisely
what I intend to do.
In the
National Parks,
building camps,
clearing trails,
fighting fires,
planting trees.
Hold it! Hold it!
I want
to feed them,
and house them,
and pay them.
Not much,
but enough
to send home
to their parents,
so they can hold
their heads up again,
and be proud
to be Americans.
That's a swell idea.
It isn't a swell idea, Annie.
It's mistaken foolishness!
Big-hearted
and empty-headed!
Which parks,
which children?
What will it cost?
Who's gonna organize it?
Who's gonna run it?
I was hoping you would.
Me?
And Annie.
Leaping lizards!
Out of the question!
How could I help?
WARBUCKS:
Wait a minute!
You could help us
recruit the young people.
Now, hold everything!
Many of them have
given up hope, Annie.
They think their
government doesn't care
whether they live or die.
With your help,
we could convince them that
with a little extra effort...
I want to say something.
There's this song
I used to sing
in the orphanage
when I'd get sad.
It always
cheered me up.
Eleanor!
* Just thinkin'
about tomorrow
* Clears away
the cobwebs
and the sorrow
* Till there's none
* When I'm stuck
with a day that's gray
* And lonely
* I just stick out my chin
* And grin
* And say
* Oh
* The sun'll come out tomorrow
* So you gotta hang on
till tomorrow
* Come what may
* Tomorrow, tomorrow
* I love ya, tomorrow
* You're only a day away
Oh, Franklin.
You'll help us too,
won't you, Oliver?
(SCOFFS)
Think of the children.
Think of Annie.
* The sun'll
come out tomorrow
Sing, Oliver.
That's an order from
your commander-in-chief.
* There'll be sun
ROOSEVELT: Eleanor.
I can't sing.
Sing.
* Tomorrow
* Clears away the cobwebs
and the sorrow
* Till there's none
Solo for the president!
* When I'm stuck
with a day
* That's gray
* And lonely
* I just
stick out my chin
* And grin and say
Everybody!
Republicans, too,
Oliver. Sing!
* The sun'll come out tomorrow
* So you gotta hang on
till tomorrow
* Come what may
Harmony!
* Tomorrow, tomorrow
I love ya, tomorrow
* You're only a day away
* Tomorrow, tomorrow
I love ya, tomorrow
* You're only a day
* Away
All right, everybody,
come on, step up here!
I got fresh fish here!
Give me two,
right there.
(DOORBELL RINGS)
Yeah?
Excuse me,
are you the lady who
runs this establishment?
Unfortunately.
Ten years ago,
we left our little baby
girl on the front steps.
We were starving.
There was a job
managing a hotel
in Maine,
but only if we
had no children.
Wrap it up,
I'm listening
to Helen Trent.
We never meant to
leave our little Annie.
Annie?
Now, we have
a hardware store
in New Jersey.
We could
take care of her.
We've always
loved her.
You're Annie's parents?
Our place isn't fancy,
but it's home.
We live
over the store.
There's a yard
out back.
We have chickens.
And a rooster.
(IMITATES ROOSTER CROWING)
Rooster?
My God!
I never would've
recognized you.
Oh, sis,
if we can fool you,
we can fool "Big Bucks."
(LILY CHUCKLING)
50,000
smackers!
You're gonna be
the death of me,
Rooster.
Oh, come on, sis.
This is gonna be
the best bunco job ever.
All we need
is details.
About Annie, specifics.
I see.
What's in it for me?
Money!
A three-way split
of the 50 thou.
I want half.
Half?
Half.
All right, half.
Rooster!
All right!
25 grand
for me and Lil,
25 grand for you.
Hey!
Why don't
we wait and see
what she's got, huh?
See if it's
worth 25 grand.
(SCREAMS)
You want details?
I got details.
I got specifics on
every kid in this dump.
It's just a question
of finding the right box!
(SCOFFS)
Annie
wears a locket
around her neck.
It's a broken locket.
She says her parents
saved the other half
to someday come
and claim her with.
Well, years ago...
Years and years ago,
her parents
were killed in a fire.
And the cops brought me
all their junk.
Well, my darling
baby brother,
if Annie's parents can
claim her with that locket,
so can we!
LILY: 50,000 smackers!
ROOSTER: And the kid,
we'll drop in the river.
They're gonna do
something bad to Annie!
Pepper!
Have you cleaned the can?
Listen to me,
I mean it!
PEPPER: Clean the can!
Duffy, Tessie, somebody!
You want
a knuckle sandwich?
We got to
warn Annie!
Scrub!
It's in an envelope.
A sealed envelope.
* It ain't fair
how we scrounge
* For three or four bucks
* While she gets Warbucks
The little brat!
Look in those.
* It ain't fair
This here life
is driving me nuts
Make yourself useful.
* When we get peanuts
* She's living fat
* Maybe she
holds the key
* That little lady
* To getting
more bucks
Right
instead of left.
It'll have
her name on it.
* Maybe we fix'a the game
* With something shady
* Where does
that put us?
* Give you one guess
(LILY SQUEALING)
Open it.
(IMITATING TEARING SOUND)
Hurry.
* Easy Street
(IMITATES ROOSTER CROWING)
* Annie is the key
* Yes, sirree
* Easy Street
* We'll live
the plush life
* Easy Street
* The lazy lush life
* Better get there
* The gravy's flowing there
* We'll soon be going there
* Where you sleep
till noon
* Yeah, yeah, yeah
* Move them feet
* Move them
ever-lovin' feet
* Easy Street
where living's sweet
* That's where we're gonna be
(HORN BLOWING)
* Easy Street
(GROANS)
(FINGER SNAPPING)
* Move them feet
* To Easy Street
* That's where we're gonna
* Yeah
Hit it, sis.
* That's where we're gonna
* Stay
* Easy Street
(CRYING)
Now, do the other one.
GIRL 1: You hit
that jack. I saw you.
GIRL 2: It's my turn.
Ow!
Duffy, Tessie,
somebody!
They're going to do
something bad to Annie.
Who is?
They are.
TESSIE: Who's they?
Miss Hannigan.
Oh, my goodness!
(FOOTSTEPS PATTERING)
It's beautiful.
(GIRLS WHISPERING)
GIRL: Shh.
Be quiet, be quiet.
Where do you think
you're going?
Go tell Annie!
(GIRLS SCREAMING)
Oh, my goodness!
Let's go,
you brats!
Don't! Don't!
Come on!
GIRL: Stop it!
LILY: Shut up!
Get in that closet!
Behave yourself!
Get in there!
(GIRLS SCREAMING)
Go in there!
Whose rotten
idea was this?
(GIRLS CRYING)
Christ!
(SANDY BARKING)
Are they here?
Did they bring me
a brother and sister?
Buddha says, man who
counts his chickens
before they hatch
gets a scrambled egg.
What?
Have my parents
come for me?
We haven't found them,
Annie.
I interviewed
865 couples.
None of them knew
about the locket.
I never realized how
many dishonest people
there are in New York.
I guess
they're dead.
I guess I've known that
deep down for a long time.
I'm not giving up.
Don't you give up.
I didn't want to be
just another orphan,
Mr. Warbucks.
I wanted to believe
I was special.
You are special.
Never stop
believing that.
We're trapped
in here!
Shh!
Annie's never
gonna get saved.
Oh, my goodness.
Poor Annie.
We'll never get
out of here, now.
I've got an idea.
What?
Great. Good idea.
GIRL: Oh, it's heavy.
Don't drop it.
Come on.
We can do it.
All right.
Now lean it over.
Shh!
MOLLY:
She'll be so mad
if she catches us.
GIRL 1:
I'm not so sure
I want to do this.
GIRL 2: We're going to be
in so much trouble anyway.
Duffy,
hand me something.
Oh, give her
something to hit with.
(GIRLS GIGGLING)
There's a space
up here.
TESSIE: Careful.
Oh, my goodness!
Somebody's gonna have
to help me get up.
Ow! Get off my hand!
I'm trying not to push!
We're out.
DUFFY: Give me your hand.
PEPPER: It's a long way down.
You sure you want to
go through with it?
Wish me luck.
Good luck.
Careful.
Don't slip.
I'm trying.
(GIRLS CHATTERING)
We were starving, ma'am.
We needed the job.
That's why
we left our
little girl.
Wrapped in
a newspaper.
On the steps of the
Hudson Street Orphanage.
What's this?
GRACE:
Mr. Warbucks, this is
Ralph and Shirley Mudge
from Hoboken, New Jersey.
Annie!
Oh!
Oh, Ralph, look.
She still has the locket.
We finally found you.
I suppose you heard
about the reward
on the radio?
Reward?
We don't have a radio.
In the paper.
Paper?
What paper?
How did you know
Annie was here?
That kind lady
at the orphanage
told us.
I have her
birth certificate
right here.
I've kept it
close to my heart
all of these years.
"Anne Marie Mudge.
"October the 18th, 1922."
I'll go pack.
Want me to help, baby?
No, thanks.
Mom.
We've got
to find her.
Come on!
A certified check!
Oh, sir, we're just so
thrilled to have found
Annie.
We don't need any money.
I'll take it back.
Of course
we are poor people.
It would
help us a lot.
We could
buy her milk,
a warm blanket...
Put it in your pocket.
Mrs. Mudge.
Come on, you guys.
Oh, my goodness!
We're never gonna
make it.
We found
Fifth Avenue!
Number one,
We got to go
to 987.
(ALL GROANING)
Come on, Molly,
get on my back.
Come on, you guys,
help!
Do you think
the stores would
take all this back?
All your new clothes?
Well, I guess so, Annie,
but don't you
want to keep them?
My new folks,
they're poor.
All these clothes
are gonna make
them feel bad.
Could you maybe
take them back
to the orphanage
and give them
to my friends?
Certainly.
This'll look
so cute on Molly.
And this'll
look good on Duffy.
* Bet you my life
is gonna be swell
* Looking at them
it's easy to tell
* And maybe I'll forget
* How nice he was to me
* And how I was
almost his baby *
(SIGHS)
* It'll be fine
* Nothing to fear
* She'll be as happy
* As she was here
* Things have worked out
* Much better than planned
* It makes you smile
* When fate takes a hand
* And I know I'll forget
* How much she meant to me
* And how she was almost my
* Baby
* Maybe
(TIRES SQUEALING)
Did you get it?
She has it.
Let me see it.
You know, I think maybe
I'd better hold it
for safekeeping.
Over my dead body.
That's the brightest thing
I've ever heard you say.
ROOSTER: Ladies, ladies.
Help!
Mr. Warbucks, help!
Get on the road!
GIRL 1: We'll never
find the house.
GIRL 2: I wish
I'd been outside
New York City before.
(SQUEALING EXCITEDLY)
When I get
my half of it...
(SANDY BARKING)
I say we go back.
We can't!
We've been walking
for 100 years!
We're never
going to get there.
But we have to.
Let's take a vote.
All in favor
of calling it quits.
Ah-ha!
Oh, I'm gonna get me
one of those little
gold lam numbers.
If they sell them
in Atlantic City.
We ain't stopping
till we hit Atlantic City!
(WHOOPING)
Boo.
Help, Mr. Warbucks!
It's Miss Hannigan!
Shut up, kid.
Look!
There's Sandy!
(CLAMORING)
(MUFFLED)
Mr. Warbucks is
gonna be furious!
Come here, Sandy!
Come here!
Come on!
Let's go!
Come on, you guys!
Hurry it up!
Hurry! Hurry!
I can't run anymore.
(SANDY BARKING)
(SANDY WHIMPERS)
(BARKS)
Hurry!
(SANDY BARKING)
(GIRLS CLAMORING)
All right, now.
Quiet down, girls.
You want to see
Mr. Warbucks?
All right.
Come on. Come on.
GIRLS: Mr. Warbucks!
Oh, my goodness!
(CLAMORING)
(SHOUTING) What now?
Sir...
I think
he's a highness.
Your Highness...
We're friends
of Annie's.
Annie's gone.
PEPPER: Oh, no!
Her parents came
and took her away.
But they wasn't her
real parents, mister.
They was bad people.
Leaping lizards!
(PHONE RINGING)
You take the autocopter,
I'll take the car.
Edgar, J. Edgar,
Warbucks here.
Yeah, orphan Annie
has been kidnapped.
I want every G-man east of
the Mississippi on this case
in the next 20 minutes.
(SIRENS BLARING)
MAN: Where's the fire, fellas?
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(SIRENS BLARING)
Sahib, sahib.
The truck is on
Canal Street,
heading east.
East on Canal Street.
Well done, Punjab.
Don't lose track
of them now.
(SIRENS BLARING)
Excuse me, mister.
Can we stop a second?
I got to go.
I really got to,
Miss Hannigan.
(HORN HONKING)
I mean it, lady.
You're asking for it.
When you got to go,
you got to go.
(BOAT HORN HONKING)
Make it fast.
(SCREAMS)
Rooster, grab her!
She got the check!
Cut her off
at the bridge!
God damn it!
ROOSTER:
Come back here,
you goddamn kid!
(ENGINE REVVING)
No!
Mr. Warbucks'll
eat your livers!
No!
I'll kill you.
I'll kill you,
you little brat!
I'll kill you!
Wring her neck,
Rooster!
He's really
gonna kill her.
MISS HANNIGAN:
Rooster!
Rooster, stop!
Rooster,
she's a baby!
ROOSTER: Come back here!
(BRIDGE BELLS RINGING)
Rooster!
I'm gonna kill her!
No, I'm not
gonna let you!
She may be a mean,
rotten little orphan,
but I'm not gonna
let you kill her!
ROOSTER:
Let go of me,
you old boozer!
MISS HANNIGAN: Stop it!
Just stop it!
(SIRENS BLARING)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(CAR HORNS HONKING)
Sahib, sahib.
They're at
the B&O bridge.
They're on the bridge.
Turn right.
I know. I know.
(AUTOCOPTER WHIRRING)
POLICEMAN 1:
Hold it up over here.
POLICEMAN 2:
Get in there, let's go.
Help, somebody!
Help! Please help!
Help, somebody! Help!
Leave me alone!
Please, help!
(SCREAMS)
FIREMAN:
Come on! Hurry up!
Let's go!
Get the ladders in there!
(ANNIE SCREAMING)
ANNIE: Somebody help me!
Somebody help me!
FIREMAN:
Come on, over here!
Hurry it up there.
Bring it in, guys!
(SCREAMS)
Help! Help!
Have we got two nets? No?
Okay, well, we'll make do.
FIREMAN: Hurry up!
You're too slow. Let's go.
Please!
Punjab!
Help me!
Help me, Punjab!
Help!
Punjab, help!
(ANNIE CRYING)
To pull you to safety
I need both hands.
You must hold on.
I can't.
Buddha says
a child without courage
is like a night
without stars.
Come!
(LAUGHING)
FIREMAN: That's it.
Back it in here.
(GRUNTS)
(ROOSTER SCREAMING)
Rooster, you reprobate!
Okay, let's clear
the area over here!
Perfect! Perfect!
That's it,
bring them up here.
(FIREMEN SHOUTING COMMANDS)
* Together at last
* Together forever
* We're tying a knot
* They never can sever
* I don't need
sunshine now
* To turn
my skies to blue
* I don't need anything
but you
(FIRECRACKERS BURSTING)
* You've wrapped me
around
* That cute
little finger
* You've made
life a song
* You've made me
the singer
* And what's that
bathtub tune
* You always
ba ba boo?
* Ba ba ba
But you
* Yesterday
was plain awful
* You can say
that again
* Yesterday
was plain awful
* But that's
* Not now
* That's then
* I'm poor
as a mouse
Ha, ha!
* I'm richer
than Midas
Oliver, that's marvelous!
* But nothing on Earth
* Could ever divide us
* And if tomorrow
* I'm an apple seller, too
* I don't need anything
* Anything, anything
* I don't need anything but
* She's like the fizz
in a Coke
* A buck when you're broke
* And more
* When woes and worries
take hold
* Who gives them
the old trap door?
* I do not mind repeating
* We got Annie
* That 4th of July kid!
* I wish she were my kid
* We've got Annie
* And she's got it all
Annie!
"To Annie,
with love."
I love you,
Daddy Warbucks.
* Tomorrow
* I love ya, tomorrow
* You're only a day away
(FIRECRACKERS BURSTING)
* Tomorrow
(BARKING)
* I love ya, tomorrow
* You're only a day
* Away
* The sun'll come out
* Tomorrow
* Bet your bottom dollar
that tomorrow
* There'll be sun
* Just thinking about
* Tomorrow
* Clears away the cobwebs
and the sorrow
* Till there's none
* When I'm stuck
with a day
* That's gray
* And lonely
* I just stick out
my chin
* And grin
* And say
* Oh
* The sun'll come out
* Tomorrow
* So you gotta hang on
till tomorrow
* Come what may
* Tomorrow
* I love ya, tomorrow
* You're only a day away
* Tomorrow
* I love ya, tomorrow
* You're only a day
* Away
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/9jf3m
Help other users to choose the best subtitles