♪♪ [“Superstar” Instrumental ]
♪♪ [Discordant Note]
♪ My mind is clearer now ♪
♪ At last, all too well ♪
♪ I can see ♪
♪ Where we all
soon will be ♪
♪ If you strip away ♪
♪ The myth from the man ♪
♪ You will see ♪
♪ Where we all
soon will be ♪
♪ Jesus ♪
♪ You've started to believe
the things they say of you ♪
♪ You really do believe
this talk of God is true ♪
♪ And all the good you've done
will soon get swept away ♪
♪ You've begun
to matter more ♪
♪ Than the things you say ♪
♪ Listen, Jesus
I don't like what I see ♪
♪ All I ask is that
you listen to me ♪
♪ And remember ♪
♪ I've been your right-hand man
all along ♪
♪ You have set them all
on fire ♪
♪ They think they've found
the new messiah ♪
♪ And they'll hurt you
when they find they're wrong ♪
♪ I remember when
this whole thing began ♪
♪ No talk of God then
We called you a man ♪
♪ And believe me ♪
♪ My admiration for you
hasn't died ♪
♪ But every word
you say today ♪
♪ Gets twisted 'round
some other way ♪
♪ And they'll hurt you
if they think you've led ♪
♪ Nazareth, your famous son
should have stayed a great unknown ♪
♪ Like his father carving wood
he'd have made good ♪
♪ Tables, chairs and oaken chests
would have suited Jesus best ♪
♪ He'd have caused nobody harm
No one alarm ♪
♪ Listen, Jesus
Do you care for your race? ♪
♪ Don't you see
we must keep in our place ♪
♪ We are occupied ♪
♪ Have you forgotten
how put down we are ♪
♪ I am frightened
by the crowd ♪
♪ For we are getting
much too loud ♪
♪ And they'll crush us
if we go too far ♪
♪ If we go ♪
♪ Too far ♪
♪ Listen, Jesus
to the warning I give ♪
♪ Please remember
that I want us to live ♪
♪ But it's sad
to see our chances ♪
♪ Weakening with every hour ♪
♪ Your followers are blind ♪
♪ Too much heaven
on their minds ♪
♪ It was beautiful
but now it's sour ♪
♪ Yes, it's all ♪
♪ Gone sour ♪
♪ Oh-oh, oh-oh-oh-oh
Oh-oh, oh-oh-oh-oh ♪
♪ Listen, Jesus
to the warning I give ♪
♪ Please remember
that I want us to live ♪
♪ So come on, come on
He won't listen to me ♪
♪ Ah, Ah-ah-ah
Oh-oh-oh ♪
♪ Come on, listen
Listen to me ♪
♪ Come on
and listen to me ♪
♪ Ah, Ahh
Oh-oh-oh-oh ♪
♪ Come on
Listen to me ♪
♪ Come on, listen
♪ Ah-ah-ahh
Ohh, oh-oh-ohh ♪
♪ Come on
Listen to me ♪
♪ Listen to me ♪♪
♪ What's the buzz
Tell me what's happening ♪
♪ What's the buzz ♪
♪ Tell me what's
a-happening What's the buzz ♪
a-happenin' ♪
♪ What's the buzz
Tell me what's a-happening ♪
Tell me what's a-happenin' ♪
♪ What's the buzz
♪ Why should you
want to know ♪
♪ Don't you mind
about the future ♪
♪ Don't you try
to think ahead ♪
♪ Save tomorrow
for tomorrow ♪
- ♪ Think about today instead ♪
- ♪ What's the buzz Tell me what's a-happenin' ♪
- ♪ What's the buzz Tell me what's a-happening ♪
- ♪ I could give you ♪
- ♪ Facts and figures ♪
- ♪ What's the buzz Tell me what's a-happenin' ♪
- ♪ Even give you pains and forecasts ♪
- ♪ When do we ride to Jerusalem ♪
- ♪ Even tell you where I'm goin' ♪
♪ When do we ride to Jerusalem
When do we ride to Jerusalem ♪
♪ Why should you
want to know ♪
♪ Why are you obsessed
with fighting ♪
♪ Times and fates
you can't defy ♪
♪ If you knew
the path we're riding ♪
♪ You'd understand it
less than I ♪
♪ What's the buzz
Tell me what's a-happenin' ♪
♪ Let me try to cool
down your face a bit, ♪
down your face a bit ♪
♪ Let me try to cool
♪ Let me try to
cool down your face ♪
♪ Oh, let me try
Let me try ♪
♪ To cool down your face ♪
♪ Let me try to cool down
your face a bit ♪
♪ Mary, mmm, that is good ♪
♪ While you prattle
through your supper ♪
♪ Where and when
and who and how ♪
♪ She alone
is trying to give me ♪
♪ What I need
right here and now ♪
♪ What's the buzz
Tell me what's a-happenin' ♪
Tell me what's a-happening ♪
♪ What's the buzz
Tell me what's a-happenin' ♪
Tell me what's a-happening ♪
♪ What's the buzz
Tell me what's a-happenin' ♪
Tell me what's a-happening ♪
♪ What's the buzz
Tell me what's a-happenin' ♪
♪ It seems to me
a strange thing ♪
♪ Mystifying ♪
♪ That a man like you
can waste his time ♪
♪ On women of her kind ♪
Hey, cool it, man.
[ Chuckling ]
♪ Yes, I can understand that ♪
♪ She amuses ♪
♪ But to Let her kiss you
and stroke your hair ♪
♪ That's hardly
in your line ♪
♪ It's not that I object
to her profession ♪
♪ But she doesn't fit in well
with what you teach and say ♪
♪ It doesn't help us
if you're inconsistent ♪
♪ They only need
a small excuse ♪
♪ To put us all away ♪
♪ Who are you
to criticize her ♪
to despise her ♪
♪ Leave her, Leave her
Let her be now ♪
She's with me now ♪
♪ If your slate is clean
then you can throw stones ♪
♪ If your slate is not
then leave her alone ♪♪
- Hey, Jesus, what do we say?
- [ Disciples Chattering ]
[ Chattering, Indistinct ]
♪ I'm amazed
that men like you ♪
♪ Can be so shallow
thick and slow ♪
♪ There is not a man among you
who knows or cares if I come or go ♪
♪ No, you're wrong
You're very wrong ♪
♪ How can you say that
How can you say that ♪
How can you say that ♪♪
Not one.
Not one of you!
♪ We've been sitting on the fence
for far too long ♪
♪ Why Let him
upset us ♪
♪ Caiaphas, Let him be ♪
♪ All those imbeciles
will see ♪
♪ He really
doesn't matter ♪
♪ Jesus is important ♪
♪ We've Let him
go his way before ♪
♪ And while he starts
a major war ♪
♪ We theorize
and chatter ♪
♪ He's just another
Scripture-thumping hack from Galilee ♪
♪ The difference is
they call him King ♪
♪ The difference
frightens me ♪
What about the Romans?
♪ When they see
King Jesus crowned ♪
♪ Do you think
they'll stand around ♪
♪ Cheering and applauding ♪
♪ What about our people ♪
♪ If they see
we've lost our nerve ♪
♪ Don't you think
that they deserve ♪
♪ Something more rewarding ♪
♪ They've got
what they want ♪
♪ They think so anyway ♪
♪ If he's what they want ♪
♪ Why take
their toy away ♪
♪ He's a craze ♪
♪ Put yourself in my place
I can hardly step aside ♪
♪ Cannot Let my hands
be tied ♪
♪ I am law and order ♪
♪ What about our priesthood ♪
♪ Don't you see
that we could fall ♪
♪ If we are to last
at all ♪
♪ We cannot be divided ♪
♪ Then say so
to the Council ♪
♪ But don't rely
on subtlety ♪
♪ Frighten them
or they won't see ♪
♪ Then we are decided ♪♪
Then we are decided.
♪ Try not to get worried
Try not to turn onto ♪
♪ Problems that upset you ♪
♪ Don't you know
everything's all right ♪
♪ Yes, everything's fine ♪
♪ And we want you
to sleep well tonight ♪
♪ Let the world turn
without you tonight ♪
♪ If we try, we'll get by
so forget all about us ♪
- ♪ Tonight ♪
- ♪ Everything's all right, yes ♪
♪ Everything's
all right, yes ♪
♪ Sleep and I shall soothe you
calm you and anoint you ♪
- ♪ Myrrh for your hot forehead ♪
- ♪ Ah ♪
♪ Then you'll feel everything's all right
Yes, everything's fine ♪
♪ And it's cool and
the ointment's sweet ♪
♪ For the fire
in your head and feet ♪
♪ Close your eyes
Close your eyes ♪
♪ And relax
Think of nothing ♪
- ♪ Tonight ♪
- ♪ Everything's all right, yes ♪
- ♪ Hey, hey, woman ♪
♪ Your fine ointment
brand-new and expensive ♪
♪ Should have been saved
for the poor ♪
♪ Why has it been wasted
We could have raised maybe ♪
♪ Three hundred
silver pieces or more ♪
♪ People who are hungry
People who are starving ♪
♪ They matter more
than your ♪
♪ Feet and hair ♪
♪ Try not to get worried
Try not to turn onto ♪
- ♪ Problems that upset you ♪
- ♪ Oh ♪
- ♪ Don't you know everything's all right ♪
- ♪ All right, yes ♪
- ♪ Everything's all right, yes ♪
- ♪ Surely you're not saying ♪
♪ We have the resources ♪
♪ To save the poor
from their lot ♪
♪ There will be poor always
pathetically struggling ♪
♪ Look at the good things
you've got ♪
♪ Think while
you still have me ♪
♪ Move while
you still see me ♪
♪ You'll be Lost
and you'll be sorry ♪
♪ When I'm gone ♪
[ Mary Magdalene ]
♪ Sleep and I shall soothe you
calm you and anoint you ♪
- ♪ Myrrh for your hot forehead ♪
- ♪ Oh ♪
♪ Then you'll feel
everything's all right, yes ♪
♪ Everything's fine and it's cool
and the ointment's sweet ♪
♪ For the fire
in your head and feet ♪
♪ Close your eyes
Close your eyes and relax ♪
- ♪ Think of nothing tonight ♪
- ♪ Tonight close your eyes and relax ♪
- ♪ Think of nothing ♪
- ♪ Close your eyes, Close your eyes ♪
- ♪ And relax ♪
- ♪ Everything's all right, yes ♪
- ♪ Close your eyes Close your eyes and relax ♪
♪ Everything's all right, yes
Everything's all right ♪♪
♪ Good Caiaphas ♪
♪ The Council
waits for you ♪
♪ The Pharisees ♪
♪ And priests
are here for you ♪
♪ Ah, gentlemen ♪
♪ You know
why we are here ♪
♪ We've not much time ♪
♪ And quite
a problem here ♪
[ Men ]
♪ Hosanna, Superstar ♪
♪ Hosanna
Superstar ♪
[ Women ]
♪ Hosanna, Superstar ♪
♪ Hosanna
Superstar ♪
♪ Listen to
that howling mob ♪
♪ Of blockheads
in the street ♪
♪ A trick or two
with lepers ♪
♪ And the whole town's
on its feet ♪
[ All ]
♪ He is dangerous ♪
♪ Jesus Christ
Superstar ♪
♪ He is dangerous ♪
♪ Tell us that you're
who they say you are ♪
♪ That man is in town right now
to whip up some support ♪
♪ A rabble-rousing mission
that I think we must abort ♪
♪ He is dangerous ♪
♪ Jesus Christ ♪
♪ Superstar ♪
♪ He is dangerous ♪
[ Chattering ]
♪ Look, Caiaphas
They're right outside our yard ♪
♪ Quick, Caiaphas
Go call the Roman guard ♪
♪ No, wait ♪
♪ We need a more permanent solution
to our problem ♪
♪ What then to do
about Jesus of Nazareth ♪
♪ Miracle wonderman
hero of fools ♪
♪ No riots, no army
no fighting, no slogans ♪
♪ One thing I'll say for him
Jesus is cool ♪
♪ We cannot Leave him
to his own devices ♪
♪ His half-witted fans
will get out of control ♪
- ♪ How can we stop him ♪
- ♪ His glamour increases ♪
- ♪ By leaps every minute ♪
- ♪ He's top of the pole ♪
♪ I see
bad things arising ♪
♪ The crowd crowned him king
which the Romans would ban ♪
♪ I see
blood and destruction ♪
♪ Our elimination
because of one man ♪
♪ Blood and destruction
[ All ]
♪ Because, because, because of one man ♪
♪ Our elimination
because of one man ♪
♪ Because, because
because of one ♪
♪ Cause of one
cause of one man ♪
[ Priest ] ♪ What then to do
about this Jesus mania ♪
[ Annas ] ♪ Oh, how do we deal
with the carpenter-king ♪
[ Priest ] ♪ Where do we start
with a man who is bigger ♪
♪ Than John was when John did
his baptism thing ♪
♪ Fools, you have
no perception ♪
♪ The stakes we are gambling
are frighteningly high ♪
♪ We must crush him
completely ♪
♪ So like John before him
this Jesus must die ♪
♪ For the sake of the nation
[ All ] ♪ Must die, Must die
This Jesus must die ♪
♪ So like John before him
this Jesus must die ♪
♪ Must die, Must die
This Jesus must, Jesus must ♪
♪ Jesus must die ♪♪
♪♪ [ Trumpets ]
♪ Hosanna, Heysanna
Sanna, sanna, ho ♪
♪ Sanna, heysanna
hosanna ♪
♪ Hey, J.C., J.C. ♪
♪ Won't you smile at me ♪
♪ Sanna, hosanna
Hey, superstar ♪
♪ Tell the rabble
to be quiet ♪
♪ We anticipate a riot ♪
♪ This common crowd ♪
♪ Is much too loud ♪
♪ Tell the mob
who sing your song ♪
♪ That they are fools
and they are wrong ♪
♪ They are a curse ♪
♪ They should disperse ♪
♪ Hosanna, heysanna
Sanna, sanna, ho ♪
♪ Sanna, heysanna
hosanna ♪
♪ Hey, J.C., J.C.
You're all right by me ♪
♪ Sanna, hosanna
Hey, superstar ♪
♪ Why waste your breath
moaning at the crowd ♪
♪ Nothing can be done
to stop the shouting ♪
♪ If every tongue
were still ♪
♪ The noise
would still continue ♪
♪ The rocks and stones
themselves ♪
♪ Would start to sing ♪
♪ Hosanna, heysanna
sanna, sanna, ho ♪
♪ Sanna, heysanna
hosanna ♪
♪ Hey, J.C., J.C.
won't you fight for me ♪
♪ Sanna, hosanna
Hey, superstar ♪
♪ Sing me your songs
but not for me alone ♪
Sing out for yourselves...
♪ For you are blessed ♪
♪ There is not one of you
who cannot win the Kingdom ♪
♪ The slow, the suffering ♪
♪ The quick, the dead ♪
♪ Hosanna, heysanna
sanna, sanna, ho ♪
♪ Sanna, heysanna
hosanna ♪
♪ Hey, J.C., J.C.
would you die for me ♪
♪ Sanna, hosanna
Hey, superstar ♪♪
[ Cheering ]
Jesus! Jesus!
♪ Christ, you know I love you
Did you see I waved ♪
♪ I believe in you and God
so tell me that I'm saved ♪
♪ Christ, you know I Love you
Did you see I waved ♪
♪ I believe in you and God
so tell me that I'm saved ♪
♪ Jesus, I am with you
Touch me, Touch me, Jesus ♪
♪ Jesus, I am on your side
Kiss me, Kiss me, Jesus ♪
♪ Christ, what more do you need
to convince you ♪
♪ That you've made it
and you're easily as strong ♪
♪ As the filth from Rome
who rape our country ♪
♪ And who've terrorized
our people for so Long ♪
♪♪ [ Vocalizing ]
♪ Jesus, I am with you
Touch me, Touch me, Jesus ♪
♪ Jesus, I am on your side
Kiss me, Kiss me, Jesus ♪
♪ Christ, you know I Love you
Did you see I waved ♪
♪ I believe in you and God
so tell me that I'm saved ♪
♪ Christ, you know I Love you
Did you see I waved ♪
♪ I believe in you and God
so tell me that I'm saved ♪
♪ Christ, you know I Love you
Did you see I waved ♪
♪ I believe in you and God
so tell me that I'm saved ♪
♪ Christ, you know I Love you
Did you see I waved ♪
♪ I believe in you and God
so tell me that I'm saved ♪
♪ Jesus, I am with you
Touch me, Touch me, Jesus ♪
♪ Jesus, I am on your side
Kiss me, Kiss me, Jesus ♪
- ♪ There must be over 50,000 ♪
- ♪ 50,000 ♪
- ♪ Screamin' love and more for you ♪
- ♪ Love, Love, Love ♪
♪ And every one
of 50,000 ♪
- ♪ Would do whatever ya asked them to ♪
- ♪ Messiah ♪
♪ Keep them yellin'
their devotion ♪
♪ But add a touch
of hate at Rome ♪
♪ You will rise
to greater power ♪
♪ We will win ourselves
a home ♪
- ♪ You'll get the power and the gory ♪
- ♪ You'll get the gory ♪
- ♪ Forever and ever and ever ♪
- ♪ Ever and ever ♪
- ♪ You'll get the power and the gory ♪
- ♪ You'll get the power ♪
- ♪ Forever and ever and ever ♪
- ♪ Ever and ever ♪
- ♪ You'll get the power and the gory, Lord ♪
- ♪ You'll get the power ♪
- ♪ Forever and ever and ever ♪
- ♪ You'll get the gory ♪
♪ You'll get the power
You'll get the gory ♪
- ♪ Hey, hey, hey, hey ♪
- ♪ You'll get the gory ♪
- ♪ You ♪
- ♪ You'll get the power ♪
♪ You'll get the power
You'll get the gory ♪
- ♪ Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey ♪
- ♪ You'll get the power ♪
- ♪ You ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Forever
Amen ♪
♪ A... ha-ah-ah
ah-ah-ah ♪
♪ ...men ♪♪
♪ Neither you, Simon ♪
♪ Nor the 50,000 ♪
♪ Nor the Romans
nor the Jews ♪
♪ Nor Judas
nor the twelve ♪
♪ Nor the priests
nor the scribes ♪
♪ Nor doomed Jerusalem
itself ♪
♪ Understand
what power is ♪
what gory is ♪
♪ Understand at all ♪
♪ Understand
at all ♪
♪ If you knew ♪
♪ All that I knew ♪
♪ My poor Jerusalem ♪
♪ You'd see the truth ♪
♪ But you'd close your eyes ♪
♪ But you'd close
your eyes ♪
♪ While you live ♪
♪ Your troubles are many ♪
♪ Poor Jerusalem ♪
♪ To conquer death ♪
♪ You only have to die ♪
♪ You only have
to die ♪♪
♪ I dreamed
I met a Galilean ♪
♪ A most amazing man ♪
♪ He had that look
you very rarely find ♪
♪ The haunting, hunted kind ♪
♪ I asked him to say
what had happened ♪
♪ How it all began ♪
♪ I asked again
He never said a word ♪
♪ As if he hadn't heard ♪
♪ And next
the room was full ♪
♪ Of wild and angry men ♪
♪ They seemed
to hate this man ♪
♪ They fell on him and then ♪
♪ Disappeared again ♪
♪ Then I saw
thousands of millions ♪
♪ Crying for this man ♪
♪ And then I heard them
mentioning my name ♪
♪ And leaving me
the blame ♪
[ Chorus ]
♪ Pilate ♪♪
[ Bleating ]
♪ Roll on up, Jerusalem
Come on in, Jerusalem ♪
♪ Sunday, here we go again
Live in me, Jerusalem ♪
♪ Here you live, Jerusalem
Here you breathe, Jerusalem ♪
♪ While your temple still survives
you at least are still alive ♪
♪ I got things you won't believe
Name your pleasure, I will sell ♪
♪ I can fix your wildest needs
I got heaven, I got hell ♪
♪ Roll on up for my price is down
Come on in for the best in town ♪
♪ Take your pick of the finest wine
Lay your bets on this bird of mine ♪
♪ What you see
is what you get ♪
♪ No one's been
disappointed yet ♪
♪ Don't be scared
Give me a try ♪
♪ There is nothing
you can't buy ♪
♪ Name your price, I got everything
Hurry, It's all going fast ♪
♪ Borrow cash
on the finest terms ♪
♪ Hurry now
while stocks still last ♪
[ Crowd Chattering ]
♪ Roll on up, Jerusalem
Come on in, Jerusalem ♪
♪ Sunday, here we go again
Live in me, Jerusalem ♪
♪ Here you live, Jerusalem
Here you breathe, Jerusalem ♪
♪ While your temple still survives
you at Least are still alive ♪
♪ I got things you won't believe
Name your pleasure, I will sell ♪♪
[ Screaming ]
[ Woman Screaming ]
♪ My temple
should be ♪
♪ A house of prayer ♪
♪ But you have made it ♪
♪ A den of thieves ♪♪
Get out!
[ Crowd Screaming,
Yelling ]
♪ My time ♪
♪ Is almost through ♪
♪ Little left to do ♪
♪ After all, I've tried
for three years ♪
♪ Seems like 30 ♪
♪ Feels like 30 ♪
♪ See my eyes
I can hardly see ♪
♪ See me stand
I can hardly walk ♪
♪ I believe
you can make me whole ♪
♪ See my tongue
I can hardly talk ♪
♪ See my skin
I'm a mass of blood ♪
♪ See my legs
I can hardly stand ♪
♪ I believe
you can make me well ♪
♪ See my purse
I'm a poor, poor man ♪
[ All ] ♪ Will you touch
Will you mend me, Christ ♪
♪ Won't you touch
Won't you heal me, Christ ♪
♪ Will you kiss
You can cure me, Christ ♪
♪ Won't you kiss
Won't you pay me, Christ ♪
♪ See my eyes
I can hardly see ♪
♪ See me stand
I can hardly walk ♪
♪ I believe
you can make me whole ♪
♪ See my tongue
I can hardly talk ♪
♪ See my skin
I'm a mass of blood ♪
♪ See my Legs
I can hardly stand ♪
♪ I believe
you can make me well ♪
♪ See my purse
I'm a poor, poor man ♪
♪ Will you touch
Will you mend me, Christ ♪
♪ Won't you touch
Will you heal me, Christ ♪
♪ Will you kiss
You can cure me, Christ ♪
♪ Won't you kiss
Won't you pay me, Christ ♪
♪ See my eyes
I can hardly see ♪
♪ See me stand
I can hardly walk ♪
♪ I believe
you can make me whole ♪
♪ See my tongue
I can hardly talk ♪
♪ See my skin
I'm a mass of blood ♪
♪ See my Legs
I can hardly stand ♪
♪ I believe
you can make me well ♪
♪ See my purse
I'm a poor, poor man ♪
♪ Will you touch
Will you mend me, Christ ♪
♪ Won't you touch
Will you heal me, Christ ♪
♪ Will you kiss
You can cure me, Christ ♪
♪ Won't you kiss
Won't you pay me, Christ ♪
♪ See my eyes
I can hardly see ♪
♪ See me stand
I can hardly walk ♪
♪ I believe you can make me whole
See my tongue I can hardly talk ♪
- ♪ See my skin, I'm a mass of blood ♪
- [ Jesus Moaning ]
- There's too many of you!
- ♪ I believe you can make me well ♪
- Don't push me!
- ♪ See my purse, I'm a poor, poor man ♪
- ♪ Will you touch Will you mend me, Christ ♪
- There's too little of me.
- ♪ Will you kiss You can cure me, Christ ♪
- Don't crowd me!
♪ See my eyes
I can hardly see ♪
- Leave me alone!
- ♪ I believe you can make me whole ♪
♪ See my tongue
I can hardly talk ♪♪
Jesus!
Touch me, Jesus!
♪ Close your eyes
Close your eyes ♪
♪ And forget
all about us ♪
♪ Tonight ♪♪
♪ I don't know
how to Love him ♪
♪ What to do
How to move him ♪
♪ I've been changed ♪
♪ Yes, really changed ♪
♪ In these past few days
when I've seen myself ♪
♪ I seem like someone else ♪
♪ I don't know how
to take this ♪
♪ I don't see
why he moves me ♪
♪ He's a man ♪
♪ He's just a man ♪
♪ And I've had
so many men before ♪
♪ In very many ways ♪
♪ He's just one more ♪
♪ Should I bring him down
Should I scream and shout ♪
♪ Should I speak of Love
Let my feelings out ♪
♪ I never thought
I'd come to this ♪
♪ What's it all about ♪
♪ Don't ya think
it's rather funny ♪
♪ I should be
in this position ♪
♪ I'm the one
who's always been ♪
♪ So calm, so cool
No lover's fool ♪
♪ Running every show ♪
♪ He scares me so ♪
♪ I never thought
I'd come to this ♪
♪ What's it all about ♪
♪ Yet if he said
he loved me ♪
♪ I'd be lost
I'd be frightened ♪
♪ I couldn't cope ♪
♪ Just couldn't cope ♪
♪ I'd turn my head
I'd back away ♪
♪ I wouldn't want to know ♪
♪ He scares me so ♪
♪ I want him so ♪
♪ I Love him ♪
♪ So ♪♪
[ Engines Roaring ]
♪ Now if I help you
it matters that you see ♪
♪ These sordid kind of things
are coming hard to me ♪
♪ It's taken me some time
to work out what to do ♪
♪ I weighed the whole thing out
before I came to you ♪
♪ I have no thought at all
about my own reward ♪
♪ I really didn't come here
of my own accord ♪
♪ Just don't say I'm ♪
♪ Damned for all time ♪
♪ I came because I had to
I'm the one who saw ♪
♪ Jesus can't control it
like he did before ♪
♪ Furthermore, I know
that Jesus thinks so too ♪
♪ Jesus wouldn't mind
that I was here with you ♪
♪ I have no thought at all
about my own reward ♪
♪ I really didn't come here
of my own accord ♪
♪ Just don't say I'm ♪
♪ Damned for all time ♪
♪ Annas, you're a friend
a wordily man and wise ♪
♪ Caiaphas, my friend
I know you sympathize ♪
♪ Why are we the prophets
Why are we the ones ♪
♪ We see the sad solution
Know what must be done ♪
♪ I have no thought at all
about my own reward ♪
♪ I really didn't come here
of my own accord ♪
♪ Just don't say I'm ♪
♪ Damned ♪
♪ For all time ♪
♪ Cut the protesting
Forget the excuses ♪
♪ We want information
Get up off the floor ♪
♪ We have the papers
we need to arrest him ♪
♪ You know his movements
We know the law ♪
♪ Your help in this matter
won't go unrewarded ♪
♪ We'll pay you in sliver
cash on the nail ♪
♪ We just need to know
where the soldiers can find him ♪
- ♪ With no crowd 'round him ♪
- ♪ Then we can't fall ♪
♪ I don't want
your blood money ♪
♪ Oh, that doesn't matter
Our expenses are good ♪
♪ I don't need
your blood money ♪
♪ But you might as well take it
We think that you should ♪
♪ Think of the things
you can do with that money ♪
♪ Choose any charity
Give to the poor ♪
♪ We've noted your motives
We've noted your feelings ♪
♪ This isn't blood money
It's a... ♪
- A fee.
- ♪ A fee, nothing more ♪♪
♪ On Thursday night ♪
♪ You'll find him
where you want him ♪
♪ Far from the crowds ♪
♪ In the Garden ♪
♪ Of Gethsemane ♪♪
[ Chorus ]
♪ So long, Judas ♪
♪ So Long, Judas ♪♪
[ Jets Roaring ]
♪ Look at all my trials
and tribulations ♪
♪ Sinking in a gentle pool
of wine ♪
♪ Don't disturb me now ♪
♪ I can see the answers ♪
♪ Till this evening
is this morning ♪
♪ Life is fine ♪
♪ Always hoped that
I'd be an apostle ♪
♪ Knew that I would
make it if I tried ♪
♪ Then when we retire ♪
♪ We can write
the Gospels ♪
♪ So they'll still talk about us
when we've died ♪
♪ The end ♪
♪ Is just a little harder ♪
♪ When brought about ♪
♪ By friends ♪
♪ For all you care ♪
♪ This wine
could be my blood ♪
♪ For all you care ♪
♪ This bread ♪
♪ Could be my body ♪
The end.
♪ This is my blood
you drink ♪
♪ This is my body you eat ♪
♪ If you would, remember me ♪
♪ When you eat and drink ♪♪
♪ I must be mad
thinking I'll be remembered ♪
♪ Yes, I must be
out of my head ♪
♪ Look at your blank faces
My name will mean nothing ♪
♪ Ten minutes
after I'm dead ♪
♪ One of you denies me
One of you betrays me ♪
[ Apostles Shouting ]
No! No!
[ Indistinct Shouting ]
♪ Peter will deny me ♪
- No, not me!
- ♪ In just a few hours ♪
♪ Three times will deny me
And that's not all I see ♪
♪ One of you here dining
One of my 12 chosen ♪
♪ Will leave to betray me ♪
♪ Cut out the dramatics
You know very well who ♪
- ♪ Why don't you go do it? ♪
- ♪ You want me to do it? ♪
- ♪ Hurry, they are waiting ♪
- ♪ If you knew why I do it ♪
♪ I don't care
why you do it ♪
♪ To think I admired you
Well, now I despise you ♪
- ♪ You liar, you Judas ♪
- ♪ You wanted me to do it ♪
♪ What if I just stayed here and
ruined your ambition Christ, you deserve it ♪
♪ Hurry, you fool
Hurry and go ♪
♪ Save me your speeches
I don't want to know ♪
♪ Go, Go ♪♪
♪ Look at all my trials
and tribulations ♪
♪ Sinking in a gentle pool
of wine ♪
♪ What's that in the bread
It's gone to my head
♪ Till this morning
is this evening ♪
♪ Life is fine ♪
♪ Always hoped that
I'd be an apostle ♪
♪ Knew that I would make it
if I tried ♪
♪ Then when we retire
we can write the Gospels ♪
♪ So they'll all talk about us
when we've died ♪♪
♪ You sad
pathetic man ♪
♪ See where you
brought us to ♪
♪ Our ideals die around us
and all because of you ♪
♪ But the saddest cut of all
Someone had to turn you in ♪
♪ Like a common criminal
Like a wounded animal ♪
♪ A jaded mandarin
A jaded mandarin ♪
♪ Like a jaded, faded
faded, jaded, jaded mandarin ♪
♪ Get out
They're waiting ♪
♪ Get out ♪
♪ They're waiting
Oh, they're waiting for you ♪
♪ Every time I Look at you
I don't understand ♪
♪ Why you let the things you did
get so out of hand ♪
♪ You'd have managed better
if you'd had it planned ♪
♪ A-a-a-ah ♪♪
[ Bleating ]
♪ Always hoped that
I'd be an apostle ♪
♪ Knew that I would make it
if I tried ♪
♪ If I tried ♪
♪ Then when we retire
we can write the Gospels ♪
♪ So they'll still
talk about us ♪
♪ When we've died ♪♪
♪ Will no one stay awake
with me ♪
♪ Peter, John, James ♪
♪ Will none of you wait
with me ♪
♪ Peter ♪
♪ John ♪
♪ James ♪
♪ I only want to say ♪
♪ If there is a way ♪
♪ Take this cup
away from me ♪
♪ For I don't want
to taste its poison ♪
♪ Feel it burn me ♪
♪ I have changed ♪
♪ I'm not as sure
as when we started ♪
♪ Then, I was inspired ♪
♪ Now ♪
♪ I'm sad and tired ♪
♪ Listen ♪
♪ Surely I've exceeded
expectations ♪
♪ Tried for three years ♪
♪ Seems like 30 ♪
♪ Could You ask as much ♪
♪ From any other man ♪
♪ But if I die ♪
♪ See the saga through ♪
♪ And do the things
You ask of me ♪
♪ Let them hate me
hit me, hurt me ♪
♪ Nail me
to their tree ♪
♪ I'd want to know
I'd want to know, my God ♪
♪ I'd want to see
I'd want to see, my God ♪
♪ Why I ♪
♪ Should die ♪
♪ Would I be more noticed
than I ever was before ♪
♪ Would the things
I've said and done ♪
♪ Matter any more ♪
♪ I'd have to know
I'd have to know, my Lord ♪
♪ I'd have to see
I'd have to see, my Lord ♪
♪ If I die
what will be my reward ♪
♪ Have to know
I'd have to know, my Lord ♪
♪ Why ♪
♪ Why should I die ♪
♪ Oh, why should I die ♪
♪ Can You show me now ♪
♪ That I would not be
killed in vain ♪
♪ Show me just a little ♪
♪ Of Your omnipresent brain ♪
♪ Show me there's a reason
for Your wanting me to die ♪
♪ You're far too keen
on where and how ♪
♪ But not so hot on why ♪
♪ All right ♪
♪ I'll die ♪
♪ Oh, Oh
Just watch me die ♪
♪ See how ♪
♪ See how I'll die ♪
♪ Oh-h-h ♪
♪ Just watch me die ♪
♪ Then ♪
♪ I was inspired ♪
♪ Now ♪
I'm sad and tired.
♪ After all ♪
I've tried for three years.
Seems like 90.
♪ Why then am I scared
to finish ♪
♪ What I started ♪
♪ What You started ♪
I didn't start it.
♪ God ♪
♪ Thy will is hard ♪
♪ But You hold every card ♪
♪ I will drink ♪
♪ Your cup of poison ♪
♪ Nail me to Your cross ♪
♪ And break me ♪
♪ Bleed me ♪
♪ Beat me, Kill me ♪
♪ Take me now ♪
♪ Before I change my mind ♪♪
Judas,
must you betray me...
♪ With a kiss ♪
♪ What's the buzz
Tell me what's happening ♪
Tell me what's happenin' ♪
♪ What's happenin' ♪
♪ What's the buzz
Tell me what's a-happenin' ♪
♪ Hang on, Lord
We're gonna fight for you ♪
- ♪ Hang on, Lord We're gonna fight for you ♪
- ♪ Hang on, Lord ♪
♪ Hang on, Lord
We're gonna fight for you ♪
- ♪ Hang on, Lord We're gonna fight for you ♪
- ♪ We're gonna fight for you ♪
♪ Put away your sword ♪
♪ Don't you know
that it's all over ♪
♪ It was nice, but ♪
♪ Now it's gone ♪
♪ Why are you obsessed
with fighting ♪
♪ Stick to fishing
from now on ♪♪
[ Indistinct Chatter ]
[ Man Laughing ]
♪ Tell me, Christ
how you feel tonight ♪
♪ Do you plan
to put up a fight ♪
♪ Do you feel that
you've had the breaks ♪
♪ What would you say
were your big mistakes ♪
♪ Do you think that
you may retire ♪
♪ Did you think
you would get much higher ♪
♪ How do you view
your coming trial ♪
♪ Have your men proved
it's all worthwhile ♪
♪ Come with us
to see Caiaphas ♪
♪ You'll just Love
the high priest's house ♪
seeing Caiaphas ♪
♪ You'll just die
in the high priest's house ♪
♪ Come on, God
This is not like you ♪
♪ Let us know
what you're gonna do ♪
♪ You know what
your supporters feel ♪
♪ You'll escape
in the final reel ♪
♪ Tell me, Christ
how you feel tonight ♪
♪ Do you plan
to put up a fight ♪
♪ Do you feel that
you had the breaks ♪
♪ What would you say
were your big mistakes ♪
♪ Come with us
to see Caiaphas ♪
♪ You'll just Love
the high priest's house ♪
seeing Caiaphas ♪
♪ You'll just die
in the high priest's house ♪
♪ Now we have him
Now we've got him ♪
♪ Now we have him now
We have got him now ♪
♪ Jesus, you must realize ♪
♪ The serious charges
facing you ♪
♪ You say you're the Son of God
in all your handouts Well, is it true ♪
♪ That's what you say
You say that I am ♪
♪ There you have it, gentlemen
What more evidence do we need ♪
♪ Judas, thank you
for the victim ♪
♪ Stay a while
You'll see it bleed ♪
♪ Now we have him
Now we've got him ♪
♪ Take him to Pilate
Take him to Pilate ♪
Take him to Pilate ♪♪
♪ I think I've
seen you somewhere ♪
I remember.
♪ You were with that man
they took away ♪
♪ I recognize
your face ♪
♪ You've got
the wrong man, lady ♪
♪ I don't know him ♪
♪ And I wasn't where
he was tonight ♪
♪ Never near the place ♪
♪ That's strange for I am sure
I saw you with him ♪
♪ You were right by his side
and yet you denied ♪
♪ I tell you
I was never, ever with him ♪
But I saw you too.
He looked just like you.
I don't know him!
♪ Peter, don't you know
what you have said ♪
♪ You've gone
and cut him dead ♪
♪ I had to do it
Don't you see ♪
♪ Or else
they'd go for me ♪
♪ It's what he told us
you would do ♪
♪ I wonder
how he knew ♪♪
[ Crowd Shouting ]
[ Shouting Continues ]
- Come on. Come on.
- There he is, see? Hurry. Come on.
♪ Who is ♪
♪ This broken man ♪
♪ Cluttering up ♪
♪ My hallway ♪
♪ Who is this unfortunate ♪
♪ Someone Christ
King of the Jews ♪
Oh. So this is
Jesus Christ.
♪ I am really
quite surprised ♪
You Look so small.
Not a king at all.
♪ We all know
that you are news ♪
But are you King?
♪ King of the Jews ♪
Your words, not mine.
♪ What do ♪
♪ You mean by that ♪
♪ That is not an answer ♪
♪ You're deep ♪
♪ In trouble, friend ♪
♪ Someone Christ
King of the Jews ♪
♪ How can someone
in your state ♪
♪ Be so cool
about his fate ♪
An amazing thing,
this silent king.
♪ Since you come
from Galilee ♪
♪ Then you need not
come to me ♪
You're Herod's race.
[ Chuckles ]
You're Herod's case.
♪ Hey, hosanna
Heysanna ♪
♪ Sanna
sanna ho ♪
♪ Sanna, heysanna, ho
and how ♪
♪ Hey, J.C., J.C. ♪
♪ Please explain to me ♪
♪ You had everything
Where is it now ♪♪
Jesus, I am overjoyed...
♪ To meet you face to face ♪
You've been getting
quite a name...
♪ All around the place ♪
♪ Healing cripples ♪
- Ooh.
- ♪ Raising from the dead ♪
[ All Gasping ]
♪ Now I understand
you're God ♪
[ Gasping ]
Hmm? Huh?
Mmm.
♪ At Least that's
what you've said ♪
♪ So ♪
♪ You are the Christ
You're the great Jesus Christ ♪
♪ Prove to me
that you're divine ♪
♪ Change my water
into wine ♪
♪ That's all you need do
Then I'll know it's all true ♪
♪ Come on
King of the Jews ♪
♪ Jesus, you just won't believe the hit
you've made around here ♪
♪ You are all we talk about
You're the wonder of the year ♪
♪ Oh, what a pity
if it's all a lie ♪
♪ Still I'm sure that you can rock
the cynics if you try ♪
♪ So if you are the Christ
Yes, the great Jesus Christ ♪
♪ Prove to me that
you're no fool ♪
♪ Walk across
my swimming pool ♪
- ♪ If you do that for me ♪
- Whoo!
- ♪ Then I'll Let you go free ♪
♪ Come on
King of the Jews ♪
♪ I only ask what I'd ask
any superstar ♪
♪ What is it that you have got
that puts you where you are ♪
♪ Oh-ho-ho
I am waiting ♪
♪ Yes, I'm a captive fan ♪
♪ I'm dying to be shown that
you are not just any man ♪
♪ So if you are the Christ
Yes, the great Jesus Christ ♪
♪ Feed my household
with this bread ♪
♪ You can do it
on your head ♪
Uh, or has something gone wrong?
Jesus, why do you take so Long?
Aw, come on,
King of the Jews!
♪ Hey, aren't you ♪
♪ Scared of me, Christ ♪
♪ Mister wonderful Christ ♪
Aaah!
You're a joke!
You're not the Lord.
You're nothing but a fraud.
♪ Take him away
He's got nothing to say ♪♪
Get out, you King of the...
Get out, King of the... Oh!
Get out, you King of the Jews!
Get out of here!
You... You...
Get out of here, you!
Get out of my life!
♪ I've been living
to see you ♪
♪ Dying to see you
but it shouldn't be like this ♪
♪ This was unexpected
What do I do now ♪
♪ Could we start again
please ♪
♪ I've been very hopeful
so far ♪
♪ Now for the first time ♪
♪ I think we're going wrong ♪
♪ Hurry up and tell me
This is just a dream ♪
♪ Or could we start again
please ♪
♪ I think you've made
your point now ♪
♪ You've even gone a bit too far to get
the message home ♪
♪ Before it gets
too frightening ♪
♪ We ought to call
a halt ♪
♪ So could we start again
please ♪
♪ I've been living
to see you ♪
♪ Dying to see you
but it shouldn't be like this ♪
♪ This was unexpected
What do I do now ♪
♪ Could we start again
please ♪
♪ I think you've made
your point now ♪
♪ You've even gone a bit too far to get
the message home ♪
♪ Before it gets
too frightening ♪
♪ We ought to call a halt
So could we start again please ♪
♪ Could we start again
please ♪
♪ Could we start again ♪
♪ Could we start again ♪♪
♪ My God
I saw him ♪
♪ He Looked three-quarters dead and
he was so bad I had to turn my head ♪
♪ You beat him so hard
that he was bent and lame ♪
♪ And I know who
everybody's gonna blame ♪
♪ I don't believe he knows
I acted for our good ♪
♪ I'd save him all this suffering
if I could ♪
♪ Don't believe
Our good ♪
♪ And I'd save him
if I could ♪
♪ Cut the confessions
Forget the excuses ♪
♪ I don't understand why
you're flied with remorse ♪
♪ All that you've said has
come true with a vengeance ♪
♪ The mob turned against him
You backed the right horse ♪
♪ What you have done will be
the saving of everyone ♪
♪ You'll be remembered
forever for this ♪
♪ And not only that
You've been paid for your efforts ♪
♪ Pretty good wages
for one little kiss ♪
♪ Christ, I know
you can't hear me ♪
♪ But I only did
what you wanted me to ♪
♪ Christ, I'd sell out
the nation ♪
♪ For I have been saddled
with the murder of you ♪
♪ I have been spattered
with innocent blood ♪
♪ I shall be dragged through
the slime and the mud ♪
♪ I have been spattered
with innocent blood ♪
♪ I shall be dragged through the slime
and the slime and the ♪
♪ Slime and the mud ♪♪
♪ I ♪
♪ Don't know how
to Love him ♪
♪ I don't know
why he moves me ♪
♪ He's a man ♪
♪ He's just a man ♪
♪ He is not a king ♪
♪ He's just the same ♪
♪ As anyone I know ♪
♪ He scares me so ♪
♪ When he's cold and dead ♪
♪ Will he Let me be
Does he Love ♪
♪ Does he Love me too ♪
♪ Does he care for me ♪♪
My mind is...
It's in darkness.
God. God, I'm sick!
I've been used!
And You knew all the time!
God... God, I will never know
why You chose me...
for Your crime!
For Your bloody crime!
You have murdered me!
Mur... Murdered me!
Murdered me! Murdered me!
Murdered me! Murdered...!
♪ So Long, Judas ♪
♪ And so, the king
is once again my guest ♪
♪ And why is this ♪
♪ Was Herod unimpressed ♪
[ Caiaphas ]
♪ We turn to Rome ♪
♪ To sentence Nazareth ♪
♪ We have no Law ♪
♪ To put a man to death ♪
♪ We need him crucified ♪
♪ It's all
you have to do ♪
♪ We need him crucified
It's all you have to do ♪
♪ Talk to me, Jesus Christ
You have been brought here ♪
Manacled, beaten,
by your own people.
Do you have the first idea
why you deserve it?
♪ Listen, King of the Jews
Where is your kingdom ♪
♪ Look at me
Am I a Jew ♪
I have no kingdom.
In this world, I'm through.
- ♪ Talk to me, Jesus Christ ♪
- There may be a kingdom...
for me somewhere.
If you only knew.
- Then you are a king.
- ♪ It's you that say I am ♪
♪ I Look for truth
and find that I get damned ♪
♪ And what is truth
Is truth unchanging Law ♪
♪ We both have truths
Are mine the same as yours ♪
[ Crowd ]
Crucify him! Crucify him!
What do you mean?
You'd crucify your king?
[ Crowd ]
♪ We have no king but Caesar ♪
He's done no wrong.
No, not the slightest thing.
♪ We have no king but Caesar
Crucify him ♪
Well, this is new.
Respect for Caesar!
Until now, this has been
noticeably lacking.
Who is this Jesus?
Why is he different?
You Jews produce messiahs
by the sackful.
♪ We need him crucified
It's all you have to do ♪
♪ Talk to me
Jesus Christ ♪
♪ Look at
your Jesus Christ ♪
♪ I'll agree
he's mad ♪
♪ Ought to be locked up ♪
♪ But that is not a reason
to destroy him ♪
♪ He's a sad little man
not a king or god ♪
♪ Not a thief
I need a crime ♪
[ Shouting ]
Crucify him! Crucify him!
Crucify him!
♪ Behold the man
Behold your shattered king ♪
♪ We have no king
but Caesar ♪
♪ You hypocrites
You hate us more than him ♪
♪ We have no king but Caesar
Crucify him ♪
♪ I see no reason
I find no evil ♪
♪ This man is harmless
so why does he upset you ♪
♪ He's just misguided
Thinks he's important ♪
But to keep you vultures happy,
I shall flog him!
Crucify him! Crucify him!
Crucify him!
Crucify!
Crucify! Crucify!
Crucify him! Crucify him!
Crucify! Crucify! Crucify!
Crucify! Crucify him!
Crucify him!
Crucify! Crucify!
- [ Pilate ] One,
- [ Mary Screaming ]
Two,
three, four,
five, six,
seven,
eight, nine,
ten,
eleven,
twelve,
thirteen,
fourteen,
fifteen,
sixteen,
seventeen,
eighteen,
nineteen,
twenty,
twenty-one,
twenty-two,
twenty-three,
twenty-four,
twenty-five,
twenty-six,
twenty-seven,
twenty-eight,
twenty-nine,
thirty,
thirty-one,
thirty-two,
thirty-three,
thirty-four,
thirty-five,
thirty-six,
thirty-seven,
thirty-eight,
thirty-nine!
[ Pilate ]
♪ Where are you from Jesus ♪
♪ What do you want
Jesus ♪
♪ Tell me ♪
♪ You've got to be careful ♪
♪ You could be dead soon ♪
♪ Could well be ♪
♪ Why do you not speak ♪
♪ When I hold your life
in my hands ♪
♪ How can you
stay quiet ♪
♪ I don't believe
you understand ♪
♪ You have nothing
in your hands ♪
Any power you have...
comes to you
from far beyond.
Everything is fixed,
and you can't change it.
You're a fool,
Jesus Christ!
- ♪ How can I help you ♪
- [ Crowd ] ♪ Pilate, crucify him ♪
♪ Crucify
Remember Caesar ♪
♪ You have a duty
to keep the peace ♪
♪ So crucify him ♪
♪ Remember Caesar
You'll be demoted ♪
♪ You'll be deported
Crucify him ♪
♪ Remember Caesar
You have a duty ♪
♪ To keep the peace
so crucify him ♪
♪ Remember Caesar
You'll be demoted ♪
♪ You'll be deported
Crucify him ♪
♪ Remember Caesar
You have a duty ♪
♪ To keep the peace
so crucify him ♪
♪ Remember Caesar
You'll be demoted ♪
♪ You'll be deported
Crucify him ♪
♪ Don't Let me stop ♪
♪ Your great
self-destruction ♪
♪ Die if you want to ♪
♪ You misguided martyr ♪
♪ I wash my hands ♪
♪ Of your demolition ♪
♪ Die if you want to ♪
♪ You innocent puppet ♪♪
[ Crowd Cheering,
Shouting ]
♪♪ [ “Superstar” Instrumental ]
♪ Mmm, every time I Look at you
I don't understand ♪
♪ Why you Let the things you did
get so out of hand ♪
♪ You'd have managed better
if you'd had it planned ♪
♪ Now why'd you choose such a backward
time and such a strange land ♪
♪ If you'd come today you could
have reached the whole nation ♪
♪ Israel in 4 B.C. had
no mass communication ♪
- ♪ Don't you get me wrong ♪
- ♪ Don't you get me wrong now ♪
- ♪ Don't you get me wrong now Only wanna know ♪
- ♪ Don't you get me wrong ♪
- ♪ Only wanna know ♪
- ♪ Only wanna know now ♪
- ♪ Only wanna know, Only wanna know ♪
- ♪ Only wanna know ♪
♪ Oh-Ohh
I only wanna know ♪
♪ Jesus Christ
Jesus Christ ♪
♪ Who are you
What have you sacrificed ♪
♪ Jesus Christ
Jesus Christ ♪
♪ Who are you
What have you sacrificed ♪
♪ Jesus Christ Superstar ♪
♪ Do you think you're
what they say you are ♪
♪ Jesus Christ Superstar ♪
♪ Do you think you're
what they say you are ♪
♪ Tell me ♪
♪ What you think about
your friends at the top ♪
♪ Now who'd you think besides yourself
was the pick of the crop ♪
♪ Buddha, was he where it's at
Is he where you are ♪
♪ Could Mohammed move a mountain
or was that just P.R. ♪
♪ Did you mean to die like that
Was that a mistake or ♪
♪ Did you know your messy death
would be a record breaker ♪
- ♪ Don't you get me wrong Don't you get me wrong ♪
- ♪ Don't you get me wrong ♪
- ♪ Don't you get me wrong now ♪
- ♪ Don't you get me wrong Don't you get me wrong ♪
♪ Only wanna know Only wanna know now ♪
- ♪ Only wanna know ♪
- ♪ Only wanna know, Only wanna know ♪
- ♪ Only wanna know now ♪
- ♪ I only wanna know ♪
♪ Jesus Christ
Jesus Christ ♪
♪ Who are you
What have you sacrificed ♪
♪ Jesus Christ
Jesus Christ ♪
♪ Who are you
What have you sacrificed ♪
- ♪ Jesus Christ Superstar ♪
- ♪ Jesus ♪
- ♪ I only wanna know ♪
- ♪ Do you think you're what they say you are ♪
- ♪ Tell me, tell me, tell me ♪
- ♪ Jesus Christ Superstar ♪
♪ Tell me
Don't you get me wrong ♪
♪ I only wanna know ♪
- ♪ Jesus Christ, Jesus Christ ♪
- ♪ Jesus ♪
♪ I only wanna know ♪
- ♪ Tell me, Tell me, Tell me ♪
- ♪ Tell me, Tell me ♪
♪ Tell me
Don't you get me wrong ♪
♪ I only wanna know
Come on ♪
- ♪ Jesus ♪
- ♪ Only wanna know ♪
- ♪ Jesus, only wanna know ♪
- ♪ I only wanna know ♪
- ♪ Tell me, Tell me, Tell me, Tell me ♪
- ♪ Jesus Christ Superstar ♪
♪ Don't you get me wrong
I only wanna know ♪
- ♪ Come on, Jesus ♪
- ♪ Jesus Christ ♪
♪ Jesus ♪
♪ I only wanna know
Tell me ♪
- ♪ Tell me, Tell me, Tell me ♪
- ♪ Tell me ♪♪
[ Laughter ]
[ Laughter Continues ]
Father, forgive them.
They don't know
what they're doing.
My God. My God,
why have You forgotten me?
Father,
into Your hands...
I commend...
my spirit.