♪ A little less conversation
A little more action, please
♪ All this aggravation
ain't satisfactioning me
♪ A little more bite
and a little less bark
♪ A little less fight
and a little more spark
♪ Close your mouth and open up
your heart and, baby, satisfy me ♪
Ladies and gentlemen,
please welcome the man
who knows what you're going
to do before you do it.
The amazing Frank Cadillac!
Here's to world peace.
Good evening. Welcome to
beautiful downtown Las Vegas.
How many people are here from
the Orient? Raise your hands.
You, sir.
Where are you from?
No, wait! Wait.
Don't tell me.
I'm sensing you
must have soul.
You're a Seoul man.
Why don't you share with
everyone where you're from?
Korea.
How about that, folks?
And may I assume that this charming
young lady is your daughter?
She's my wife!
Well, of course she is!
And what happens in
Vegas stays in Vegas.
What's your name?
Yong Kyunge.
Would you be kind enough to
join me up on stage, please?
Are you serious
about this guy? This a joke?
Want me to round up some mimes
and clowns while we're at it?
Yong Kyunge,
what if I told you
that that pretty necklace you're
wearing has a broken catch,
and on my count of three,
will fall into your drink?
Wouldn't that be something?
Wouldn't that just blow your mind?
Yeah.
Yes!
Wouldn't it blow
all your minds?
Three, two, one, now.
Did somebody say "spooky"?
Wait a minute. Look at your glass.
Where'd it go?
Yong Kyunge, why don't you
look inside my pocket?
Reach in. Dig deep.
Let's have a big hand
for Yong Kyunge.
That's magic, folks, and
that's why I'm here.
You've probably seen
a lot of those shows.
Mentalists. Magicians.
Illusionists.
You'd be shocked to
know that sometimes,
not often, but sometimes,
it's the real deal.
Masquerading as an act.
Hiding behind a few $50 tricks.
Hiding in plain sight.
Because if the magician
doesn't do that,
the alternative is impossible
for others to live with.
Anyway, Wednesday night at the
Back Page doesn't pay very well,
so I gamble.
But I don't play against other people.
Only against the house.
So, no mega-jackpots,
no long shots.
The idea is to go unnoticed.
That way, I can
keep coming back.
I'm not a god.
I can't see everyone's future.
Only my own.
And only within two minutes.
Except for when I saw her.
But we'll come back to that.
There's no pattern to this guy.
He's all over the map.
Well, he's not counting.
Not off the top of a five-deck shoe.
Wait a minute.
Isn't that that two-bit magic
act over at the Back Page?
What's his name?
Cadillac.
Yeah, that's Frank Cadillac.
Is he pulling tricks on us?
Is that legal?
You can't trick the deck.
I'm telling you, that little
prick knows what's coming.
If he's running that good a system,
why is he not betting more?
That's going to be
my second question.
Look at that.
He's looking right at us.
It's like he can hear us.
What table was that?
27.
This is Roybal. Give me two men
on table 27. I'm coming right down.
Place your bets,
please.
Here's the thing
about the future.
Every time you look at it,
it changes because
you looked at it.
Hi.
And that changes everything else.
$9,070.
Empty the drawer. Move!
Drop the gun! Now!
$9,070.
Drop the gun! Step back!
It's his gun. He was going
to shoot two people!
Step back.
We'll settle this right now.
What's he doing?
Secure the doors, elevators, escalators,
every way out of this damn place! Now!
Freeman, seal off the blackjack
tables. Sullivan, link up with Roybal.
We're on the floor.
On the floor right now.
Bring up the other cameras.
That way. This way.
He's right next to you.
$10 slots, aisle 14.
There he is! Behind you!
Your left! Turn around!
He's right between you!
He's in the men's room near the
gift shop. Gift shop! Gift shop!
Davis, where the hell is he?
Black T-shirt, straw hat!
Heading towards the entrance!
Come on, let's go.
Call Vegas P.D.
Just stole a silver Charger,
tag 585G4S.
Drop the gun!
Step back.
He rose to the top of our gambling
fraud wish list about two months ago.
What he does has nothing to do with luck.
It's definable ability.
Look at him. He knows exactly
what to do and not be caught.
Can you explain that to me?
No, I can't explain it, Callie,
nor do I have the time.
The Russian Federation has a
10-kiloton nuclear munition
unaccounted for.
I understand that.
I'm not sure you do. We need every
agent available beating the street.
That bomb was stolen five weeks ago.
We've just been informed of it now.
Which means it could be parked
under this truck for all we know.
I need
actionable intelligence,
not paranormals
and bullshit magicians.
With all due respect, sir,
this bullshit magician's shown a
pattern of advanced awareness
that is statistically
impossible.
You let me bring him in
and you'll get what you want.
Five days, Callie. That's it.
Get me the head
of casino security.
You Roybal?
It's Roybal.
Whatever.
Who are you?
Cavanaugh. Take a walk.
Hey, Roybal, this isn't a
pissing contest. Come on.
What'd you do? You got a new car?
Stole it.
Look at this.
Twenty minutes
to walk 20 steps.
Well, that's what you get
from two packs a day.
Oh, hey.
I got you two sandwiches.
Two sandwiches?
That's 20 grand.
Take it. I love you.
Oh, jeez.
How can I repay you?
Must be a bitch
to park this thing.
Chief Roybal.
Special Agent Ferris.
I'm sure Agent Cavanaugh
has explained to you
that everything you say
is admissible in court
and anything you knowingly
admit can be used against you.
Do we understand each other?
Sure.
Tell me about Cris Johnson.
I don't know who that is.
How about Frank Cadillac?
You chased him
out of your casino tonight.
He stole a car from valet parking.
Yeah, I know Cadillac.
I thought
he was cheating us at cards.
Next thing I know, he's tackling
some guy and waving a gun.
The gun wasn't his.
The man he tackled is wanted for
two casino killings in Reno.
He's in custody now.
Come on,
I want to show you something.
You remember this?
Oh, yeah, of course I do.
We were saying he's looking right at us.
How'd you get this?
Think carefully.
What were you talking about
right when he looked up?
We were saying, if he has a
system, why isn't he betting more?
You sure you weren't doing
or saying anything else?
I was going down to pick him up,
I was reaching for my radio...
And right then? That's when he
looked up? Be very specific.
That's what I said.
He looked up, really.
So he doesn't
have to be there to do it.
Once you enter his consciousness,
he can pick it up.
Is that to work his system?
Thank you. We're finished.
Done some good here, Mr. Roybal, but
none of it is up for discussion.
Now, as far as you're concerned,
Cris Johnson never existed.
That's going to be difficult considering
100 cameras saw him at the casino.
Not to worry. Those tapes
have been destroyed.
Hey. Is she single?
Cris, you can't keep stealing
cars and having people chase you.
That's not a life.
But you got to forget this girl
that you keep seeing in your head.
I'm not going anywhere
until I meet her.
Well, suppose
she don't show up?
She already did,
at the diner. 8:09.
Well, you got a couple hours.
How about a game of pool?
All right, Irv.
We'll shoot some pool.
We timed every hand
of blackjack.
The longest was 89 seconds, when
Johnson pulled a six-card 21.
So we know he can see at least
a minute and a half ahead.
I had our techs run a radio
frequency spectrum analysis.
Came up dry, so he's not receiving
any form of electronic help.
At one point, there was
a two-minute, 16-second delay.
He never bet,
just got up and walked away.
Well, maybe 2:16's too long.
He can't see that far.
Narrows our window
a little bit, anyway.
Got him. Vegas P.D. got a LoJack
hit on the stolen vehicle.
Okay.
Listen, about that girl.
When you looked at the clock,
did you happen to see a calendar?
Because it could be 10 years
from now she gets hungry.
It's got to be soon.
I've never seen further ahead
than two minutes.
Except for her.
Now, what do you think
the reason is for that?
I don't know.
Maybe she doesn't scare easy.
Maybe she's the one.
Well, when you get like this
there's no talking to you.
She's almost here.
What happened to the diner?
Somebody else, a cop.
A cop? Well, then, you got to go.
Hold on. I want to see how much
she knows. What she wants from me.
Cris Johnson. Still here, huh?
Where else would I be?
Special Agent Ferris.
Next time, steal a car
without LoJack.
Can we speak privately?
It's okay, Irv.
Go ahead. Thanks.
I'm sure you know
why I'm here.
Because you're the man who knows what
I'm going to do before I do it, right?
Oh, the show, right. Right!
I saw you there.
Wonderful.
You like magic tricks.
Yeah, yeah, I do like your
magic tricks, clairvoyance...
Whatever you're calling it.
Let's talk
about something hard.
A stolen nuclear munition is being
smuggled into the United States,
or may, in fact,
already be here.
I want you to look ahead and tell
me where it's going to be deployed.
I think you've got the wrong guy.
It's a magic act.
You going to stick
with that story?
Because millions of lives
are at risk
and you could, maybe,
prevent a major catastrophe.
On a practical note, we're standing
in front of a stolen vehicle
and you are wanted for assault
involving a weapon at the casino.
All right, that was an accident.
He had a gun.
He was going to shoot two people.
Yeah?
How'd you know that?
No good deed goes unpunished,
does it?
I can fix your legal problems,
buddy, but you've got to step up.
Otherwise, your next magic show is
going to be at Folsom State Prison.
It's ironic, but people
like you who try to help
have been torturing me, in the full sense
of the word, since I was three years old.
What did they call it?
Oh, yeah.
Observed play therapy.
Featuring the marathon,
36-hour,
can-you-guess-
the-next-flash-card game.
So, please, leave me alone
and let me live some semblance
of a normal life.
I'd love
to indulge your feelings,
but I am dealing with a slightly
larger picture right now.
Now, you can exercise your
responsibility to help your fellow man
or I will exercise
that responsibility for you.
You're right. I got to go.
He's gone, right?
I missed him by seconds,
didn't I?
Excuse me, honey,
can you get off my car?
Yeah, thank you. Jeez.
Mr. Roybal?
It's Roybal.
Can I help you, man?
I have a few questions
if this is a good time.
Gaming Commission?
It's after hours.
You guys should be at a
strip club, right? Come on.
What can you tell us
about Cris Johnson?
I don't know
who you're talking about.
Let me rephrase the question.
It's destiny.
Here you go, hon.
Thanks.
Excuse me.
Hello.
I noticed you were alone, too.
Do you mind if I join you?
Actually, I do.
Sorry to bother you, but I have
a question about the coffee.
The bean they use...
Isn't that something you should
probably ask your waitress?
Yes, it is.
Excuse me,
do you have a light?
I don't smoke.
Here you go, hon.
Thanks.
Please.
Don't.
Hey, Liz.
Did you follow me here,
Kendall?
No! No, I just thought
we could talk.
You know, we got really
nothing to talk about.
And I told you that
three weeks ago.
Liz, come on, all right? I had an
off day. Just give me another shot.
It's not gonna happen.
Okay? So maybe you should just go.
Do you know
how hard it was to find you?
I was at your apartment.
I tried the Starbucks on Lexington.
I was at the dry cleaner.
All I am asking for
is a few minutes of your time
so that we can work things out.
Okay, Jesus, you are stalking me now.
Don't!
Don't say that, please. That's a
terrible thing to say to somebody.
Let go of me, Kendall.
Look, I just... I thought we could
talk, maybe we could take a drive.
And now you are ruining it.
You're hurting me.
Kendall, I think you're having
another off day.
Who the hell are you?
I'm her future.
Really?
Hi, my name's Cris.
You okay, Kendall?
See, the thing is, I feel connected to you.
I don't know the reason why.
See, now, listen.
All right.
I think it's only fair that you
pay for the lady's breakfast.
What are you having?
Pecan pie is amazing.
Excuse me, I can pay
for my own breakfast.
And you know what?
You two work things out.
Okay.
You're hurting me.
Kendall, I think you're having
another off day.
Who the hell are you?
I'm her future.
Really?
Incoming.
Did you see that?
Goddamn it! Kendall!
What? Don't blame me.
This is your fault.
Get out of here!
Will somebody please call the cops?
I am so sorry.
Are you okay?
Let me help you.
Come on,
let's get you cleaned up.
Come on.
Okay.
Oh, yeah,
I'm seeing some stars.
Yeah.
I'm Liz.
Cris.
You must have a death wish
getting involved in that.
Here. Just...
Okay.
Just...
Okay, hold it there
for a little bit.
Okay.
Yeah.
It will.
What will?
Your luck. It's going to change.
What are you? A leprechaun?
Do leprechauns get punched in the
face or have their car stolen?
Your car was stolen?
Yeah. I'm hoping
they find it today.
I'm supposed to be
in Flagstaff.
Hey, is this tooth
loose here?
I don't know.
I don't think so.
Hurts.
Well, listen,
maybe I could give you a ride,
and I'm kind of
going that way.
That would really
be helpful, Liz. Thank you.
Well, I do have to
make a stop, though.
It's okay.
And it might take a few hours,
so if you're cool with that.
Hey, look, if you're
uncomfortable with this,
I'll take the bus.
No, no, no.
It's fine, it's fine.
You're not a psycho.
Right?
Because the first psycho vibe
I get, you're out of the car.
Okay. Yes, ma'am.
Okay.
Deal.
It's amazing, isn't it?
I end up in a diner
where you are,
and we're both headed
in the same direction.
I don't know if I would
call it amazing, but...
Destiny.
That's what it really is.
Okay, I'm starting to
get that psycho vibe.
Oh no.
You don't believe in destiny?
Well, even if it does exist,
I don't think I want to know.
I mean, if every move we make
is preordained,
then what is
the point of that?
I mean, life is supposed
to be a surprise.
Isn't it?
It would be nice.
Yeah.
So he came in twice a day
for a week at exactly 8:09?
Yeah, he'd stay a few minutes,
have a martini, and then he'd go.
Till today,
when he met that lady.
You didn't find
anything strange about that?
Not strange enough
to call the police.
We got a regular that counts
the corn flakes in his bowl
because it has to be
an even number.
Got any cameras?
Inside? No.
Outside?
No.
Did you notice what kind
of car he was driving?
Maybe overhear
where they were going?
I don't know what car, but they
were headed up to Flagstaff.
Flagstaff.
That's what they said.
Got another regular,
she's always on a diet.
Brings in a scale
and her own salad dressing.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Guy knows we're after him,
but he still risks coming here.
8:09, twice a day.
Doesn't even know if it's day or night.
Just the time.
He was waiting for her.
All right, there's a
traffic cam over there,
a bank, a 7-Eleven
across the street.
Just run all the tapes. Maybe we'll
get lucky and catch him in wide.
Your buddy Roybal,
the casino chief?
Had his throat cut last night
after getting a kneecap shot off.
You're telling me this now?
We just talked to him about Johnson.
Hey, I just found out.
All right.
Local weapon?
Dead end.
And forensics came up empty.
Not a hair, not a fiber.
Somebody wants information.
Now, the next time anything
happens relative to Johnson,
I want to know right away.
I don't care
if it's a paper cut.
Okay, boss.
That's good! Good.
Right there!
The head of casino security,
what did you learn from him?
For a macho guy,
he screams like a girl.
But he was questioned by federal
agents looking for Cris Johnson,
yes?
He said they haven't
found him yet.
Do you believe this shit?
He can see things
before they happen?
It makes no difference
what I believe.
Look, we spent two years
setting this up
and that man out there
is worried all this will be
compromised by Johnson.
We're wasting our time
looking for some magician.
We're being paid to secure
the operation, Jones,
not to hunt down
some carnival barker.
Really? Then why are
the same authorities
that are looking for us
so interested in him?
Get rid of him.
Do it now.
Hey.
Havasupai Reservation.
I teach here once a week.
The conditions
are pretty lousy.
But it's in the Canyon, one of
the Eight Wonders of the World.
Hey, Sam.
Hey, Liz.
Well, a couple hundred years
ago, this tribe was booming.
Plenty of food and a thriving culture.
They should be better off.
But I guess this was
just their destiny.
I'd like to meet
their shaman.
I read once that in many
North American tribes
their shaman's purpose
wasn't only healing
but they also claimed to have
power over the atmosphere.
To bring on or stop rain.
Even know future events.
Do you think
that's possible?
Well, I believe
anything is possible.
Me, too.
Whose birthday?
One of my students'.
Hey! Hi!
How's it going?
Hello! How is everybody? Good?
That's good.
Oh, I was close.
That was a lot. You messed up
on the last part.
On the last part. Yeah.
I thought you weren't
coming back until next Monday.
Well, I'm not, but it's Jake's birthday.
How could I miss that?
Who's that man you're with?
Is he your boyfriend?
No, no, he's not my boyfriend.
He's just my friend.
I think he likes you.
Well, why would you say that?
Because he looked at you like my
brother looks at his girlfriend.
Hey, Jake,
you want to see some magic?
I'll show you something.
Come here.
I found this rock
out in the Canyon
and I want you to hold it
because it's a magic rock.
That's right. Hold it really tight.
Keep squeezing.
It's magic.
He won't bite.
Happy birthday.
So, you're a magician?
Well...
I have a small magic act
back in Vegas.
The Frank Cadillac Show.
I thought your name was Cris.
It is.
Frank Cadillac
is my stage name.
How did you
come up with that?
I picked two things I really
liked and I put them together.
Frankenstein and Cadillacs.
You are odd.
Charming,
but odd.
Cease fire!
Visitor on the range!
Nice.
A little close, though.
Okay.
You were right about the traffic cam.
We got a positive ID.
I'm sorry.
Don't be.
It's okay.
Did I drool?
Drool?
Yeah.
Drool? No.
Oh, my God, it's coming down
so hard.
Yeah.
I like rain.
I like rain, too.
You know, once,
I think it was in Denmark,
it rained fish.
Because the sun
dehydrated the water
and took it up
into the atmosphere,
rehydrated the fish eggs
and they hatched
and it rained fish.
Is that true?
Yeah, in the clouds. True story.
It happened 50 years ago.
I just felt like
sharing that with you.
Road's washed out ahead.
You can't cross till morning.
Not even then
if this keeps up.
You want to spin around
and go back about two miles,
take your second left.
There'll be a motel there called...
"The Cliffhanger." Thanks.
Right.
Him, right?
That's it?
There's no front plate.
Where's the other side?
I don't have it.
What was that
on the front window? Go back.
Back, back.
Back. There! Zoom in.
That's a permit.
Track it and find her.
I'll light a fire.
Cris, one little problem.
Oh, no, no,
I'm going to sleep in the car.
Okay.
Here.
Thanks.
Sure.
Hey, did you hear the joke about the
Zen master who ordered the hot dog?
No.
He said he'd have one
with everything.
Good night.
What do we have?
They're at the Cliffhanger
Motel outside Flagstaff.
We found an Arizona DOT foreman
who remembered the Land Cruiser.
Why would he do that?
The road was flooded. He was about
to suggest a place to stay.
But Johnson
already knew. Right?
Exactly.
Callie. It just got worse.
All right, people,
we've got a nuclear alert.
Code Red, in the Southern
California region. L.A. to San Diego.
95% certainty.
Nuclear emergency search teams are
on the way, but until they get here,
can somebody please tell me what my
agency, the FBI, is doing about it?
Sir, tier-one suspects
have been interrogated.
Cars and premises have been
checked, friends and acquaintances.
We've opened up surveillance on
tier-two and three suspects,
but nothing actionable yet.
Oh, is that what we're doing,
waiting for something actionable?
There are eight million lives
that are precarious at best.
I say we widen the net
to "slightly suspicious"
and get some decent intel before
this nuke blows up Los Angeles.
All right, Callie.
What do you propose
we do next?
I believe that the urgency
of this situation
compels the use of any and all
resources to obtain Cris Johnson.
We know where he is.
Let my team pick him up.
He said they're mobilizing.
Standard procedure
when security is escalated.
Tell him to wrap it up.
They'll lead us
straight to Johnson.
You hungry? There's a
coffee shop down the road.
I'd rather eat here,
if that's okay.
Sure.
What?
There's an Italian painter
named Carlotti,
and he defined beauty.
He said it was
the summation of the parts
working together in such a way
that nothing needed to be
added, taken away or altered.
That's you.
You're beautiful.
Wow.
That was incredible.
What was?
This.
Right here gives us
a good standoff position
and open view
of the front of the motel.
We can run multiple point
and area surveillances
from this road here,
that turn out.
Get a team with a
parabolic set right here.
That's fine, but I also want
mobile surveillance.
And give me
two or three roamers.
If he rabbits on us,
I want to be flexible.
Ferris.
Call the local police
in Flagstaff.
Tell them to hold
the outside perimeter.
I want that area locked down.
A body turned up
in an apartment
with a line of sight
to my office.
Slit throat, like Roybal.
Somebody's trying
to follow us to Johnson.
Cris.
Yeah.
Maybe there is such a thing
as destiny.
Give it 40 seconds.
So, after two minutes, he just stops
seeing what's going to happen?
I sure as hell hope so.
Elizabeth Cooper?
Yeah.
Federal Agent Ferris.
What is this about?
I'm going to need
a few minutes of your time.
Yeah, okay.
They're putting her
in the car.
Drop the gun!
Step back.
It's his gun.
He was going to shoot two people!
This was three days ago?
He used you
to get away from us in Vegas.
You can be pretty sure that
everything he told you is a lie.
He's delusional. A sociopath.
Oh, my God.
Oh, shit.
Go back
to the motel.
Have a drink.
Put one of these in his glass.
It'll take five minutes
to put him to sleep.
Then we'll come in
and get him.
Nobody's been hurt.
But this is important.
You need to do it
at least two minutes
after you get him
out of the room.
Why do you need me?
Why can't you just get him?
Liz, as I understand it, you work
for a federally funded program
teaching on various reservations.
Is that true?
Yes, that's true.
Well, I'd think
you'd be eager to help us.
We're on the same team.
Now they're letting her go.
Hey.
Thanks for the note.
Sure.
Did you have a nice walk?
I did.
You know,
it's really beautiful here.
I have a present for you.
Oh, thanks.
I need that.
Yeah.
Is something wrong?
Oh, no, no, I'm fine.
Why don't you go wash up and
I'm gonna make us breakfast?
Okay.
45 seconds.
One minute, thirty.
And that's two.
Looks good.
You think so?
Thank you.
Don't drink that!
It's drugged.
Oh, God, I don't know
what I'm doing.
I have no idea what I'm doing.
Some federal agent
came up to me and said
that you were a delusional
sociopath and showed me this tape.
So maybe you are.
But I don't want
to believe that.
I don't think
I can believe that.
And she also said
that if you ran,
they would shoot you.
So I should drug you instead.
Even if what they said is true,
I don't want you to die.
Cris, is it true?
Oh, shit.
Wow!
Get me broadband noise reduction.
I don't like hearing this!
Speak quietly
and act normally.
How long did they say
the drugs would take?
About five minutes.
...a nice inside kick.
Wow!
What is he doing?
He's drinking.
Give it a minute.
Got a clean shot?
Not yet.
The man in that casino
would have killed two people.
It happened.
It just hadn't happened yet.
Oh, my God,
you are delusional.
Fluffy cranberry or a stack of
chocolate chip pancakes for the kids.
Fluffy cranberry or a
stack of chocolate chip pancakes
for the kids in an instant.
Safe? Who knows what's safe?
I knew a man who dropped dead
from looking at his wife.
Safe?
Who knows what's safe?
I knew a man dropped dead
from looking at his wife.
You can't get lost in the woods
if you never go into the woods.
You can't
get lost in the woods
if you never go
into the woods.
That's right, sir. You're the
only person authorized to do so.
That's right, sir. You are
the only person authorized to do so.
How are you doing this?
I have no idea how, but I can.
I was born with it.
Is this some kind of a trick?
You know we don't
have time for that.
You said
anything was possible.
So, you see things
before they happen?
You see the future?
My future. What'll affect me,
and only two minutes ahead.
Except you.
For some reason, I saw you.
For some reason, I saw you
far beyond anything I'd ever
seen before and I don't know why.
What do you mean, you saw me?
You've been...
You've been doing that to me?
You know what I'm going to do
and what I'm going to say?
That you've just been
setting me up?
No, I haven't.
I wanted to find you because I
needed to know why I was seeing you.
And because I...
It wasn't a setup.
What do they want from you?
They think I can help them in
matters of national security.
...call code is received.
The normal SSB radios
in the aircraft...
I don't understand.
If you can help, then why don't you?
Because I can't.
I can only give them
a two-minute head start.
And that's if my life
is personally involved.
But with me,
you can see further.
Yeah.
But they don't know that.
There's almost $10,000
in this envelope.
They know about you.
You need to get away from here.
What time do you have?
9:10.
Set your watch to 9:17.
Read this when I leave
and wait exactly 45 seconds
before you do what it says.
I'll take Ferris with me.
It might be a week or a month,
but if you can wait,
I'll find you.
...and yes, gentlemen, they are on their
way and no one can bring them back.
Something's wrong.
Don't do it.
I already have.
Go get him! Alive!
Let's go!
Bitch! Come on!
Are you crazy?
Oh, shit!
Watch out! Get down!
Johnson.
You know you're not
going to shoot.
You going to let me die?
Hey, I need some help!
Let's get him out of here!
- Let's get him out of here.
- I got him.
You all right? You okay?
Open your eyes. Look at me.
No good deed goes unpunished,
does it?
She got him.
Now what?
You see her?
Smoke?
Thanks for today.
Could've let me die.
I appreciate it.
That was a real show
of character.
I know I seem like
the bad guy in all this,
but in the interests
of preserving our freedom
there are larger issues
at play.
What about my freedom?
With freedom
comes responsibility.
I have rights.
This isn't about you.
This is about
eight million other people.
If I do what you want, you'll
keep me in this chair forever.
There is a nuclear bomb
somewhere in Los Angeles.
And every television station
in the world
will broadcast the precise
details of its detonation.
So, go on, push that two
minutes as far as you can
and find it.
The system, which is still
just a tropical storm,
is picking up steam and
heading for the U.S.
Experts fear this storm
has a good chance of growing to an
F3 status before making landfall.
More worrisome, though,
is the strong possibility
that it could travel through
what is known as Hurricane Alley
into the Gulf of Mexico.
The warm Gulf waters would cause
the storm to intensify quickly.
Evacuation plans are
already in place...
...broadcast
this afternoon for
breaking news out of
downtown Los Angeles.
...largest technology
corporations oppose this idea,
and tech lobbying is blamed
for stalling the proposal...
...members of the
LAPD bomb squad
are staging in that area.
We go live now to reporter Lisa Joyner
at the scene for the very latest. Lisa.
Jeff, the standoff began when police
received an anonymous phone call
stating that explosives would be
detonated at this parking garage
at 2nd and Broadway
at 6:00 tonight.
There's no...
They have no idea on a motive.
The victim, however...
Liz, I'm sorry.
What?
What did you say?
The LAPD has surrounded the area.
They've secured a perimeter.
But now the bomb squad
is making their way
onto the deck of this building.
And they're the men that are walking
up with black suits on and such.
Oh, my God.
There's been...
There's been an explosion.
There's been an explosion...
Oh, my God.
The victim
has been identified
as Elizabeth Cooper
of Las Vegas.
She was strapped
to a wheelchair.
Sorry.
Approximately 10% of U.S.
workers receive stock options.
Many technology companies
give the options away...
Tell me what just happened.
Yeah, I can't.
It won't work like this.
Get me out of this room
and I'll do what you want.
I beg you, please get me
out of this room.
Let him out!
Callie! Callie, wait up.
What?
Forensics report
on Betty Peterson.
The dead girl in the apartment?
Her throat was cut, bled out.
Otherwise, nothing to DNA.
The place was immaculate again.
How'd it go with Johnson?
Well, something happened,
but he's not sharing.
You know, there are traces
of potassium iodide.
Some medication
Peterson was taking?
They found an empty pillbox.
No.
The only reason to take it is
to prevent radiation poisoning.
Hey, wait, can I get a smoke
or something? I need to relax.
Thanks.
Hey, can I get a light?
Look at this. Look.
Ta-da!
Get it up here! Let's go!
Base, Air 1.
Base, Air 1. I've got visual.
Subject is spotted heading
south on 5th Street.
Be advised, subject is
turning east onto Broadway.
Stay here.
Let me deal with this.
Why are you here?
They killed her.
Two hours from now.
They killed Liz.
Tell me what you saw.
I saw them execute her.
Right there.
On the roof.
It hasn't happened yet
and I know who has her.
It's the same people
we're after.
There's a reason that they brought
you here. They're using Liz as bait.
10-1 you go out on that roof,
they're going to put
a bullet in your brain.
I know.
Right now,
she's still alive.
She is, you are, we all are.
Let's try to keep it that way.
I help you, you help me,
all right?
I want a two-mile radius.
Every telephone grid,
shortwave, cell tower.
Shut it down.
What do you want me to do?
Let him shoot you.
Your call cannot
be completed as dialed.
Check the number
and dial again.
Your call cannot be
completed as dialed.
FBI!
Down on your knees!
You okay?
That looked pretty close.
Sleight of hand.
You didn't get him.
Not alive. He fired on the chopper.
But it doesn't matter.
He couldn't call in the hit.
So as far as they're concerned,
you're not here yet.
It buys us time.
Every way I try this,
she still ends up dead.
What if you do it earlier?
They have to bring her here
in a vehicle, right?
Looking for a license plate.
Right.
Can you see it?
It helps if you don't speak
right now.
California plate number
50KF272.
California tag. 5, 0,
kilo, foxtrot, 2, 7, 2.
Please, where are you
taking me?
What do you want with me?
Who the hell are you people?
SITREP, Cavanaugh.
Local SWAT has been deployed and the
regional team just showed to back us up.
All right, listen up.
A van carrying Elizabeth
Cooper will exit the warehouse
across from Pier 18 compound
in approximately five minutes.
Four minutes and 27 seconds.
Do you mind?
Not anymore. Go ahead.
They've got her wrapped in
explosives, wired to a cell phone.
Remote trigger.
Another cell phone sets it off.
Usually a one-button
speed dial.
They'll take this route
to the entrance gate.
At that point, Alpha and Bravo
will swarm the entrance...
If you could just be quiet
and do exactly what I say,
I'll save your life.
We need to stop
the vehicle here
before they get
through the gates.
Alpha and Bravo
will hold and contain here.
Sniper teams will initiate
on Johnson's call.
On his call. Are we clear?
All elements shoot
to kill any hostiles.
What about intel?
We don't need them.
We have him.
All right, everybody!
Let's go!
Move out! Let's go!
Go! Let's go! Move!
Back up! Back up! Back up!
Go, go, go!
Stop the van.
Not yet. You'll kill her.
Now.
You're good to go! Now, now!
This is Charlie 1 on
approach, east side of building.
Move back! Move back!
This is Alpha Unit, Alpha-U!
We're taking fire!
Take out the guy on the crane,
northeast corner.
Negative on a visual.
Give me that.
Aim for the doorway, eight
inches above the guardrail.
On me, let's go!
Zed David, Charlie
1 at entry point.
Turn right.
You're clear.
You're good! Go! Go!
Come on! Let's go!
Number 2 loading dock.
Repeat. Number 2 loading dock.
Stop.
No!
Go.
This is Charlie 1 element,
moving and clearing, over.
Thanks.
There are explosives
there, there and there.
Stay close.
Sniper.
Where?
Behind us.
Sniper, six o'clock.
Got a visual?
Nobody move!
I'll find him.
Catwalk, second level.
Catwalk, six o'clock.
Second level.
Got him.
We'll have to clear
this deck by deck.
You take this one.
I'll do the rest.
Let's sweep and clear.
She's near the engine room.
Come on, man.
Release the hostage.
You can still get out of this.
Don't patronize me.
How good are you
with that gun?
Very.
You're going to be okay, Liz.
Back off!
I've seen every
possible ending here.
None of them are good for you.
I'll take my chances.
One more step, fortune teller,
and it definitely
won't be good for you.
You have one way out of this.
That wasn't it.
Liz, look at me.
It's okay.
Look at me. It's over.
It's over.
No, it's not.
The nuclear device was moved.
We need to find its exact location.
Now, this registers any significant
detonation in the earth's crust.
Take a look.
Tell me what you see.
Something's wrong.
I made a mistake.
What?
It's happening.
When?
Now!
All right, I got four teams
in place.
We're just waiting
on the road crew.
All right.
Ferris.
It's me.
I'll do it,
but I have conditions.
I want her left out of it.
I'm sure we can work
something out.
Liz?
Hey.
Come back to bed.
I got to go.
Go where?
There's something I have to do.
I can't put it off any longer.
Are you coming back?
Yeah.
It may be a week
or a month.
But if you can wait,
I'll find you.
Here's the thing
about the future.
Every time you look at it,
it changes because
you looked at it.
And that changes
everything else.
You ready?
Yeah.