Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from www.OpenSubtitles.org
[Telephone Ringing]
[Heartbeat]
[Woman Screaming]
[Blade Slices]
[Ringing]
- Hello?
- [Male Voice] Hello.
- Yes?
- Who is this?
- Who you trying to reach?
- What number is this?
- What number are you trying to reach?
- I don't know.
- Well, I think you have the wrong number.
- Do I?
It happens. Take it easy.
[Hangs Up]
[Telephone Ringing]
[Rings]
[Groans]
Hello?
I'm sorry.
I guess I dialed the wrong number.
- So why'd you dial it again?
- To apologize.
- You're forgiven. Bye now.
- Wait, wait! Don't hang up.
- What?
- I wanna talk to you for a second.
They've got 900 numbers for that. See ya.
[Hangs Up]
[Scoffs]
[Crickets Chirping]
[Creaking]
[Telephone Rings]
[Groans]
[Beeps]
- Hello?
- Why don't you want to talk to me?
- Who is this?
- You tell me your name, I'll tell you mine.
[Chuckles]
I don't think so.
[Rattling]
- What's that noise?
- Popcorn.
- You're making popcorn?
- Uh-huh.
I only eat popcorn at the movies.
- Well, I'm getting ready to watch a video.
- Really? What?
Oh, just some scary movie.
- You like scary movies?
- Uh-huh.
- What's your favorite scary movie?
- Uh, I don't know.
You have to have a favorite.
What comes to mind?
Um, Halloween.
You know, the one with the guy
in the white mask...
who walks around and stalks babysitters?
- [Man] Yeah.
- What's yours?
Guess.
Um, Nightmare on Elm Street.
Is that the one where the guy
had knives for fingers?
- Yeah, Freddy Krueger.
- Freddy, that's right.
I liked that movie. It was scary.
Well, the first one was,
but the rest sucked.
So, you got a boyfriend?
[Chuckles]
Why? You wanna ask me out on a date?
- Maybe. Do you have a boyfriend?
- Mmm, no.
- You never told me your name.
- Why do you want to know my name?
'Cause I want to know who I'm looking at.
What did you say?
[Dog Barking]
I want to know who I'm talking to.
- That's not what you said.
- What do you think I said?
[Switch Clicks]
What?
Hello?
Look, I gotta go.
Wait! I thought we were gonna go out.
Uh, no. I don't think so.
Don't hang up on me!
[Beeps]
[Popping]
[Rings]
Shit.
[Beeps]
- Yes?
- I told you not to hang up on me.
- What do you want?
- To talk.
Well, dial someone else, okay?
[Beeps]
[Popping Continues]
[Rings]
[Beeps]
Listen, asshole!
No, you listen, you little bitch!
You hang up on me again,
I'll gut you like a fish, understand?
[Chuckles]
Yeah.
Is this some kind of joke?
More of a game, really.
Can you handle that,
blondie?
- Can you see me?
- [Breathing Heavily]
Listen, I am two seconds away
from calling the police.
They'd never make it in time.
We're out in the middle of nowhere.
- What do you want?
- To see what your insides look like.
[Sobs]
[Doorbell Ringing]
[Screams]
Who's there? Who's there?
I'm calling the police.
[Rings]
[Screams]
[Beeps]
You should never say, “Who's there?”
Don't you watch scary movies?
It's a death wish.
You might as well just come out here
to investigate a strange noise or something.
Look, you've had your fun now,
so I think you better just leave or else.
Or else what?
Or else my boyfriend'll be here any second,
and he'll be pissed when he finds out.
I thought you didn't have a boyfriend.
I lied! I do have a boyfriend, and he'll be
here any second, so your ass better be gone.
- Sure.
- I swear.
He's big and he plays football
and he'll kick the shit out of you!
I'm getting scared.
I'm shaking in my boots.
So you better just leave.
His name wouldn't be...
Steve, would it?
How do you know his name?
Turn on the patio lights... again.
Oh, God!
[Lock Clicks]
- I wouldn't do that if I were you.
- Where are you? Where are you?
Guess.
Please don't hurt him.
[Muffled Shouting]
That all depends on you.
Why are you doing this?
- I wanna play a game.
- No.
- Then he dies right now!
- No! No!
Which is it? Which is it?
Wha— What kind of game?
Turn off the light.
You'll see what kind of game.
Just do it!
[Mouthing Words]
[Muffled]
Casey! No! No!
No! Casey!
Here's how we play.
I ask a question.
If you get it right, Steve lives.
- Please don't do this.
- Come on. It'll be fun.
- Please.
- It's an easy category.
- Movie trivia.
- I'll even give you a warm-up question.
- Don't do this. I can't.
- Name the killer in Halloween.
- No.
Come on!
It's your favorite scary movie, remember?
He had a white mask,
he stalked the babysitters.
I don't know.
- Come on. Yes, you do.
- No, please.
- What's his name?
- I can't think.
Steve's counting on you.
Michael. Michael, Michael—
Yes! Very good.
- Now for the real question.
- No!
But you're doing so well.
We can't stop now.
- Please stop! Leave us alone!
- Then answer the question. Same category.
[Sniffles]
Oh, please stop.
Name the killer in Friday the 13th.
Jason! Jason! Jason!
I'm sorry. That's the wrong answer.
No, it's not!
No, it's not. It was Jason.
Afraid not. No way.
Listen, it was Jason.
I saw that movie 20 goddamn times!
Then you should know Jason's mother,
Mrs. Voorhees, was the original killer.
Jason didn't show up until the sequel.
I'm afraid that was a wrong answer.
You tricked me.
Lucky for you, there's a bonus round.
But poor Steve. I'm afraid he’s out!
[Muffled Screaming]
[Splattering]
[Groaning]
[Whimpering]
[Cackling]
Hey. We're not finished yet.
Final question. Are you ready?
[Sobbing]
Please. Please leave me alone.
Answer the question, and I will.
What door am I at?
What?
There are two main doors to your house—
a front door and the patio doors.
If you answer correctly, you live.
- Very simple.
- [Gasps]
Don't do this. I can't. I won't.
Your call.
[Screams]
[Footsteps]
- [Shouts]
- [Screams]
[Groans]
[Gasping]
[Glass Smashes]
[Muffled Whimpering, Screaming]
- [Yelps]
- [Grunts]
[Breathing Heavily, Whimpering]
- [Groans]
[Car Doors Open, Close]
[Man, Woman Chattering]
[Woman]
Did you water over here today?
- It was just that water from the rain.
- They look great, don't they?
- [Man] Don't they smell strong?
- I told you. You could send it back.
[Continues]
[Weakly]
Mom!
- Jesus!
- What is it?
[Growls]
Casey.
[Smoke Alarm Beeping]
Oh. Oh, G—
Casey? Casey?
Casey!
- Where is she?
- Call the police.
[Tapping Keys]
[Casey Gasps, Grunts]
Casey!
[Casey Grunts]
- Casey, you upstairs?
- Oh, my God. Casey, baby?
- [Father] Where is she?
- [Mother] She's here.
- Mama.
- [Mother] Oh, my God, I can hear her.
- [Weakly] Mom.
- Where is she?
[Gasping]
- [Whimpering]
- Oh, my God! I can hear her.
- [Gasps]
- [Man] Hey!
[Rapid Beeping]
Get in the car.
Drive down to the MacKenzies'.
- No. No, not my daughter.
- Just go.
- Not my daughter.
- Call the police.
[Screaming Continues]
[Thunderclap]
[Typing]
[Frogs Croaking]
[Thunder Rumbling]
[Typing Stops]
[Sighs]
[Typing Resumes]
[Clattering]
[Glass Breaks]
[Dog Barking]
[Screams]
- It's just me.
- Billy, what are you doing here?
- Sorry. Don't hate me.
- Oh, my God.
- You sleep in that?
- Yes, I sleep in this.
My dad is in the other room.
You can't be in here.
- I'll just stay a sec.
- No. You can't be—
[Knocking]
[Gasps] Oh, no.
You gotta go. Go, go, go.
What's going on in there?
- Are you okay?
- Can you knock?
- I heard screaming.
- No, you didn't.
No?
Oh, well. I'm hitting the sack.
My flight leaves
first thing in the morning.
Now, the expo runs all weekend,
so I won't be back till Sunday.
There's cash on the table,
and I'm staying at—
- The Hilton.
- Out at the airport, so call if—
- If I need anything. Yeah, I got it.
I could have sworn I heard screaming.
Have a good trip, okay?
Sleep tight, sweetie.
[Door Closes]
[Cartoon Voice]
Oh! Close call.
Billy—
[Sighs]
What are you doing here?
It occurred to me that...
I've never snuck through
your bedroom window.
Shh, shh, shh.
Great. And now that
it's out of your system—
I was home watching television.
The, uh—The Exorcist was on.
Got me thinking of you.
It did?
Yeah.
[Stereo On]
It was edited for TV—
all the good stuff was cut out—
♪♪ [Rock Ballad]
and it got me thinking of us.
How two years ago
we started off hot and heavy—
nice solid R-rating
on our way to an NC-1 7.
♪♪ [Man Singing]
And how things have changed and...
lately we're just sort of
edited for television.
Oh. So you thought
you would climb in my window...
and we'd have a little raw footage?
[Laughs] No. No, I wouldn't dream
of breaking your underwear rule.
I just— I thought maybe we could do
a little on-top-of-the-clothes stuff.
Okay.
Yeah?
Yeah.
♪ We'll be able to fly♪
♪ Baby, I'm your man ♪
♪ La, la, la, la, la ♪
[Chuckles]
Hey.
♪ La, la, la, la, la ♪
Okay. Okay, okay.
Time is up, stud-bucket.
God, you see what you do to me?
[Laughs]
You know what my dad will do to you?
Yeah.
- Well, I'm going.
- Okay.
♪ Romeo andJuliet♪
♪ Are together in eternity♪
You know, I appreciate
the romantic gesture.
♪ So, come on, baby♪
Hey.
About the, uh, sex stuff—
♪ Take my hand♪
I'm not trying to rush you at all.
I was only half serious.
[Laughs]
Okay.
♪ Baby, I'm your man ♪
Hey, Billy.
Would you settle for a PG-1 3 relationship?
What's that?
♪ La, la, la, la, la ♪
- [Chuckles]
- [Laughs]
My God. You're just a tease.
♪♪ [Ends]
[Police Radio Chatter]
[Chattering]
There's blood found? All right.
[Woman] ...are doing drugs,
that they are high in the classrooms,
and that they are involved in the occult.
- [Woman #2] Occult?
- [Voices Overlapping]
[Woman #3] The small town of Woodsboro,
California, was devastated last night...
when two young teenagers
were found brutally murdered.
Authorities have yet to issue a statement,
but our sources tell us
that no arrest has been made...
and the murderer could strike again.
- Do you believe this shit?
- [Gasps] Tatum!
- What is going on?
- You don't know?
No.
Casey Becker and Steve Orth
were killed last night.
What? No way!
And we're not just talking killed.
We're talking splatter-movie killed.
Ripped open from end to end.
Casey Becker.
She sits next to me in English.
Not anymore.
It's so sad. Her mom and dad,
they found her hanging from a tree,
her insides on the outside.
Oh, my God!
- Do they know who did it?
- Fucking clueless.
I mean, they're interrogating the entire
school— teachers, students, janitors.
- They think it's school-related?
- They don't know.
Dewey was saying this is the worst
crime they've seen in years,
even worse than—
[School Bell Rings]
Well, it's bad.
- Here you go, Mrs. Tate.
- Thank you, James.
[Tate]
Sidney.
It would appear to be your turn.
- Who's up next?
- Uh, Sidney Prescott.
- She was daughter of, uh—
- [Clears Throat]
- Sidney. How you feelin'?
- Fine.
Hi, Sidney.
Sheriff Burke, Dewey.
Uh, that's Deputy Riley today, Sid.
- [Burke] How is everything?
- Good.
And your dad? How's he doin'?
We're fine. Thanks.
We're gonna keep this
very brief, Sidney.
The police just want to
ask you a few questions. You okay?
Mm-hmm.
Sidney, were you very close
to Casey Becker?
[Man On P. A.] Remember, your principal
loves you, and I want you to be safe.
All students are encouraged to return
to their homes promptly from school grounds.
Avoid strangers. Walk in twos and threes.
[Tatum] What kind of questions
did they ask you, Sidney?
They asked if I knew Casey.
Yeah. They asked me that too.
- Hey, they ask if you like to hunt?
- Yeah, they did. They ask you?
Hunt? Why would they ask you
if you like to hunt?
'Cause their bodies were gutted.
Thank you, Randy.
They didn't ask me
if I like to hunt.
That's 'cause there's no way
a girl could've killed 'em.
That is so sexist.
The killer could easily be female.
Basic Instinct?
That was an ice pick.
Not exactly the same thing.
Yeah, Casey and Steve
were completely hollowed out.
And the fact is,
it takes a man to do something like that.
Or a man's mentality.
How do you... gut someone?
You take a knife,
and you slit 'em
from groin to sternum.
Hey. It's called tact, you fuck-rag.
Hey, Stu, didn't you used to date Casey?
Yeah, for like two seconds.
Before she dumped him
for Steve.
I thought you dumped her for me.
I did. He's full of shit.
And are the police aware
that you dated the victim?
Hey, what are you saying?
That I killed her?
It would certainly improve
your high school “Q.”
- Stu was with me last night, okay?
- Yeah, I was.
Ooh. Was that before or after
he sliced and diced?
[Tatum] Fuck you, nutcase.
Where were you last night?
Working, thank you.
At the video store?
I thought they fired your sorry ass.
Twice.
- I didn't kill anybody.
- Nobody said you did.
Thanks, buddy.
[Mocking] Besides, it takes a man
to do something like that.
I'm gonna gut your ass in a second, kid.
Tell me something—
[Imitating Jerry Lewis]
Did you really put her liver in the mailbox?
'Cause I heard they found her liver in the
mailbox next to her spleen and her pancreas.
Randy, you goon-fuck.
I'm trying to eat here.
She's getting mad, all right?
You better liver alone.
[Laughs]
Liver alone!
[Laughing]
Li— Ow!
Liver. Liver. It was a joke.
[Brakes Squealing]
- [Girl #1] See you, Sidney.
- [Girl #2] I'll talk to you tomorrow, Sid.
So, you sure I can stay over?
'Cause my dad won't be back till Sunday.
[Tatum] No problem.
I'll pick you up after practice.
You okay?
Uh-huh. It's just, you know,
the police and reporters and everything.
It's like déjà vu all over again.
I'll be there by 7:00. I promise.
- Thanks, Tatum.
- Later.
[Beeps]
[Dogs Barking In Distance]
[Lock Clicks]
[Clock Chiming]
The bodies of 1 7-year-old Casey Becker
and her 18-year-old boyfriend, Steven Orth,
were discovered late last night
by the girl's parents—
[Channel Changes]
[Man] The Woodsboro double murder case.
Authorities are baffled
by the lack of clues and the savage—
The town's in shock, and no one
can quite believe what has happened here,
although this is not the first time...
this small community of Woodsboro
has endured such tragedy.
Only a year ago,
Maureen Prescott, wife and mother,
was found raped and murdered
not far from this peaceful town square.
[TV Off]
[Exhales]
[Creaking]
[Ticking]
[Sighs]
[Dog Barking]
[Bird Caws]
[Ticking Continues]
[Telephone Rings]
[Exhales]
[Rings]
[Beeps]
Hello?
Practice ran late. I'm on my way, okay?
It's past 7:00.
Don't worry. Casey and Steve didn't bite it
till way after 10:00.
Oh. Oh, that's comforting.
I'm gonna swing by the video store.
I was thinkin' Tom Cruise
in All The Right Moves.
You know, if you pause it just right,
you can see his penis.
Whatever. Just hurry, okay?
- Ta-ta, Sid.
- [Beeps]
[Owl Hoots]
[Rings]
- [Beeps]
- Tatum, just get in the car—
[Male Voice]
Hello, Sidney.
Uh— Hi. Who is this?
You tell me.
Well, I have no idea.
Scary night, isn't it?
With the murders and all, it's like
right out of a horror movie or something.
[Laughs]
Randy, you gave yourself away.
Are you calling from work,
'cause Tatum's on her way over.
Do you like scary movies, Sidney?
I like that thing you're doing
with your voice, Randy. It's sexy.
What's your favorite scary movie?
Oh, come on.
You know I don't watch that shit.
Why not? Too scared?
No. No. It's just, what's the point?
They're all the same.
Some stupid killer stalking
some big-breasted girl who can't act,
who's always running up the stairs
when she should be going out the front door.
It's insulting.
Are you alone in the house?
[Sighs] Randy, that's so unoriginal.
I'm disappointed in you.
Maybe that's because I'm not Randy.
So who are you?
The question isn't “Who am I?”
The question is “Where am I?”
[Stammering]
So, where are you?
Your front porch.
Why would you be calling
from my front porch?
That's the original part.
Oh, yeah?
Well, I call your bluff.
[Bird Chirping]
[Owl Hooting]
- So where are you?
- Right here.
[Wind Chimes Tinkling]
[Exhales]
- Can you see me right now?
- Uh-huh.
Uh-huh. Okay.
What am I doin'? Huh?
Huh? What am I doin'? Hello!
[Chuckles]
Nice try, Randy.
Tell Tatum to hurry up, okay?
Bye now.
If you hang up on me,
you'll die just like your mother!
Do you wanna die, Sidney?
Your mother sure didn't.
Fuck you, you cretin!
[Screams, Grunts]
No!
[Grunts]
[Grunting, Gasping]
[Doorknob Rattling]
[Grunts]
[Door Clattering]
[Busy Signal]
Shit!
[Shivering]
[Gasps]
Billy! God!
Door's locked.
I heard screaming. You all right?
The killer's here. He's in the house.
He's in the house. He's gonna kill me.
He's gonna kill me.
He's gone. He's gone.
It's all right.
[Sobbing, Stops]
What?
Sid, what?
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Wait, wait, Sidney, wait!
Wait, wait, wait, wait! What's going on?
Sidney, come back! Sidney!
[Screams]
Sorry! I found this.
Come on!
[Man]
All right. Hold your hands together.
[Dewey] Do you wish to give up
your right to remain silent?
[Handcuffs Clicking]
I didn't do anything.
[Siren Wailing]
Do you wish to give up your right
to speak to an attorney...
and have them present
during questioning?
Ask her. She'll tell you.
Ask her.
- [Burke] What do you got, Dewey?
- I caught him, Sheriff.
- Wait!
- Who is that?
- Billy Loomis.
- Sheriff.
Sheriff, call these guys off.
I didn't do it.
[Groans]
Sheriff, wait. Wait, listen.
Call my dad.
Please, call him.
He'll tell you. Just call him.
Sidney! Sidney!
[Engine Starts]
- How's she doing?
- Sid's tougher than she looks.
[Siren Wailing]
Have to be, all the shit she's been through.
[Billy Screaming]
Sid!
Well, we're seein'
a lot of you today.
You gonna be able to come down to the station
and answer a few questions, Sid?
Oh, shit. Sidney!
God, Sid. I'm so sorry I was late.
Are you all right?
Tatum, you can't be here.
This is an official crime scene.
- It's okay.
- [Sighs]
Her dad's out of town, all right?
She's staying with us tonight.
- Does Mom know?
- Yes, doofus.
- Let's get you out of here.
- [Woman] She'll be okay.
- Thanks.
- Come on, Sid.
You won't believe this.
- [Man] Right there.
- Creepy, huh?
- [Man] Break this up.
- I'll be damned.
- What?
- Jesus! The camera, hurry!
My name isn't Jesus.
Sidney, is that you in there?
Excuse me.
Is that Sidney Prescott they took away?
- I'm not talking to you.
- What happened to her?
None of your damn business.
I heard something about a costume.
Is that true?
Can you tell me anything?
Yeah, you're a real pain in the ass.
Leave Sid alone.
Where's she goin'?
- Look. Kenny?
- Yeah?
I know that you're about
50 pounds overweight,
but when I say “hurry,”
please interpret that as
“move your fat, tub-of-lard ass now!”
[Snorts]
Did you find him?
You sure it was the Hilton?
At the airport.
[Typing]
He's not registered there.
[Sighs]
Could he have stayed somewhere else?
I don't know. I guess.
[Sniffles]
Don't worry, Sid.
We'll find him.
[Man] Dewey, they got
that mask in.
I'll be right back.
[Handcuffs Rattling]
Let me ask you this.
What are you doing
with a cellular telephone, son?
Everybody's got one, Sheriff.
I didn't make those calls, I swear.
Why don't you check the phone bill,
for Christ's sake?
Call Vital Phone Comp.
They got the records of every number dialed.
Thanks, Hank. We're on top of it.
What were you doing
over at Sidney's house tonight?
I wanted to see her. That's all.
And last night? Sidney said you crawled
through her window last night too.
You went out last night?
[Stammers]
I was watching TV.
I got bored. I decided to go for a ride.
Did you happen to ride by
Casey Becker's house?
No. No, I didn't.
Sheriff, I didn't kill anybody,
We're gonna have to hold you, son,
till we get those phone records.
This is crazy.
You know that? I didn't do it.
[Chattering]
[Woman]
Camera Two? Okay.
Are there any more doughnuts in there?
- Move it, Kenny.
- They're not lettin' anybody in.
I'm not just anyone.
[Mutters]
More like a bitch goddess.
- Kenny, are we on?
- Yeah, go.
Hi. Gale Weathers reporting live
from the Woodsboro police station,
where we hope to get a glimpse
of Sidney Prescott.
[Man]
Hey. Watch it, lady.
Hey, watch the hand!
You know who you're dealing with here?
Tell 'em. Come on, Dad.
Tell 'em!
- Just wait for the lawyer, Billy.
- Sidney!
- Sidney, come on. You know me.
- [Deputy] Come on, come on.
- Sidney, look at me!
- [Deputy] Don't give us any trouble.
[Billy]
Come on!
Sid.
We're gonna get you
out of here, okay? You okay?
[Sighs] They sell this costume
at every five-and-dime in the state.
There's no way to track the purchase.
What about that cellular phone bill?
We're pulling Loomis's account.
We won't know anything until the morning.
[Tatum]
Oh, come on!
You think he did it?
Twenty years ago,
I would've said, “Not a chance.”
But these kids today—
[Snorts]
Damned if I know.
- Hey, Dewey, can we go now?
- Hold on a second.
- Goddamn it, Dewey!
- [Deputies Mocking]
What did Mama tell you? When I wear this
badge, you treat me like a man of the law.
I'm sorry, Deputy Dewey-boy,
but we're ready to go. Now, okay?
- [Man] Whoa.
- [Laughter]
Take 'em out the back way.
Avoid that circus out there.
- Come on.
- Don't touch me!
- He's my superior!
- Janitors are your superior.
Let's get back to work!
Isn't there a back way
out of this building?
Yeah. Down that alley, I think.
You guys stay here.
I'm gonna get the car.
Don't move.
Don't make a sound.
[Gale]
There she is. Sidney!
Hi. Some night.
What happened? Are you all right?
She's not answering any questions,
all right? Just leave us alone.
No. No, Tatum, it's okay.
She's just doin' her job, right, Gale?
- Yes, that's right.
- So, how's the book?
Well, it'll be out later this year.
Oh. I'll look for it.
I'll send you a copy.
[Grunts]
[Kenny]
Ooh! Jeez.
- [Kenny] Nice shot.
- [Gale] Bitch.
- No, I mean, camera shot.
- Where'd you learn to punch like that?
God, I loved it. “I'll send you a copy.”
Bam! Bitch went down.
“I'll send you a copy.”
Bam! Sid, superbitch!
You are so cool.
Thought you might
want some ice for that right hook.
Thanks.
I'll be right next door.
Try to get some sleep.
Yeah, yeah.
Do you really think Billy did it?
[Telephone Rings]
He was there, Tatum.
He was destined to have a flaw.
I knew he was too perfect.
[Knocking]
- Telephone, honey.
- Who is it?
- It's for Sid.
- My dad?
- I don't think so.
- [Tatum] Take a message.
No. I'll get it.
How's she doin'?
Hello?
[Male Voice]
Hello, Sidney.
No!
Poor Billy boyfriend.
An innocent guy doesn't stand
a chance with you.
Leave me alone!
Looks like you fingered the wrong
guy... again!
[Knocking]
Who are you?
- Dewey!
- Hang up, Sid.
Don't worry.
You'll find out soon enough.
- I promise.
- [Mother] Dewey!
[Dial Tone]
[Dewey]
What?
- [Tatum] “What?”
- What?
Hello?
[Man] Sidney Prescott, who escaped
a vicious attack last night,
is the daughter of Maureen Prescott,
who was brutally killed last year...
when convicted murderer
Cotton Weary broke into their home...
and savagely raped
and tortured the deceased.
Cotton Weary is currently awaiting appeal
for the death sentence handed down...
after the young Sidney
testified against him.
She was the key witness
in the state's case against the—
It's never gonna stop, is it?
Billy was released.
His cellular bill was clean.
He didn't make those calls.
We're checkin'
every cellular account in the county.
Any calls made to you or Casey Becker
are being cross-referenced.
It's gonna take some time,
but we'll find him.
You okay?
[Siren Wails]
Don't worry, Sid.
It's school. You'll be safe here.
So how does it feel
to be almost brutally butchered?
Hey, now leave her alone.
People want to know!
They have a right to know!
- [Dewey] Leave her alone.
- How does it feel?
[Dewey] She just wants to get an education.
Turn that thing off.
What?
[Mouthing Words]
Just a sec.
Stop right there.
I'm not here to fight.
I just need to talk.
Kenny, camera, now!
- Off the record. No cameras.
- Forget it.
Please? You owe me.
- I owe you shit.
- You owe my mother!
Your mother's murder
was last year's hottest court case.
Somebody was gonna write
a book about it.
Right, and it had to be you
with all your lies and bullshit theories.
What is your problem?
You got what you wanted.
Cotton Weary's in jail.
They're gonna gas him.
A book is not gonna change that.
Do you still think he's innocent?
Your testimony put him away.
It doesn't really matter what I think.
During the trial, you did all those stories
about me. You called me a liar.
I think you falsely identified him, yes.
- Have you talked to Cotton?
- Many times.
And has his story changed?
Not one word.
He admits to having sex
with your mother, but that's all.
He's lying.
She never would have touched him.
He raped her,
and then... he butchered her.
Her blood was all over his coat.
He was drunk that night.
He left his coat at your house
after your mother seduced him.
I saw him leave wearing it.
[School Bell Rings]
No, you saw someone leave wearing that coat.
The same someone who planted it
in Cotton's car, framing him.
No. Cotton murdered my mother.
You're not so sure anymore, are you?
Nice welt, sweetie.
Let's go, Sid.
- The killer's still on the loose, isn't he?
- Come on, Sid.
Those murders are related.
- I'm sorry I mangled your face.
- Wait. Sidney, don't go!
Just stop, all right?
[Students Chattering]
Jesus Christ!
An innocent man on death row,
a killer still on the loose.
Kenny, tell me I'm dreaming.
- You wanna go live?
- No, no. Not so fast.
We don't have anything concrete.
This is huge. You can't just sit on it.
I know! That's why we need proof.
If I'm right about this,
I could save a man's life.
Do you know what that could do
for my book sales?
This is a mistake. I shouldn't be here.
I want you to meet me
right here after class, okay, Sid?
All right.
Hey, hey.
I haven't seen Billy around.
Is he really pissed?
You mean after you branded him
the Candyman? No, his heart's broken.
- Ow!
- Stu!
[Shrieking]
[Gasps]
[School Bell Rings]
[Shrieking Continues]
Why are they doing this?
Are you kidding me?
Look at this place. It's like Christmas.
- Stupidity leak.
- Ow. Easy.
Sidney!
- Oh! Ow!
- Jesus! Shit!
It's just me.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
You still think it's me.
No. No, I-I don't. It's just—
Somebody was there.
- Billy, someone tried to kill me.
- I know, I know.
The cops said I scared him away.
It wasn't me, Sid.
I know. He called me again
last night at Tatum's house.
You see? Couldn't have been me.
I was in jail. Remember?
I'm so... sorry. Please understand.
Understand what?
That I have a girlfriend...
who would rather accuse me of being
a psychopathic killer than touch me?
- You know that's not true.
- Then what is it?
What... is it?
Billy, I was attacked
and nearly filleted last night!
I mean between us.
You haven't been the same since—
since your mother died.
Is your brain leaking? My mom was killed.
I can't believe you're bringing this up!
- I know. It's been a year.
- Tomorrow! One year tomorrow.
I know. I think it's time you got over that.
I mean, when my mom left my dad,
I accepted it. It's the way it is.
She's not comin' back.
Your parents split up.
This is not the same thing.
Your mom left town.
She's not lying in a coffin somewhere.
Okay, okay, okay. I'm sorry.
It's a bad analogy.
But it's just that...
I want my girlfriend back.
- Sid!
- Billy.
I am sorry if my traumatized life...
is an inconvenience to you
and your perfect existence.
What? What—
Nobody said that. Sid!
Stupid!
You make me so sick!
Your entire havoc-inducing, thieving,
whoring generation disgusts me!
So, two of your fellow students
just savagely murdered,
and this is the way you show
your compassion and sensitivity, huh?
Let me tell you something.
You're both expelled! Get out!
Come on, Mr. Himbry!
- It was just a joke!
- That's not fair!
You're absolutely right. It is not fair.
Fairness would be to rip your insides out,
hang you from a tree...
so we can expose you for the heartless,
desensitized little shits that you are.
[Sighs]
[Girl #1] She was never attacked.
I think she made it all up.
- [Girl #2] Why would she lie about it?
- For attention!
The girl has some serious issues.
[Toilet Flushes]
And what if she did it?
What if Sidney killed Casey and Steve?
[Girl #2]
And why would she do that?
[Girl #1] Maybe she had the hots for Steve
and killed them both in a jealous rage.
What would Sidney want with Steve?
She has her own bubble-butt boyfriend, Billy.
Maybe she's a slut, just like her mother.
You're evil.
Please. it's a common fact.
Her mother was a tramp.
Cut some slack.
She watched her mom get butchered.
And it fucked her up royally.
Think about it.
Her mother's death leaves her disturbed
and hostile in a cruel and inhumane world.
She's delusional. “Where's God?”
Et cetera. Completely suicidal.
One day she snaps.
She wants to kill herself,
but she realizes that teen suicide
is out this year...
and homicide is a much healthier
therapeutic expression.
- Where do you get this shit?
- Ricki Lake.
[Scoffs]
You are pathetic!
[Door Opens, Closes]
Pathetic.
[Hissing]
[Male Voice Whispers]
Sidney.
Is someone there?
[Door Closes]
[Mouths Word]
[Shouts]
[Shrieking]
- [Gasps, Panting]
- [Woman] In what appears to be a prank,
several students were seen
wearing scary masks.
School officials have yet to comment,
but this is known to be
the same costume worn by the killer.
Seventeen-year-old Casey
Becker and her boyfriend,
Steven Orth,
have already lost their lives.
Who's next? You can literally
feel the fear on this campus.
Hi! Gale Weathers,
field correspondent, Top Story.
I know who you are, Miss Weathers.
How's the eye?
It's productive.
Is there a problem on campus?
No, everything's under control.
Well, of course. You're here.
You're not supposed to be here.
I know. I should be in New York covering
the Sharon Stone stalker, but who knew?
You look awfully young
to be a police officer.
I'm 25 years old.
You know, in a demographic study,
I proved to be most popular
amongst males 1 1 to 24.
Guess I just missed you.
[Chuckles]
Course, you don't look a day over 1 2.
Except in that upper torso area.
Does the force require you to work out?
No, ma'am.
'Cause of my boyish good looks,
muscle mass has increased my acceptance
as a serious police officer.
- [P. A.: Feedback]
- [Himbry] I need your attention now, kids.
Due to the recent events
that have occurred,
effective immediately, all classes
are suspended until further notice.
[Teens Cheering] The Woodsboro police
department has issued a citywide curfew...
beginning at 9:00 tonight.
[Teens Groaning]
Looks like we've got
a serial killer on our hands.
Serial killer's not really accurate.
Gotta knock off a couple more
to get that title.
Well, we can hope, can't we?
[Chuckles]
I mean, we certainly don't have any leads.
Have you located Sidney's father yet?
No, not yet.
He's not a suspect, is he?
We haven't ruled him out
as a... possibility.
If you'll excuse me.
I'm sorry. Am I keeping you?
If I may say so, Miss Weathers,
you are much prettier in person.
So you do watch the show.
I'm 25. I was 24 for a whole year.
Please, call me Gale.
It was just some sick fuck
having a laugh, Sidney.
No. It was him, Tatum. I know it.
Well, you're not to be alone anymore, right?
If you pee, I pee. Is that clear?
Cizzool cuz scizzool is izzout.
I don't know what you did, Sidney,
But on behalf of the entire student body,
- we all say, “Thank you!”
- Drop it, Stu.
I say, impromptu party tonight,
my house.
Celebrate this little siesta.
What do you say?
[Sidney]
Are you serious?
This little vixen doesn't invite
the entire world, we'll be fine.
Intimate gathering, intimate friends.
What do you say, Sid?
I mean, pathos could have its perks.
Totally protect you.
Yo, I am so buff.
- I got you covered, girl.
- I don't know.
I mean, come on, Sid.
For me? It could be fun.
Okay. Whatever.
Yeah? Nice.
Cool. You guys bring food, all right?
[Imitating Engine]
[Growls]
[Laughs]
[Knocking]
Yes?
Hello?
[Knocking]
Damn it.
Damn little shits.
What'd you call me? Huh?
- Not you, Fred.
- [Mutters] You little prick.
[Screaming]
[Groans]
[Man Singing Rock]
♪ School's out for summer♪
♪ School's out with fever♪
What if Cotton Weary is telling the truth?
Maybe he was having
an affair with your mom.
I mean, your dad was always
out of town on business. Maybe—
Maybe your mom was just
a very unhappy woman.
If they were having an affair,
how come Cotton couldn't prove it in court?
Well, you can't prove a rumor.
That's why it's a rumor.
Right. Created by
that little tabloid twit, Gale Weathers.
It goes further back, Sid.
[Exhales]
There's been talk about other men.
And you believe it.
Well—
I mean, you can only hear that Richard Gere
gerbil story so many times...
before you have to start believing it.
Oh, I'm sorry.
You know, if I was wrong
about Cotton Weary,
then the killer's still out there.
Don't go there, Sid.
You're starting to sound like
some Wes Carpenter flick or something.
Don't freak yourself out, okay?
We've got a long night ahead of us.
Okay?
Let's boogie.
- It's alive!
- Henry, in the name of God.
In the name of God!
Now I know—
- Watch it, jerk.
- I'm sorry.
[Mock Scream, Laughs]
Dork.
Jesus, this place
is packed tonight, man.
- We had a run in the mass murder section.
- Comin' to my fiesta?
- Yeah, I'm off early. Curfew, you know.
- Cool.
What's that werewolf movie
with E.T.'s mom in it?
- The Howling. Horror. Straight ahead.
- Okay, thanks.
- Oh, now that's in poor taste.
- What?
If you were the only suspect
in a senseless bloodbath,
would you be standing
in the horror section?
What? It was just a misunderstanding.
He didn't do anything.
You're such a little lapdog.
He's got “killer” printed
all over his forehead.
[Mocking]
Okay! Really?
Well, why'd the cops let him go,
smart guy?
Because obviously
they don't watch enough movies.
This is standard horror movie stuff.
Prom Night revisited, man.
Yeah? Why would he want to
kill his own girlfriend?
There's always some stupid, bullshit
reason to kill your girlfriend.
- Huh?
- That's the beauty of it all: simplicity.
Besides, if it gets too complicated,
you lose your target audience.
Well, what's his reason?
Maybe Sidney wouldn't have sex with him.
[Laughs]
What, is she savin' herself for you?
Maybe. Now that Billy tried to mutilate her,
do you think Sid would go out with me?
No, I don't at all. No.
You know who I think it is?
Yo, I think it's her father.
Why can't they find her pops, man?
Because he's probably dead.
His body will come poppin' up
in the last reel somewhere!
Eyes gouged out,
fingers cut off, teeth knocked out!
The police are always
off-track with this shit.
If they'd watch Prom Night,
they'd save time.
There's a formula to it. A very simple
formula! Everybody's a suspect!
I'm telling you,
the dad's a red herring. It's Billy.
How do we know
you're not the killer? Huh?
- Huh?
- Hi, Billy.
Maybe your movie-freaked mind lost its
reality button. You ever think of that?
You're absolutely right.
I'm the first to admit it.
If this were a scary movie,
I'd be the prime suspect.
- That's right.
- And what would be your motive?
It's the millennium.
Motives are incidental.
Millennium. Hmm.
Millennium. I like that.
That's good.
It's the millennium.
Good kid.
“Millennium.” Good word, my man.
And you're telling me that's not a killer.
♪♪ [Rock Ballad]
♪ You'll see him in your nightmares♪
♪ You'll see him in your dreams♪
♪ He'll appear out of nowhere ♪
♪ But he ain't what he seems♪
♪ You'll see him in your head♪
♪ On the TVscreen ♪
♪ Hey, buddy, I'm warnin'you to turn it off♪
♪ He's a ghost, he's a god♪
♪ He's a man, he's a guru♪
♪ You're one microscopic cog
in his catastrophic plan ♪
♪ Designed and directed
by his red right hand♪
♪♪ [Continues]
[Dewey] Sure is quiet.
God, look at this place.
It's The Town That Dreaded Sundown.
Yeah, I saw that movie.
It's about a killer in Texas, huh?
- Mmm.
- Hey, Sid, just think.
If they make a movie about you,
who's gonna play you?
I shudder to think.
I see you as a young Meg Ryan myself.
Thanks, Dewey. With my luck,
they'd cast Tori Spelling.
I'm just gonna be a few minutes.
You girls don't go too far.
Is Billy gonna
be there tonight?
He'd better not be.
I told Stu to keep his mouth shut.
I think we can live
without the endorphin rush for one night.
Billy's right, you know. Whenever he
touches me, I just can't relax.
So you have a few intimacy issues
as a result of your mother's untimely death.
That's no big deal, Sid. You'll thaw out.
Yeah, but he has been so patient with me—
you know, with all the sex stuff.
How many guys would put up with
a girlfriend who's sexually anorexic?
Billy and his penis
don't deserve you, all right?
[Police Radio Chatter]
- Dewey, where the hell you been?
- I was keepin' an eye on Sidney, uh—
Thought you quit.
I did. But damn it—
Dewey, Vital Phone just faxed us.
Those calls are listed to Neil Prescott,
Sidney's father.
He made the calls with a cellular phone.
It's been confirmed.
There's no way his cellular
could've been cloned?
There's more. Guess what tomorrow is.
The anniversary of his wife's death.
We'll keep the roadblocks and the curfew
in effect through the night.
If he's not picked up by morning,
then we'll do a house-to-house.
Where's Sidney?
She's with my sister.
You want me to bring her in?
Nah. Not just yet.
Let's find Neil first,
make sure he's our man.
You stay close to Sidney.
Don't let her out of your sight.
Yes, sir.
♪♪ [Hard Rock]
♪ Say a prayer for the youth of America ♪
♪ God bless the youth of America ♪
♪ I can't stand their sight anymore ♪
All right. You girls have fun.
Not too much fun, or I'll bust you.
- Bye.
- Bye, Sid.
♪ You're obsessed♪
- Caterer's here.
- [Shouting, Whooping]
Oh. That's mature.
You guys were tardy for the party,
so we started without you.
- My man!
- [Belches]
♪♪ [Continues]
[Engine Off]
Shh.
Well, were we spotted?
I don't think so. Now get the camera.
- I'm sorry. I didn't mean to scare you.
- [Sighs] Deputy, that's okay.
What brings you
to these parts?
Well, you just never know
when or where a story will break.
Not much of a story here.
Just a bunch of kids cuttin' it loose.
Then what are you doing here?
Just keepin' an eye on things.
I'm gonna check the party out.
Do you mind if I join you?
Not at all.
All right.
Let me just get my coat.
- All right.
- Yeah, I'm fine.
Oh! Yeah.
♪♪ [Rock On Stereo]
How many Evil Deads?
[Boy]
Yeah!
- How many Hellraisers?
- Hellraiser right here.
The Fog, Terror Train, Prom Night.
How come Jamie Lee Curtis
is in all of these movies?
She's the... scream queen.
With a set of lungs
like that, she should be.
- Yeah.
- Tits. See?
[Doorbell Rings]
Oh, I'll get it.
[Woman]
♪ This time, you'll listen ♪
Hey, Tate, grab another beer, would you?
[Rings]
[Boy]
There's beer in the garage.
What am I, the beer wench?
- And she was nominated.
- Oh, yeah?
She was nominated
for Terror Train.
You are not gonna believe who's here!
It's that chick from Top Story.
- Gale Weathers?
- Here. Yeah.
- [Shouting, Chattering]
- Shit!
You're underage, son.
I'm kiddin'. Have a good time.
Watch your driving.
- [Tatum] Dewey?
- Hi.
Dewey?
- What is she doing here?
- She's with me.
- I'm just checkin' things out.
- So you did.
Now leave, and take
your media muff with you.
- I just think you're awesome.
- Oh, thank you very much.
- I watch your show religiously.
- That's great.
- Hey.
- I need a camera.
- [Sighs]
- Did they find my father?
- I'm afraid not.
- [Sidney] Should I be worried?
- [Dewey] Not yet.
♪ Get out, you're walkin'♪
[Boy] That's the one I want—Halloween.
♪ Too bad, I've spoken ♪
[Chattering Continues]
♪ When I look at you♪
♪♪ [Continues, Faint]
[Muttering]
♪ You're forgiven ♪
♪♪ [Continues, Faint]
[Hinges Squeak]
- [Loud Clattering]
- Jesus!
[Yowls]
[Sighs]
Tatum, it's okay.
Shit.
Hey, shitheads!
Hello!
Shit. Piss.
Is that you, Randy?
[Scoffs]
Cute.
And what movie is this from?
I Spit On Your Garage?
Lose the outfit.
If Sidney sees it, she'll flip.
Oh, you wanna play psycho killer?
Can I be the helpless victim?
Okay, let's see—
No, please don't kill me, Mr. Ghost Face.
I wanna be in the sequel!
[Chuckles]
Cut, Casper. That's a wrap.
Randy, what the hell are you doing?
[Yelps, Grunts]
[Screams]
Stop!
[Groans]
Fucker!
[Grunts]
[Grunts, Groans]
[Grunting, Gasping]
[Fabric Tears]
[Gasping, Whimpering]
[Screams]
[Screaming Continues]
No!
[Splatters]
[Hinges Creak]
♪♪ [Continues]
- Happy curfew.
- [Girl] Nice party, Stu.
- Tatum, come on!
- [Girl] Nobody here but us chickens!
- Do you know where she is?
- No, I haven't seen her.
[Shouts]
Oh, Billy. Hey.
♪♪ [Blues Rock On Stereo]
Billy. Hmm. What are you doin' here?
I was hoping I could talk to Sid alone.
You know, if Tatum sees you here,
she'll draw blood.
I'll tell you what. Why don't you guys
go up to my parents' room?
You know, you guys can talk,
whatever.
Subtlety, Stu. You should look it up.
No, it's okay. We do need to talk.
Ooh! Ow.
♪♪ [Continues]
What's Leatherface doin' here?
Cute. He came to make up.
There goes my chance with Sid.
Damn it!
As if.
That's all I'm sayin'. As if.
Oh, really, Alicia?
“As if.”
I'm gonna go check on them.
[Kenny]
Come on!
[Gale] Okay, everyone.
It was nice to meet all of you.
- Thank you.
- Stick around.
[Laughs]
You're a genius.
- Oh, shit.
- What?
- I got a delay.
- [Gale] How long is it?
I don't know. What'd it take you
to walk from the house, 30 seconds?
- It'll be fine. Just record it.
- All right.
Oh, the placement is perfect.
- Tell me, Kenneth—
- Hmm?
Has a cheesy tabloid journalist
ever won the Pulitzer?
Well, first time for everything.
You're damn right.
So, um—
- [Sighs]
- So—
I'm sorry.
I've been selfish,
and I want to apologize.
No, Billy, I'm...
the one who's been selfish
and self-absorbed...
with all this post-traumatic stress.
- You lost your mom.
- Yeah, I know, but you're right.
Enough is enough.
I can't wallow in
the grief process forever, and—
and I can't...
keep lying to myself about who my mom was.
[Sniffles, Sighs]
Yeah, I think I'm really...
scared...
that I'm gonna turn out
just like her, you know?
Like The Bad Seed or somethin'.
And I know it doesn't make sense.
Yeah, it does.
Hmm.
It's like Jodie Foster in
Silence of the Lambs,
when she keeps having
flashbacks of her dead father.
But this is life.
This isn't a movie.
Sure it is, Sid.
It's all— It's all a movie.
It's all...
one great big movie.
Only you can't pick your genre.
Why can't I be a Meg Ryan movie?
Or even a good porno.
What?
You heard me.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
I think so.
[Boy]
Look, look, look. Here it comes.
- Blam!
- Ohh!
The blood is all wrong!
Why do they do that? It's too red!
Wait. Here comes another.
[Muttering]
- Ooh! Ooh!
- Yes! Yes!
Predictable.
I knew he was gonna bite it.
- How can you watch this shit over and over?
- Shh!
When do we see breasts?
I wanna see Jamie Lee's breasts.
- When do we see Jamie Lee's breasts?
- Breasts?
Not until Trading Places in '83.
Jamie Lee was always the virgin
in horror movies.
She never showed her tits
till she went legits.
- Could afford a decent pair.
- What'd you say?
That's why she always outsmarted the killer
in the big chase scene at the end.
Only virgins can do that.
Don't you know the rules?
- What rules?
- You don't—
[TV: Breathing Heavily]
Jesus Christ.
You don't know the rules?
Have an aneurysm, why don't you?
There are certain rules
that one must abide by...
in order to successfully survive
a horror movie.
For instance, number one:
You can never have sex.
[Jeering]
Big no-no! Big no-no!
I'm a dead man.
Sex equals death. Okay?
Number two:
You can never drink or do drugs.
[Shouting, Whooping]
No, the sin factor.
It's a sin.
It's an extension of number one.
And number three: Never, ever, ever,
under any circumstances,
say “I'll be right back,”
'cause you won't be back.
- I'm gettin' another beer. You want one?
- Yeah, sure.
- I'll be right back!
- [Mock Gasping]
[Shouting, Whooping]
You see? You push the laws
and you end up dead.
Okay? I'll see you in the kitchen
with a knife.
Only virgins can outsmart the killer
in the big chase scene at the end.
- Don't you know the rules?
- What rules?
You don't know the rules?
There are certain rules
that one must abide by—
[Groans]
Boring.
[Banging]
The sheriff just radioed.
Somebody reported a car in the bushes
down the road. I'm gonna go check it out.
- Would you care to join me?
- I'd love to.
If you're sure it's all right.
Uh, ma'am, I'm the deputy of this town.
Be right back.
[Monitor On]
[Shouting, Whooping]
You see? You push the laws
and you end up dead.
- Excuse me, ma'am.
- Mm-hmm?
I thought maybe we'd walk.
It's such a nice night out.
I got a flashlight.
You're not scared, are you?
No.
- All right.
- Great.
- Do you know what that constellation is?
- No. What is it?
- I don't know. That's why I was askin' you.
- [Both Laugh]
[Chattering]
- So what happened to Tatum, Stu?
- She probably got pissed at me and bailed.
- [Boy] Bye.
- [Girl] Bye.
[Stu Kisses, Moans]
No, I'm just kidding.
I'm just kidding.
Hey.
Look! Here comes the obligatory tit shot!
- Yes! Oh!
- Lovely!
Beautiful! Oh! Oh.
- Oh, my God.
- I'll leave you guys alone.
You are so...
amazing.
[Ringing]
Hello? Yeah?
Holy shit.
No— Ho—
Listen up.
They found Principal Himbry dead.
He was gutted and hung from the goalpost
on the football field.
So what are we waiting for?
Let's go over there
before they pry him down!
- [Whoops]
- Hey.
- [Boy] To arms! To arms!
- Where you guys—
- Where did he say he was?
- At the football field!
- Come on!
Where you guys goin'?
We were just gettin' to the good part.
Hello? Yeah?
[Shouting, Whooping]
Where you guys—
Whoo!
[Engine Starts]
- Whoo!
- ♪♪ [All Singing “Ride of the Valkyries”]
Hi-ho, Silver! Let's go!
[Owl Hooting]
So, is Dewey your real name?
No, it's Dwight.
Dwight?
- I'm sorry.
- No, that's all right.
Dewey's just somethin' I got stuck
with a long time ago.
Well, I like it.
It's sexy.
- Sexy?
- Mm-hmm.
Ah, it's just this town's way
of not takin' me serious.
What about Gale Weathers?
[Giggles]
Sounds like I'm a meteorologist
or something.
People treat me like I'm the Antichrist
of television journalism.
I don't think you're that bad.
- No?
- No.
[Shouting, Hooting]
I think that's just
'cause you kinda like me.
They sure are comin' fast.
Slow down!
- Freeze! Jump!
- [Gale Screams]
[Groans]
I'm sorry. Are you okay?
Yeah.
I'm sorry. I'm on duty.
[Chuckling]
Is that what you're looking for?
My whole life.
- Damn!
- What?
- What is it?
- This is Neil Prescott's car.
- Sidney's father?
- Yeah.
Jesus. What's he doing here?
We gotta get back.
You okay?
Yeah.
Yeah, I'm fine.
[Chuckles]
Who'd you call?
What?
Well, I don't know—
When you're arrested,
you're allowed one phone call,
so I was just curious— who'd you call?
Called my dad.
No, um, Sheriff Burke called your dad.
I saw him.
Yeah, but when I called
I didn't get an answer.
Huh.
You don't still think it was me, do you?
[Chuckles]
No.
No. I was just thinking if it were you,
it'd be a very clever way
to throw me off track.
You know, using your one phone call
to call me so I wouldn't think it was you.
That's all.
Really?
What do I have to do
to prove to you that I'm not a killer?
- Oh, my God.
- Huh?
Oh, my God.
- Sidney—
- Billy, watch out!
- [Grunts]
- [Screams]
[Groaning]
[Wheezing]
Sid.
[Pounding]
[Groans]
- [Pounding]
- Shit!
Help me, somebody! Help me!
[Gasping, Panting]
[Yelps, Gasps]
Help me!
[Screaming]
[Screams]
[Retches]
No, Jamie. Uh, watch out.
Watch out, Jamie. You know he's around.
You— You know—
Look, there he is. I told you.
I told you he was right around the corner.
Jamie. Jamie.
Jamie, look behind you. Look behind you.
Turn around. Behind you.
Oh, turn— Behind you!
Behind, Jamie.
Jamie, turn around.
Oh, God! Yeah.
Help me! Help!
[Panting]
- [Pounding]
- Let me in!
The killer's coming after me!
He's in the house!
Where? Wait, wait.
- There's a camera in the house. Look.
- Behind you!
- Oh, God. No.
- Oh, shit.
Jamie. Jamie.
- Behind you, kid!
- Randy!
- Behind you!
- Look around!
- Shit.
- What?
- We're on 30-second delay.
- Oh, my God.
[Screams]
[Gasping, Whimpering]
The... door.
[Kenny Groans]
[Body Thuds]
[Screams]
- Is there a phone in the van?
- Yeah.
Lock yourself in it.
Call the sheriff for backup.
Be careful!
[- Grunts]
- [Woman Screaming On TV]
- [Grunts]
- [Whimpering]
- Neil?
- [Whimpering Continues]
[Weeping]
Mr. Prescott?
Shit!
[Screams]
Oh!
[Groaning]
[Clears Throat]
Kenny, I need the cellular!
Kenny!
[Echoing]
[Squishes]
[Beeping, Line Rings]
- [Woman] 9-1-1.
- What's going on?
- [Screaming]
- [Grunting, Groans]
- [Body Thuds]
- [Engine Starts]
Oh, God!
[Whimpering]
[Tires Screeching]
[Screams]
Oh!
[Gasping]
Oh, God. Kenny, I'm sorry,
but get off my fucking windshield!
Stop!
- [Screams]
- [Tires Screeching]
Oh, God!
[Crying]
[Panting]
Dewey!
[Echoing]
Dewey, where are you?
Dewey!
Sidney?
Shit!
[Tapping]
[Jingling]
[Woman On Police Radio]
7825, suspect at 105 North Avenue 52.
Hello. Help me, please.
I'm at Stu Marker's house on Turner Lane.
It's 261 Turner Lane.
Please. He's gonna try and kill me.
- [Yells]
- [Grunting]
[Grunts]
[Randy]
Sidney!
Sidney! Jesus, we've gotta
get the fuck out of here!
Stop right there!
Don't shoot. It's me!
I found Tatum. She's dead!
- I think Stu did it.
- Don't listen to him, Sidney!
- Stay back!
- Stu did it.
- He killed Billy. He killed my Tatum.
- You did it!
- He killed my Tatum!
- No, I didn't!
You lie! Sidney, baby.
Please, give me that gun!
Give me that gun! Christ, man!
No, I didn't. No, I didn't!
Sid, he did it! He did it, Sidney!
Please, I didn't do it.
He did it. Please!
- Please, Sidney. Oh!
- Fuck you both!
- Please!
- No! No! Sidney!
- [Banging]
- Open up!
[Grunts]
Help me! He's going crazy!
- Sidney!
- Go away!
- [Banging]
- Sidney?
[Whispers]
Leave me alone.
[Grunting]
- Sid.
- Billy.
[Groans]
Oh! Billy. Billy. Are you okay?
- I'm okay.
- I thought you were dead.
No. Bleeding like a stuck pig,
but I'm all right.
Get up.
- I'm okay.
- You're bleeding.
- Oh, my God.
- We've gotta get help.
No, he's out there!
No, give me the gun.
Give me the gun. It's okay.
It's okay. It's okay.
Careful.
- Please help me!
- Whoa, whoa. Come here, come here!
Stu's flipped out! He's gone mad!
We all go a little mad sometimes.
- No, Billy!
- Oh, fuck!
[Screams]
- [Moans]
- [Sobs]
Anthony Perkins, Psycho.
[Panting]
Mmm.
Corn syrup. Same stuff they used for
pig's blood in Carrie.
No.
[Gasps]
Stu.
Help me, please.
[Male Voice]
Surprise, Sidney.
- No!
- [Stu] Ooh!
Oh, now. Whoa.
[Male Voice] What's the matter, Sidney?
You look like you've seen a ghost.
[Gasps]
Why are you doing this?
It's all part of the game, Sidney.
- It's called “Guess How I'm Gonna Die.”
- Fuck you!
No, no, no, no, no.
We already played that game, remember?
- You lost.
- It's a fun game, Sidney.
See, we ask you a question,
and if you get it wrong,
bookah— you die!
You get it right, you die.
You're crazy, both of you.
Actually, we prefer the term “psychotic.”
You'll never get away with this.
Oh, no?
Tell that to Cotton Weary.
You wouldn't believe
how easy he was to frame.
Watch a few movies, take a few notes.
- It was fun.
- No!
- Whoa!
- Where you goin'?
[Sobbing]
Why?
- [Slaps Counter]
- Why did you kill my mother?
Why?
[Shouts] Why?
You hear that, Stu?
I think she wants a motive.
[Chuckling]
I don't really believe in motive, Sid.
I mean, did Norman Bates have a motive?
No.
Did they ever really decide why Hannibal
Lecter liked to eat people? Don't think so!
See, it's a lot scarier
when there's no motive, Sid.
We did your mom a favor, Sid.
That woman was a slut-bag whore...
who flashed her shit all over town
like she was Sharon Stone.
[Stu] Yeah, we put her out of her misery,
'cause let's face it, Sidney,
your mother was no Sharon Stone, huh?
Is that motive enough for you?
Well, how 'bout this?
Your slut mother was fucking my father,
and she's the reason
my mom moved out and abandoned me.
How's that for a motive?
Maternal abandonment
causes serious deviant behavior.
Certainly fucked you up.
It made you have sex with a psychopath.
That's right. You gave it up.
Now you're no longer a virgin.
[Giggles]
I said “virgin.” Whoops!
Now you gotta die. Those are the rules.
Just pretend it's all a scary movie, Sid.
How do you think it's gonna end?
Oh! Oh! This is the greatest part!
You're gonna love this.
We got a surprise for you, Sidney.
Yeah, you're gonna love this one.
It's a scream, baby!
Hold on a sec. I'll be right back.
[Mock Scream]
You know what time it is, Sid?
It's after midnight.
It's your mom's anniversary.
Congratulations.
We killed her exactly one year ago today.
Attention! Oh!
What do we have behind
door number three, Sidney?
- Daddy!
- Whoa, hold it.
That's enough.
[Male Voice] Guess we won't be
needing this anymore.
And, oh, look at this.
Ring, ring. Won't need this.
Got the ending figured out yet, Sid?
Come on, Sidney.
You think about it now, huh?
Your daddy's the chief suspect.
We cloned his cellular.
Evidence is all right there, baby!
What if your father snapped?
Your mother's anniversary set him off,
and he went on a murder spree,
killing everyone.
Except for Billy and me.
We were left for dead.
Then he... kills you...
and shoots himself in the head.
- Perfect ending.
- I thought of that.
Watch this.
- Ready?
- Yeah.
Yeah! I'm ready, baby!
Hit it! Get up!
Yeah, babe, get up! Hit it!
- [Groans]
- [Gasps]
Good one, man. Jesus.
Oh, shit. My turn.
Don't forget.
Stay to the side and don't go too deep.
Okay. I'll remember.
[Screams]
Fuck! Fuck!
Fuck! Goddamn it, Stu!
Sorry, Billy.
I guess I got a little too zealous, huh?
- Give me the knife.
- No.
Give me the knife!
Now!
You see, Sid, everybody dies but us.
Everybody dies but us.
We get to carry on and plan the sequel,
'cause let's face it, baby,
these days you gotta have a sequel!
[Stabbing]
[Stu Groaning]
You sick fucks.
You've seen one too many movies.
Now, Sid, don't you blame the movies.
Movies don't create psychos.
Movies make psychos more creative!
[Yelps]
Stop it, Billy, would you? All right?
I can't take anymore.
I'm feeling a little woozy here!
All right. All right, you get the gun.
And I'll untie Pops, okay?
[Dripping]
- Now!
- Okay.
- [Dripping Continues]
- [Exhales]
Um. Uh—
Houston, we have a problem here.
- What?
- The gun, man. The gun.
I put it right there, and it's not there.
Where the fuck is it?
[Hammer Cocks]
Right here, asshole.
- Excuse me. I thought she was dead.
- She looked dead, man. Still does.
I've got an ending for you.
The reporter left for dead
in the news van...
comes to,
stumbles on you two dipshits,
finds the gun,
foils your plan and saves the day.
I like that ending.
I know something you don't.
Fuck. No!
[Grunts]
Yeah, man.
Yeah. Aw, so sweet.
Works better
without the safety on.
[Neck Bones Crack]
[Panting]
This is Gale Weathers, signing off.
Baby, you're gonna love this!
Shit.
What?
Where are they?
[Coughs]
I don't know, but I'm hurtin', man.
[Phone Ringing]
Fuck!
Should I let the machine get it?
[Ringing Continues]
- Hello?
- [Male Voice] Are you alone in the house?
Bitch! You bitch! Where the fuck are you?
Not so fast. We're gonna play
a little game. It's called—
[Sidney] “Guess who just called the police
and reported your sorry motherfucking ass. ”
Find her, you dipshit! Get up!
I can't, Billy. You cut me too deep.
I think I'm dying here, man.
[Weeping]
Talk to her. Talk to her.
Hello?
Oh, Stu, Stu, Stu.
What's your motive?
Billy's got one.
The police are on their way.
What are you gonna tell them?
Peer pressure. I'm far too sensitive.
I'm gonna rip you up,
you bitch, just like your fucking mother!
You've gotta find me first,
you pansy-assed mama's boy!
Fuck!
Ow. You fuckin' hit me
with the phone, dick!
Fucker, where are you?
[Yelling]
[Fabric Tearing]
- You fuck! [Roars]
- [Crashing]
Did you really call the police?
You bet your sorry ass I did.
My mom and dad
are gonna be so mad at me.
[Yells]
Bitch!
[Whimpering]
[Clattering]
[Whimpering, Screaming]
[Whimpering]
[Groans]
[Yelps]
[Pistol Clatters]
[Screaming]
- [Grunts]
- [Groans]
Oh! My arm!
- [Yelling]
- [Grunts]
I always had a thing for you, Sid!
[Screams]
Bitch.
In your dreams.
[Screams]
[Yelping]
[Groans]
- [Gasps]
- I'm sorry. It's all right.
Oh, my God, Randy,
I thought you were dead.
I probably should be. I never thought
I'd be so happy to be a virgin.
- [Gasps]
- Fucker!
[Grunting]
- [Gasps]
- Say hello to your mother.
[Screaming]
[Yelps, Groans]
[Coughing]
[Panting]
[Randy Groans]
[Sidney Gasps]
[Randy Groaning]
- Come on.
- [Whimpers]
It's okay.
Guess I remembered the safety that time,
you bastard.
Careful.
This is the moment when the supposedly
dead killer comes back to life...
for one last scare.
- [Grunts]
- [Screams]
Not in my movie.
[Crash]
[Screaming]
[Muffled Grunting]
[Exhales]
Dad.
Randy, help me out.
- Ah. Ah.
- You okay?
[Sidney]
I'm sorry. Sorry, sorry, sorry.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
- Hang in there, buddy.
- All right.
- Over here.
- Sorry, kid.
Okay, I think it's gonna go something
like this. Just stay with me.
[Siren Wailing]
Hi, this is Gale Weathers...
with an exclusive eyewitness account
of this amazing breaking story.
Several more local teens are dead,
bringing to an end the harrowing mystery
of the mass killing...
that has terrified this peaceful community
like the plot of some scary movie.
It all began with a scream over 9-1-1...
and ended in a bloodbath
that has rocked the town of Woodsboro,
all played out here
in this peaceful farmhouse,
far from the crimes and the sirens of the
larger cities that its residents had fled.
Okay, let's take it back to one.
Come on, move it.
This is my big shot. Let's go.
[Thunderclap]
[Thunder Rumbling]
♪♪ [Pop]
[Woman] ♪ Love comes down upon us
and it flows like water♪
♪ Burning with the hope of insight♪
♪ Feathered books,
the colors of a bright elation ♪
♪ Stolen in the sight of love ♪
♪ We are, we are, we are,
we're just children ♪
♪ Fighting our way around indecision ♪
♪ We are, we are, we are rather helpless♪
♪ Change is forever
A whisper to a scream ♪
♪ Birds fly in the eye
of the faithless daughter♪
♪ Spoken at the bitter end♪
♪ Wasted, sacrificed for the new nirvana ♪
♪ Nighttime sends the sun away♪
♪ We are, we are, we are,
we're just children ♪
♪ Fighting our way around indecision ♪
♪ We are, we are, we are rather helpless♪
♪ Change is forever
A whisper to a scream ♪
♪ A whisper to a scream ♪
♪ Whisper to a scream ♪
♪ We are, we are, we are,
we're just children ♪
♪ Fighting our way around indecision ♪
♪ We are, we are, we are rather helpless♪
♪ Change is forever
A whisper to a scream ♪
♪ Whisper to a scream ♪
♪ A whisper to a scream ♪
♪♪ [Fades]
♪♪ [Rock]
[Man] ♪ Look outside of my window ♪
♪ But all I see is the rain come down ♪
♪ A pink umbrella and a bit of her leg♪
♪ Is all I need and I'll come, come ♪
♪ I don't care if you don't care ♪
♪ The world looks just fine to me ♪
♪ Don't be shy and I'll show you, baby♪
♪ What's it like to be free ♪
♪ I don't care if you don't care ♪
♪ The world looks just fine to me ♪
♪ Don't be shy and I'll show you, baby♪
♪ What it's like to be free ♪
♪ I♪
♪ I don't care if you don't care ♪
♪ The world looks just fine to me ♪
♪ Don't be shy and I'll show you, baby♪
♪ What it's like to be free ♪
♪ Don't be shy♪
♪ Told you, baby♪
♪♪ [Ends]
Please rate this subtitle at www.osdb.link/7rhx3
Help other users to choose the best subtitles