They'll be playing
at the Hollywood Bowl
tonight, all sold out,
but we'll be giving away six more tickets
on this beautiful Saturday morning.
75 degrees in Hollywood.
You've been listening
to one hour of nonstop
power rock 'n roll, on Holly Power 92
and there's more.
- At the top of the hour,
here in the Valley,
it's a balmy 83 degrees.
Gotta go, but first, here's
the story of my life.
J‘ They got a word for girls like me I
J‘ They got a name but
they don't wanna use it I
J‘ It's all the same for girls like me J‘
J‘ It's all or nothin' to girls like me J‘
I I'm gonna jump J‘
J‘ I'm goin' to shout J‘
J” I'm goin' to make it
with them bad boys I
J‘ Shake it with the bad boy's gals J‘
J‘ I'm gonna do just what I wanna J‘
I I'm goin' to drive to Tijuana J‘
J‘ I got your number, I got your name I
J‘ I was like, yeah yeah yeah yeah J‘
J‘ They've got a line for girls like me J‘
J” They draw the line
and kids get behind it J‘
J” They're gonna line
up for girls like me I
J‘ They're doin' time for girls like me J‘
I I'm gonna twist J‘
I I'm goin' to skate J‘
I I'm gonna kill my wild J‘
I I'm gonna kill my everyday J‘
I I'm gonna dance until I drop I
J‘ Get the world come to a stop I
J‘ I got your number, I got your name I
J‘ I was like, yeah yeah yeah yeah J‘
J‘OohJ‘
J‘ Girls like me I
J‘ Girls, girls I
J‘AhJ‘
I Like me I
J‘ Ooh, ooh yeah J‘
J‘ It's in the bag for girls like me J‘
J‘ They all want the girl
with the right information J‘
J‘ They got a line up for girls like me J‘
J‘ The right type of boy
in a tight situation J‘
J‘ Wants a girl J‘
J‘ All of the J‘
J‘ Like me J‘
J‘ Girls like me J‘
J‘ All of the girls like me J‘
J‘ Girl J‘
J‘ Like me J‘
J‘ All of the J‘
J‘ Girls like me J‘
J‘ Girls J‘
J‘ All of the J‘
J‘ Girls like me J‘
J‘ Like me, uh-huh J‘
J‘ All of the J‘
J‘ Girls like me J‘
J‘ Girls J‘
J‘ All of the J‘
J‘ Girls like me J‘
J‘ Like me, yeah J‘
J‘ It's in the bag J‘
J‘ All of the J‘
J‘ Girls like me J‘
J‘ I got your number J‘
J‘ I got your name J‘
J‘ All of the J‘
J‘ Girls like me J‘
J‘ I got your number J‘
J‘ All of the J‘
J‘ Girls like me J‘
J‘ Say the girls like me J‘
J‘ Say girls like me J‘
J‘ Girls like me J‘
I don't wanna,
like, start a family.
Like, my God, I'd get
all puffed out to the max
and all, for sure!
- Please, look at you.
- Barf out.
God, gag me.
How could you?
For sure.
- I'd be freaking out.
- Like, I'd be scarfing
up everything in sight.
I'm sure, I don't know.
Ya know like, oh, I'd get so fat and all,
and what'd happen to my zits?
They can get so grody.
And besides, it's totally
gnarly birth control.
Like, he's not so awesome.
- Awesome's not the word for Brad.
Oh, I'm sure.
- He's okay, I guess.
Who am I kidding?
- Yeah, only, you know,
he makes my mouth water.
- Brad'll be at my party tonight.
- Great, that'll, like, attract every girl
west of Van Nuys Boulevard.
Your place will be packed.
Okay, so he's awesome.
- God, Julie, like, don't be so greedy.
Ya know, save some for the rest of us.
I mean, Tommy is such a
hunk I can't stand it.
I mean, he is so bitchin'.
I can't even believe you'd
give Brad the time of day.
- Yeah, but Tommy can
be such a dork, ya know?
Like, he's got the bod, but
his brains are bad news.
- But he is bitchin'.
You really are so lucky, Julie.
I know, but we've been
goin' together so long now.
Like, I'm beginning to think I'm a piece
of furniture or something,
like an old chair.
- He sounds like bad news.
I definitely need something new.
Bags off at home
and hit the beach, okay?
- God, okay.
- Yeah, let's do that.
All right, that sounds good.
- Julie, like--
God, I hate
these escalators.
- You guys.
- Hm?
We won't have time
to get ready for my party.
Yes, we will.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
- What a surprise findin' you here.
- Well where should I be,
at home waiting for the phone to ring?
I could grow old and prune up
waiting for that to happen.
- Funny.
What's your problem?
- What's my problem?
Try two days and no phone calls.
Look, I'll see you guys at the bus, okay?
Mm, okay.
- Okay, come on.
- Act like a lady.
- It's like I'm totally not in
love with you anymore, Tommy.
I mean, it's so boring.
Here.
- Not too cool, Julie.
Like, I won't be bummed out.
Like, who else is there?
No other Val dude can touch me.
I mean, she must be really freakin' out.
- I want a corn dog.
- I want a pizza.
- Corn dog!
- Diet Pepsi with french fries.
- Those are so fattening,
Julie
- I don't care
about fat!
- I'm sure, come on, Stacey.
- Diet Pepsi's diet.
- Oh, It'll be a great party night.
Everyone'll be there.
Pass on cotillion just this once, okay?
My mother would kill me if she found out
I'd skipped out on it.
- Look, this is the social
event of the season.
Don't be dull.
- Where does she live?
- 23727 Sierra Vista.
I got it!
- For sure. Move.
Ya know, like, the best guys
will be there and everything.
It'll be totally hot.
- That guy is so cute!
He is.
- Look at him!
- He smiled.
- Oh, you guys.
- His hair.
Oh boy.
- Guys, look how hairy
that guy's back is.
- Eww, gross!
- Gross!
- Totally.
- The guy has fur
all over his face, too.
Ew!
My God!
What a hunk.
Oh yeah.
- Check out those pecs!
- Oh, I'd go for that
in a minute, for sure.
- He's hot!
- Oh yeah, he's my kind of guy.
- Aren't they all?
- Well, most of 'em are.
Hey, they didn't have corn
dogs, so I got, like--
Ew, I hate these!
- Hey, man, 23727 Sierra Vista.
It's a party, it is gonna be amazing.
I've seen the chicks.
I know about these things
and I got a feelin' about this one.
It is gonna be hot, I'm tellin' you.
And it's in the Valley.
- What?
- I'm not sure
if he's funny.
- The party's in the Valley.
- I don't wanna go to the Valley.
- Trust me.
You'll wanna.
- I don't wanna
go to the Valley.
- Trust me.
- I'm not in the mood to go the Valley.
- Come on, Julie.
You know Loryn won't
let her mom wait for us.
She'll wanna pounce on
the first available bod.
God.
Hey, do you think she
does everything she says?
- I don't know.
She's gonna get in a
lot of trouble, though,
if she doesn't watch out.
- You know, like, I think she does.
I mean, who could make up,
"That stuff tastes like Clorox."
Eww.
- God, gross me out!
I don't know, I think
she's lonely, ya know?
- When does she have the time?
- Well, she's got, like, problems.
- Yeah, hormones I guess.
No, that's
when you grow a mustache.
Oh puke!
God!
- I don't know,
I think it's up to us to, like,
look out for her, ya know?
She is our friend.
She'd do the same thing for us.
- Yeah, I guess.
Okay.
- God, hold still.
- God, what am I gonna do?
Tommy's gonna be there.
You know how he is.
God, he's not gonna
appreciate me talking to Brad.
- Get real, Julie.
You're not gonna go
through with this, are you?
- I'm so sure!
God, Brad's totally hot.
I think he's totally not.
- God, I'm so nervous.
- Okay, let's go!
- All right, we're taking off now, guys.
- Don't you two look great!
- Oh, Stacey, if I were
20 years younger, honey.
- God, Dad!
- Hey, Julie.
- I won't be too late, I'm sure.
- Well, we don't wanna pressure you, dear.
- Just let us hear from
you by next Tuesday,
okay, honeybunch?
- Well, like, I'm not
going away on a peace march
or something heavy like that, Pop.
- Hey, I can dig the scene, no sweat.
- Like, I have to be home by one.
- Well, we try to give Julie
all the space she needs here.
I know, Mom.
- Bye.
- Let's go.
- Have a good time.
Bye!
- Bye!
Bye-bye.
- Have a good time.
- Bye-bye,
have a good time!
Shoo.
Sarah, do you know how
much she looks like you?
I mean, you were just
her age when I met you.
- Do I still look that way?
- You look better.
- But things were sure a lot wilder then.
- Yeah.
Different priorities, that's all.
Sex, drugs, and rock 'n roll.
- Okay, I'll tell you what.
You spend the night at my house.
We'll get his mother's car.
- Sounds good.
J‘ Can ya see things J‘
- Forget about her, Tommy.
Don't worry about it.
J‘ You've got to stall to move J‘
- Skip it.
J‘ Got to hang on J‘
J‘ We've got some Dramamine J‘
- Brad?
Brad!
Hi, Brad.
Great party, huh?
- It's all right.
- Do ya like the music?
It's okay.
- Have you tried the sushi yet?
- No, I haven't made it in there.
- Like, it's not gonna be easy, ya know.
Anytime you wanna come back,
hey, you just let me know.
I'll think about it.
- Tommy, I told you to forget it.
- You'll be back.
- Yeah, right.
- She can't live without me.
He's like totally awesome!
- Who, dear?
- Skip!
- Mom, you're not listening to me.
Skip's, like, a really nice
guy and I want him to like me
so, like, I just wanna make sure...
- Is there something that I shouldn't know
that I should know?
- Of course there is, darling.
J‘ You've got legs J‘
J‘ Dance J‘
- You're right, he is cute.
- I was hoping you'd come.
- Oh, yeah?
- Yeah.
- What about that one?
- He dresses like a dork.
- Yeah, but he's cute.
- How can you love a dork?
- Well?
- Uh-oh.
Don't look now.
Guess who?
Gnarly party, man.
- Yeah.
- Oh, hello.
- Goodbye.
God, he's such a total pukeoid.
- He's just, like, really
bitchin', you'll see.
- Honey, why don't you take this out now?
The guests are waiting
for some food, go on.
- What was that all about?
- Well I am only her
stepmother, and since Jim died
she's been kind of competitive with me.
Hm.
Okay.
Okay, now dancers.
Gnarly party, man.
- Yeah.
- Hey!
Ow!
J‘ So I saw you in the pizza place J‘
J‘ You were with another girl J‘
J‘ It was a crime J‘
- Drink lime?
- Oh!
Freak me out, freak me out, it's him.
- Who?
- The guy with the brown hair.
J‘ Cheap cologne J‘
Hi, Skip.
Skip.
- Oh.
I wouldn't eat it.
- Don't be so obvious with boys.
J‘ I don't wanna get that number J‘
- Hi, Skip.
- Hi, Suzi.
- I'd like you to meet my mother.
- Oh hi, Mrs. Brent.
Nice to meet you.
- Call me Beth.
- Skip.
Lyle.
- How do you do?
I know,
yeah, like to eat--
- Oh honey, the phone's ringing.
- Come on, Skip, let's go dance.
Like totally gag.
- Look at who Tommy's with.
- Who cares?
- Come on.
- Like, he's totally juvenile, Stacey.
J‘ Don't put another dime in the jukebox J‘
J‘ 'Cause I don't wanna
hear that song no more J‘
- Whoa oh, oh, oh.
Hi, Tommy.
- Is it?
Yes, it is.
What?
- The most beautiful girl in the world.
- What's the matter with you, dude?
- I think I'm fallin' in love.
Come on, what about Julie?
- Aw, that's a real tragedy.
Dumped.
Jilted.
Right in the toilet.
My heart's broken.
- I'm sure you gotta be drunk.
- That's what I've
always enjoyed about you.
You're perceptive.
You know how to read a guy.
I need help.
- Oh yeah?
- Yeah.
I was wondering if you'd
step into my office?
- Tommy.
- Promise it'll be--
Come on.
No, no, no.
- Don't worry about it.
- Tommy.
Oh, Jesus.
Wait, I got a great idea.
Mm.
Hi.
Let's do it.
- Uh.
Okay, smart guy.
We're here, now what?
- Mingle, blend in.
J‘ Yeah J‘
- Right.
J‘ The fanatic J‘
J‘ I am the fanatic J‘
J‘ I like-a movies and the rock shows J‘
J‘ Rock stars and the radios J‘
J‘ I am the fanatic J‘
J‘ Can I have your autograph J‘
- Can I pick 'em or what?
Check it out.
- Why don't you lower it?
You don't need to raise
up a flag or nothin'.
- Just lookin' for action.
J‘ Limo chasin' is my thing J‘
- Hey, let's check out the eats.
J‘ TV Guide, magazines J‘
J‘ Video, tape machines J‘
- What do we got goin' here, a bait shop?
- Well, like, it's sushi, don't ya know?
Like, this is tuna,
this is flying fish eggs,
and that's sea urchin.
- This is pistachio paste, isn't it?
- Oh.
It's weird, I mean.
I wouldn't eat it.
Yeah, I wouldn't eat it.
A real party.
- Come on, Fred, dig in.
- I think I'll just
get somethin' to drink.
- Wait, Tommy.
Tommy, this is, like, not right.
- How can this not be right?
- 'Cause what about Julie, huh?
- That's over.
She tossed me out.
Don't penalize me for what she did.
I'm the one that got hurt.
I am.
Aww.
- I've always thought about you.
- You have?
- Yeah.
I thought about you all day.
- Hey, you wanna dance?
- In another life.
- Yeah, I didn't either.
I was just takin' a poll.
- Ah, Fred, I didn't
know you were this good.
- Well at least I'm tryin'.
- Boy, is this, points for effort?
I told ya this place was gonna be a waste.
J‘ Know how hard it is to say, say hello J‘
- Yeah, this place sucks.
Well, well.
- What?
J‘ You've got the eyes of a stranger J‘
- Hot, very hot.
- Yeah, which one?
- Like, they're staring right at us.
- Gross, let's move.
Keep talkin'.
- Wait, let's see what happens.
- I'm sure, tell me all about it.
I think I'm gonna talk to the raw fish.
Bad luck,
Fred, yours is leaving.
- Hey, what do you mean mine's leaving?
She winked at you, didn't she?
- She did?
- Yeah, don't let her get away.
J‘ When you walked in the room J‘
Oh.
J‘ Felt my heart race J‘
J‘ My mood improved J‘
- Hello.
J‘ Looked at your face J‘
- Having a good time?
- I'm trying.
- It's really good.
- That's really good, yeah.
- That's good.
- What are you doing here?
- Well it's a party.
- Yeah, I know it's a
party, but who invited you?
- Oh wow, you mean you have to be invited?
That explains it.
- What?
- Why everyone is dressed so weird.
See, if I had been invited,
I woulda known this was a costume party.
Right.
J‘ Eyes of a stranger J‘
- I saw you once before, you know.
- Where?
- At the beach.
- That was you?
- Do you think a girl should
pet on the first date?
- Who are you, Bozo the Clown?
- What's your Sign?
- Tommy, is this gonna mean
we're, like, goin' together?
What?
- Is this gonna mean we're goin' together?
- No.
- Um, what?
- Well, I think it means, like,
you're a pretty lousy friend
messin' around with
your friend's boyfriend
while he's in a bad way.
But I'll tell ya what.
- What?
- I won't tell anybody if you don't.
J‘ Of a stranger J‘
J‘ You've got the eyes of a stranger J‘
- Get out.
J‘ Eyes of a stranger J‘
J‘OyJ‘
- No, I never said that, but--
- Oh, that wasn't you.
- You know, after football,
football.
- I'm sorry.
- Stop it.
- Football,
I'm not playin' this year.
- That was Rick.
- Rick, who's Rick?
Had somethin' to do with it.
- How ya doin', Tommy?
- Loryn, man.
- Is she good?
- Loryn, really?
I mean, really?
Supports take ya.
J‘Oh noJ‘
J‘ We're gonna rock down
to Electric Avenue J‘
- So, how's your mother?
- She's dead.
J‘ Oh, we're gonna rock
down to Electric Avenue J‘
J‘ And then we'll take it higher J‘
- Julie, remember we...
This is the Hollywood River.
- And no you can't.
- No.
- And the wind blows it up.
No, I...
Get outta my house.
- Why don't you get outta here?
- You make me get outta here.
Yeah, and the craziest words.
Get up!
Get up.
What are you doing?
- You have nothin', faggot!
- Tommy, Tommy, now stop it!
- Cool it, cool it, pal.
Fuck you!
Get the hell outta here!
J‘Oh noJ‘
Now, I don't wanna hurt you guys.
- You get outta here
you stupid shit.
- Fuck you!
J‘ Down to Electric Avenue J‘
Jerk.
And kiss my ass!
J‘ Oh we're gonna rock down J‘
- You're good, man.
Fuckin' Fred, what are you doin' in there,
kissin' girls goodnight?
- Hey Listen.
- Don't!
- I won't.
- Good.
J‘ Who is to blame in one country J‘
J‘ Never can get to the one J‘
J‘ Dealin' in multiplication J‘
- That chick Julie, she's truly dazzling.
J‘ We're gonna rock down
to Electric Avenue J‘
- Yup, but she's not one of ours.
J‘ Oh no, we're gonna rock
down to Electric Avenue J‘
J‘OhJ‘
J‘ Out in the street J‘
Oh.
Hey, what the hell?
Hey dickhead, what are you
tryin' to do, get us killed?
What the hell is the matter with you?
Hey shit, that's my mother's car!
- Who the fuck was that guy, huh?
I mean, I was doin' all
right with that chick.
Who the fuck does he think he is?
Maybe it was her boyfriend.
- Nobody is gonna tell
me who I can score with!
I want this chick, she wants me,
so fuck it, we're goin' back.
Hey!
My mom would shit if she knew
you were drivin' this car.
I really don't give a shit
what your mother thinks.
J‘ Shelly, look J‘
J‘ You got a boyfriend J‘
J‘ Don't let your boyfriend put ya down J‘
J‘ Shelly J‘
J‘ Ya know he's just a boy J‘
J‘ Keep lookin' 'til you're found J‘
J‘ Yeah, yeah J‘
- It's bad enough you got a beating.
It'd be far worse if I
got the same treatment.
Hey come on, wait a second, man.
What are we doin' here?
I don't have a death wish!
J‘ It was not all that they led
you to believe it would be J‘
J‘ So ya headed back down
to the black and white J‘
- They're cute, aren't they?
- Yeah, so swell.
J‘ Who can it be knockin' at my door? J‘
J‘ Go away J‘
J‘ Don't come round here no more J‘
J‘ Can't you see that it's late at night? J‘
J‘ I'm very tired J‘
J‘ And I'm not feelin' right J‘
J‘ All I wish is to be alone J‘
J‘ Stay away J‘
J‘ Don't you invade my home J‘
J‘ Best off if you hang outside J‘
J‘ Don't come in J‘
J‘ I'll only run and hide J‘
J‘ Who can it be now? J‘
What if somebody comes?
Don't worry about it.
J‘ Who can it be now? J‘
Somebody could come in.
I told you!
Hurry up in there!
Don't worry
about it, they can wait.
Come on, man, I gotta go.
- Take a hike!
- Doug.
- Come here.
- Don't.
Okay, you lose out.
I'm sure.
Come on.
- Come on, hurry up.
- Hurry up in there.
I'm hurrying.
Meet me later?
Unh-unh.
- Will ya?
J‘ There's nothin' wrong J‘
Creep.
Thanks a lot, man.
J‘ I like it here with
my childhood friend J‘
J‘ Here they come J‘
J‘ Those feelings again J‘
J‘ Who can it be now? J‘
I can't believe he did that.
- I can.
I can't.
But guess who's looking at you?
J‘ Who can it be now? J‘
So I said, "Oh, my God,
"I just can't touch that thing."
Oh, God, it looked so...
- So, so what?
Tell me.
- Awesome.
Look, it's like Shaking hands
with your best friend.
Only, like, real fast.
Come on, let's go.
God, like, how
many is it we've had?
You gettin' high?
Good golly,
Where did you get that?
I'm makin' some
lines here for you.
- Oh, wow!
Oh, how is it?
Is it okay?
- Here, it's good.
God, Doug, you're
gonna lose your nose, look out.
J‘ Who can it be now? J‘
J‘OhohohJ‘
J‘ Oh yeah J‘
J‘ Who can it, who can it? J‘
J‘ There's an army on the dance floor J‘
J‘ It's a fashion J‘
- Don't be afraid.
- What are you doing here?
Do you have a death wish or something?
- That's what Fred said.
- Fred said?
- Never mind.
You live around here?
Like, this is very strange.
- What are you doing back here?
- I forgot my comb.
- Really, now?
- Well, to tell you the truth,
I kinda thought that
maybe you and I could...
- We could what?
- We could get outta here.
Like, I don't
think you'd be any more welcome
down there, right now.
- I mean let's leave the party.
I'm so sure.
- Cool.
I'll meet you out front.
- Wait a minute, where are we gonna go?
J‘ Steal us all and take us all J‘
- I don't care.
J‘ But not in J‘
- What are we gonna do?
- Anything.
J‘ Love my way J‘
J‘ It's a new J‘
- Okay, but I have to
bring my best friend.
- That's fine.
J‘ I follow J‘
- I'll be waiting for you.
J‘ Where my mind goes J‘
J‘ Love my way J‘
J‘ It's a new road J‘
J‘ I follow where my mind goes J‘
God, Julie.
I don't wanna go, I told you.
- It's gonna be fun.
- It is not gonna be fun.
- I don't know
- Where are they?
- Where they're taking us,
- They're not even here.
- But it'll be okay.
- I don't, let's go back.
- No!
- God, Julie.
- I know they're around here.
- Where?
- Sh.
- Right there.
- Hey, come here.
- Oh, no, not those guys.
- Yes.
- They're hoods, juvenile delinquents.
- No.
- You've lost your mind.
- Look at them.
- Well, their reading skill is okay.
- I am freaking out.
- Do this for me.
Do this for me.
- No.
- Come on.
- Julie!
- Hi, I'm Fred.
I like tacos and '71 cabernet
and my favorite color is magenta.
- Hi.
I'm Julie, and this is Stacey.
- Charmed, I'm sure.
- I am simply gonna freak out and die!
Would you get in the car?
- God!
I will pay whatever it takes to make sure
nobody breathes a word of this.
Like, I'll be totally bummed out
if anyone on Earth, outside
this car finds out about this.
God, where is
your sense of adventure?
Will you shut up?
- I personally guarantee you
you will have the time
of your life tonight.
You'll see things that you've
only read about in books.
- Oh I'm sure.
I'm freezing!
Could you put the top up, Randy?
- I hope you don't mind if I change it.
- This is the last time
I take you anywhere.
- I'm sure.
Oh God.
- I like this song.
- I hate this song.
I hate this music.
J‘ What if I tell ya
that I love you, baby J‘
J‘ Don't ya know that I'm
talkin' from the bottom J‘
J‘ Of my heart J‘
J‘ Uh-huh, uh-huh, uh-huh J‘
J‘ I could never find another J‘
- Look.
- Ha ha!
No way, Bob!
J‘ I l-l-l-love you J‘
J‘OhohohJ‘
J‘ Ooh you make me wanna move all over J‘
J‘ Oh, make a little room
for you in my heart J‘
J‘ Uh-huh, uh-huh, uh-huh J‘
J‘ Gave me lovin' that was worth a gamble J‘
J‘ Oh, we made a song together J‘
J‘ From the very stars J‘
J‘ Like I know your heart J‘
- Sweet cheeks and velvet thighs.
- Hey, Harvey!
Harvey!
I thought you were gonna get the mohawk!
Nah, I pussed out.
J‘ I la-la-la-la J‘
- I like this song.
- God.
Hey, hey, Randy.
Man, where'd you get
that set of wheels, baby?
- Woo!
- Ow!
Ah, lookin' nasty.
- Hey, Rico!
- What, hey, we good?
- No way, man!
You didn't do that!
I'll talk to you later!
Ha ha ha!
J‘IJ‘
- Julie.
God.
- Fuck!
What's doin'?
- Ain't that roll, baby.
Check out the cool wheels you got.
- Sid.
- Sid Vicious lives.
- Like, I'm not gettin' out of this car.
- All right, but when they
attack the car save the radio.
- Julie.
- Oh yeah.
- Hey, baby,
why don't you get rid of the
lugs and we can meet later?
- Oh yeah?
- Beats me.
Baby, why
don't you try it my way?
- Julie, I don't wanna go in here.
Julie.
- Hey, how are ya?
- Good.
- Look at this.
- Let's do it.
- Like the girls.
- God, Julie!
- Lovely.
- Brewster!
- Hey!
Randy baby.
- Let's do it.
- Hey no drugs, guns, or alcohol.
- How's it goin', man?
- Woo!
Good to see ya, man.
Come on in.
- Okay, no guns or drugs
or alcohol?
- What's he doing?
Julie!
Aww, come on.
J‘ Across the way J‘
J‘ You're beginnin' to drum again J‘
J‘ Thunderstruck, all
caught up in the Sky J‘
You two, come on.
Hey!
Hey man, you need to order that pizza.
J‘ You're what I want J‘
J‘ The rich are fallin' J‘
J‘ So we took a chance J‘
Hey, Sean, so
what's your salami like?
Ha ha!
J‘ The music is callin' J‘
- Woohoo hoo hoo.
- Is this your hangout?
- This is my home away from home.
Do you wanna sit down?
- Yeah.
- Ow.
Hey, you guys
want somethin' to drink?
I got some friends
who wanna sit here, so let's go, huh?
You guys have fun.
- Ew, I don't even wanna
know what's on this seat.
God.
J‘ Somethin' struck a chord up in the sky J‘
J‘ And lightnin' flashed and
looked right into us, oh J‘
- Where do you live?
- Hollywood.
I go to Hollywood High.
- Me too.
- Oh, my God, like,
don't you have a straw?
Totally out of touch with civilization.
Go home!
- This is what we call living on the edge.
- You don't have places like
this in the Valley, do you?
- No, we're just not into...
- Slumming it.
- So what do you do over there that's hot?
- We go to normal parties.
Go to normal places.
We buy nice, new clothes.
J‘ We ran all the way, you could hear the J‘
- That's no different from what we do.
- It's the way we do things
that makes the difference.
- Yeah, I guess so.
J‘ We're animals J‘
J‘ Until then we're open J‘
J‘ And ya can't look back J‘
J‘ Tear the chains up, they're broken J‘
- You know, like, these guys
all look sick, or somethin'.
You'd all look healthier with a tan.
- You won't catch anything here.
This is the real world.
It's not fresh and clean
like a television show.
- I always thought the Valley
was real enough for me.
- Do you think they could crank
this noise up a little louder?
- Noise?
Noise?
This music's got emotion, power.
That techno-rock you guys
listen to is gutless.
- I'm sure.
- Fred, that's my leg.
- You guys think you're
so different, don't you?
- No, we're ourselves.
- Oh, and we're not?
- You're like her.
And all the rest of her friends.
You're all fucking programmed.
- So what does it take to be so free?
- That's a good question.
J‘ Yeah it was J‘
- So when can I see you again?
Thank you.
Really, Randy?
Why don't you wait until
the end of the evening
to say these things?
Any questions?
- It's the way I feel.
It's what I want.
Lookin' good.
All right, I'm gonna play this song.
It's called A Million Miles Away.
- I'm here with you now.
- I know.
- It's like I can't explain it, ya know?
It's like my brains won't stop going.
J‘ Was dreamin' about the past J‘
- Ya know?
- Yeah?
J‘ I thought about you
while the radio played J‘
Yeah.
J‘ Should've got loaded J‘
J‘ Some reason I stayed J‘
- It's like I feel
connected to you somehow.
It's like I'm, it's like,
it's like we're linked, or something.
Oh gosh, I'm starting to
sound like my parents.
J‘ I realized I was fallin'
of the face of your world J‘
J‘ And there was nothing
left to bring me back J‘
J‘ I'm a million miles away J‘
J‘ A million miles away J‘
J‘ I'll take ya a million miles away J‘
J‘ And there's nothin' left
to bring me back today J‘
- Steve.
Steve, honey, come on.
Stop worrying, she's gonna be all right.
Remember our night in the cemetery?
Oh!
Oh no, ew.
Fred.
- Stacey.
- God, you are so weird.
Go away.
- Come here my little pickle.
My darling.
J‘ Hear a new song J‘
- Like, this is so embarrassing.
- Well, I think you're cute.
God.
J‘ Like radio DJs' familiar drone J‘
J‘ They blast the listening class J‘
J‘ All the while J‘
J‘ And it's love at war J‘
J‘ And it's hate artistically J‘
- I just hope I can see you again.
- Why not, I thought you liked me.
- For sure.
- Well?
- Well, like, my friends
will freak, ya know?
None of us have had a
dude outside of school.
- Fuck 'em, be the
first one on your block.
- Do you always have to talk like that?
My darling.
My pickle.
- You're so weird.
- I wanna see you tomorrow.
- You can't.
I have to work, if you can believe that.
So uncool.
J‘ We play for free J‘
- Where do you work?
- My parents' store.
- What kind of a store?
- Like, it's a store, ya know?
- Yeah, I know, a store.
What do you sell?
- Health foods.
- Health foods?
Yeah, that's cool.
Oh, it's not.
It's so uncool.
Why couldn't they own a
Pizza Hut, or somethin'?
Oh!
Oh no, ew.
God!
Fred.
Stacey.
- Julie.
- Like, I have to go home now.
- No ya don't.
- Julie!
Julie, come on!
- My parents must be up, I'm sure.
- Are you gonna get into trouble?
- Mm, they're pretty cool.
But I've never done this before.
I better go.
- I wanna see you tomorrow.
- Julie, is that you?
Yeah, Mom, it's me, sorry.
- We have been worried sick about you.
Where have you been that you'd
have to stay out all night?
Wait, I don't think I want to hear this.
- No honey, we have no
secrets in this family.
Julie, we know you're at an age now
where boys are more important
and nature plays its little
part in the scheme of life.
What am I talkin' about?
- I'm sure, I mean it's--
- God, get serious.
I was out all night, but I didn't--
- Wait a minute, Julie.
- It's cool you don't have to,
cool.
- Julie, listen.
What your father is trying to say, dear,
is whatever you do is all right with us
as long as it doesn't
hurt you or anyone else.
- Right.
- Wait, Mom, I just--
- Ya see, we just want ya to
be careful and responsible.
I mean, your mother and
I worry about ya, honey.
It's not fair, with
all the creepy crawlers
out there and everything.
Yeah, well I'm
just going to bed now.
- Wait a minute, Julie.
- You know, Julie, we were young once.
Your mother still is.
We understand.
- This isn't the Age of Aquarius, ya know.
- I would that it were.
- God, why don't you just punish me
like Stacey's parents do?
- Bad karma, dear.
- Guess what?
- What?
Skip asked for my phone number.
Great!
- God, I hope he calls.
- Fasten your seat belt.
- God, I hate these things.
I mean, they totally ruin
the crease in my pants.
Make sure you're
in park, then turn the key.
- Hey, where did you guys
disappear to the other night?
- Sh, let Julie concentrate.
- Yeah, ya know, like, let Julie drive.
I mean you don't wanna be
part of the pavement, do you?
- Well I have the right
to know, it was my party.
- Well Suzi, I mean, I didn't feel good.
I mean, like, I almost barfed
from all that sushi, ya know?
And Julie took me home.
- Cut the chatter, girls.
- I want you guys to know
that you're my best friends.
- Eyes forward,
Julie.
- Julie, tell us quick,
who is he?
- He was at the party.
- Nothing.
- Eyes forward, mouth shut.
- Who could it be?
Brad was there the whole night.
Who is it, Julie?
- Randy.
- Who's Randy?
- He's the most awesome dude ever.
- Where was I when he was around?
- Yeah, like, where were you?
- You don't mean that guy--
- Cut the conversation, girls.
- He's that guy from Hollywood.
I mean, like, he came
back for Stacey and me
and took us back over the hill.
I mean, we had the most super time.
- Crazy.
- I mean, like,
your party was super and all,
but man, he's just like
tripendicular, you know.
Wasn't he, Stacey?
- You die, Richman.
- Straight down.
No, you can't go through there.
No, stop, stop, stop!
- You'll be in big trouble
if this gets around.
What if Tommy finds out?
- So what?
- Julie, you got a reputation to protect.
- Yeah, don't we all.
- Fail.
- Dump the Sohio at 34 and an eighth.
Sure.
Did ya net in the cocoa futures?
Yeah, today would be great.
Delivery!
- Hold on.
Come on in, the gate's open!
I'll get right back to you.
J‘ I look into your eyes J‘
J‘ You would look at my face J‘
J‘ You would see clearly J‘
- Hi, Mrs. Brent.
Skip, from the party?
- I know.
Skip, from the party.
Well, don't stand there holding those.
Put 'em down.
Put em down, put 'em down there.
J‘ Of your voice, yeah J‘
You had a good time, I hope?
- M al am?
- You enjoyed yourself at the party?
- Oh, yes, ma'am.
J‘ She talks in stereo J‘
Huh.
J‘ It sounds so good to me J‘
- I'm a little bit disappointed in you.
- M al am?
- Well, we talked quite
a bit at the party,
and I watched you.
I believe in being direct.
How about you?
Skip, just tell me exactly
what you're thinking.
Say, "Beth, I..."
- I, uh...
Okay.
Beth,
it's no accident
that I'm the one delivering the groceries.
- Well, that's a start.
Yeah.
I guess so.
- Can I get you something to drink?
- Sure.
I mean, no.
- No?
I've still got
a few more deliveries to make.
- That was quick.
J‘ Sounds so good to me J‘
J‘ She talks in J‘
- I've got a little tip for you, Skip.
You gotta be kiddin'.
- Plastics.
Skip, the time to do something
is when the time is right.
- So, um,
what time is it?
- Actually, it's almost
time for Suzi to get home.
- Yeah.
Well, I guess I see what you mean.
- Good.
If nothing else, we've learned that.
Well,
don't be a stranger.
Yeah.
Bye.
- Bye.
- See ya.
J‘ She talks in stereo J‘
A Red Zinger tea.
- A Bombay Avocado Delight,
and a cup of wheatgrass juice.
- Okay.
Would ya like some bean sprouts?
- Steve, we're out of the A,
the B-12, and the D, and the C.
- I think there's some 3-12 in the back.
- Oh, okay.
- Uh-oh.
- What?
- There go the water buffaloes.
Well they are kind of old, dear.
- Beg your pardon, I got
these for Woodstock, remember?
Or was it the march on Washington?
- That was almost 14 years ago
and you were right the first time.
You got the Earth shoes for Washington.
- Oh right, yeah, the Earth shoes.
That's right.
Are you sure?
- Positive, dear.
Remember, you were going
to do a lot of walking?
- Oh right, yeah, yeah,
yeah, you're right.
- I think I'll go get the B-12.
- Yeah.
- God, this stuff is so gross.
How could people eat that?
- Because it isn't greasy
doesn't mean it's bad for ya, dodo.
It's yuck.
- Yuck?
- Yuck.
- You're a yuck.
- Oh, my God, I'm gonna die!
- Julie, what are you doing?
Are you all right?
I'm humiliated to the max.
Hi.
- Hi.
- Randy, this is my dad.
- Steve Richman.
What's happenin', man?
How's it goin'?
- Fine, how you doin'?
- Great.
That's great.
- He wants a sandwich.
- Oh right, yeah okay.
- What are you doing here?
- I wanted to see you.
- But why here?
- What's wrong with this place?
- This place is so gross.
I mean, all this stuff
that tastes like nothing,
is supposed to be so good for you.
- When is business slow?
Maybe I just assumed--
- Did you get in trouble the other night?
For what?
- Coming home so late.
- No.
Why, didn't
your parents find out?
- Yeah, they were waiting up.
- Don't they care?
- For sure they care, but
I'm supposed to develop
into my own person, you know?
Oh.
Well that sounds good.
How about a Coke?
- Sorry, my dad said they
supported the war effort
and it rots the enzymes in your stomach.
- That sounds good to me.
Right.
Hey, let's get out of here.
- Don't you have to work?
- I've got flexible hours.
See you, Dad!
- Bye-bye, sweetie.
Come up with any new gizmos?
- We got some new stuff.
You can come by and take a look at it.
- Honey, where's Julie?
- She left with Randy.
- Who's Randy?
- I think he's that dude she
was out with the other night.
- Do you think we should
talk to her about this?
- I don't know.
Maybe I should talk to her.
J‘ Moving forwards using all my breath J‘
J‘ Making love to you
was never second best J‘
J‘ I saw the world rushing
all around your face J‘
J‘ Never really knowing it
was always mesh and lace J‘
J‘ I'll stop the world and melt with you J‘
J‘ You've seen the difference J‘
J‘ And it's getting better all the time J‘
J‘ There's nothing you and I won't do J‘
J‘ I'll stop the world and melt with you J‘
J‘ You should know better J‘
J‘ Dream of better lives J‘
J‘ The kind which never hate J‘
J‘ You should see why J‘
J‘ Trapped in the state
of imaginary grace J‘
J‘ You should know better J‘
J‘ I made a pilgrimage to
save this human's race J‘
J‘ You should see why J‘
J‘ Never comprehending the
race has long gone by J‘
J‘ Let's stop the world J‘
J‘ I'll stop the world and melt with you J‘
J‘ You've seen the difference J‘
J‘ And it's getting better all the time J‘
J‘ Let's stop the world J‘
J‘ There's nothing you and I won't do J‘
J‘ I'll stop the world and melt with you J‘
J‘ The future's open wide J‘
J‘ Let's stop the world J‘
J‘ I'll stop the world and melt with you J‘
J‘ I've seen some changes J‘
J‘ But it's getting better all the time J‘
J‘ Let's stop the world J‘
J‘ There's nothing you and I won't do J‘
J‘ I'll stop the world and melt with you J‘
J‘ The future's open wide J‘
J‘MmhmmmJ‘
J‘MmhmmmmmJ‘
J‘ I'll stop the world and melt with you J‘
J‘ Let's stop the world J‘
J‘ You've seen the difference J‘
J‘ And it's getting better all the time J‘
J‘ Let's stop the world J‘
J‘ There's nothing you and I won't do J‘
J‘ I'll stop the world and melt J‘
- So, where's Julie?
- Oh, look, we haven't seen
much of her in the last week.
- Yeah, like, She doesn't have
time for her friends anymore.
- Oh I can't believe that.
You guys used to be such good friends.
What's with her?
- Well, like, it's more
like who's with her.
I mean, this guy, Randy, he's
fillin' her head with air.
- Yeah, like, I nominated
her for class rep,
and she wasn't even there.
- Well if she'd listen to
me, I'd set her straight.
You girls are her friends,
you should at least try.
She dumped me.
Far be it for me to
interfere with her life.
- You're right, Tommy.
She did dump you and your advice, buddy.
- Yeah, go on and laugh.
I still love that girl.
- Oh nice.
- I know how
to make her happy.
This geek that she's with
could scar her for life.
- God.
For life?
- No.
Come on, Suzi.
Hey, what is it with Loryn?
J‘ They got a word for girls like me J‘
J‘ They got a name but
you don't wanna use it J‘
J‘ It's all the same to girls like me J‘
J‘ It's all or nothing to girls like me J‘
J‘ I'm gonna jump J‘
J‘ I'm gonna shout. J‘
Whoa!
- Wow, like, what's?
Oh, like way to go, spaz!
- I didn't mean to do it, spaz.
- Get lost.
Like, she's always into
everything, you know?
- Well, Suzi, it's like a total bummer
when you're young and, like,
you don't even know why you're here.
- Yeah.
- I mean.
- Okay.
This one is so tubular.
Huh.
- Suzi, pass the chips, will ya?
- Can you, like, grow some more zits?
- Uh, no, but like, I thought
maybe I could borrow some of yours, okay?
- That's like, really gross.
- Ew, Loryn!
- Like, my thighs just
grow, looking at that stuff.
What am I s'posed to do?
- Put one chip.
What, you just like, ya know,
chew 'em up and spit them out.
- Yeah, right.
- Oh, how gross!
- But people do that to stay skinny
and that's very serious.
- Yeah, ya know, like,
Cindy Boo lost 90 pounds
and even, like, scarfed on ice cream.
- Are you serious?
- No way.
- Yeah, ya know, like,
you splurge and purge?
- Or like, scarf and barf.
Sounds good.
- Very immature.
- I'll start my diet tomorrow.
- You better watch out.
'Cause, like, Randy might
like the Hollywood lean look.
- Yeah, but blimps don't
get to go with Tommy.
- Who?
J‘ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah J‘
- Tommy.
- Who?
Tommy!
- Fuck him.
- Julie!
Girls, we must fuck him.
No you don't!
You know?
No, no.
- Oh.
- Don't, God.
- What is that little brat doing?
- Oh no, I gotta go.
- Gimme the chips!
Sorry.
- Oh.
Like, not too cool all right, Peggy?
I am, too, cool.
- Your mom is so bitchin', Suzi.
- Put that back, Loryn.
You're too small for that.
- I am not too small.
I look totally hot in this, totally.
Oh!
- No man
- You guys!
Could resist my.
- Look at this.
- What do ya call it?
- Your tits.
- Well yeah, I got 'em.
Come on, put
that stuff back, Loryn.
- Do you think Randy'll
like me in this one?
- Oh yeah, like, if it was
made out of black leather.
- Ya know, Tommy's gonna look real good
after six grody bus rides into Hollywood.
- Like, all those sweaty bods.
Barf me out.
- Really, Julie, you'll really get off
hearing about all the parties.
- What do you mean?
- Well, 'cause like, you'll
never be able to go to any
as long as you got Randy.
- Like, don't you think they
have parties over there?
- Oh where, at the zoo?
- You can just, like,
kiss class rep goodbye.
- Like, big deal, okay?
J‘ Girls like me J‘
- Hello?
Who is this?
Oh hi, Skip.
I was hoping you'd call.
Oh!
- Like, my mom said she
saw you the other day.
- She did?
She said she
thinks you're all right.
- Oh, she does, huh?
- Tell him to come over.
Yeah, like,
go for it.
- Um.
- Sh.
- Why don't you come over?
- Put all these clothes away.
- All right.
- Oh.
- Huh? Like, my mom is gone.
Oh yeah, for how long?
- Oh, for most of the night.
Maybe all night, she's out on a date.
- Oh.
Well, like, what do ya say?
- Um, no I can't.
My mom's got a lot
of stuff for me to do
- Your dress.
- Around here and,
well, I was just callin'
to say hi, and all.
Ya know, see what you were up to.
- No, wait.
- What?
Wait, wait.
I'll talk to ya later, okay?
- When?
- Geez, I don't know.
Later I guess.
- Okay.
Where did he go?
My spot.
- Okay.
- And then...
- Bye.
- What?
No!
Date.
- Oh.
- Do you think he likes me?
- He called ya, didn't he?
- Yeah, you know the type,
too shy.
- Yeah.
- I could die he's so buff.
- I know he likes you.
- Oh, like the way Randy likes you?
- For sure, Stacey.
- You know, Julie, you can, like,
kiss all the bitchin' Val dudes goodbye.
- Well like I really care.
J‘ How dare the queen make a fuss J‘
- Like, ya know, I hear
there's somethin' really grody
about the air in Hollyweird, ya know?
And the guys, they only get to
be, like, that big.
- Is that true?
- God.
- Yeah.
- Well like, what's the
biggest one you've ever seen?
- Oh, like in the National
Geographic or what?
- No, in your hand.
Oh!
Shit, God.
You tighten
your hand and then...
J‘ Don't let it get me J‘
J‘ Don't let it get me, oh J‘
J‘ Well, it's Saturday
night and I'm still free J‘
J‘ And I ain't never gonna be J‘
J‘ Eaten by the monster of love J‘
J‘ Don't let it get me J‘
J‘ It's hard to fight it off much more J‘
J‘ I hear it droolin' by the door J‘
J‘ Eaten by the monster of love J‘
J‘ Don't let it get me J‘
J‘ It ain't a pretty Sight to
see the way it leaves 'em J‘
J‘ Don't let it get me J‘
J‘ It chews them up and
spits out creatures J‘
J‘ With those goo gooey eyes J‘
J‘ Sick sickly smiles J‘
J‘ It just ain't right J‘
J‘ And my father said "Don't worry, son" J‘
J‘ But look at him, he should have run J‘
J‘ Eaten by the monster of love J‘
J‘ Don't let it get me J‘
JNoJ
J‘ Don't let it get me, oh J‘
J‘ Don't let it get me J‘
J‘ Well, it's worse than war J‘
J‘ It's worse than death J‘
- Hello?
J‘ There ain't too many
left who ain't been J‘
- Hello?
Say, it's me, Skip.
J‘ Don't let it get me J‘
- I'm just returning one of Suzi's books.
J‘ A dog gets grabbed and
eaten by the monster of love J‘
J‘ Don't let it get me J‘
J‘ It ain't a pretty sight
to see the way it feeds on J‘
J‘ Don't let it get me J‘
- This is crazy.
J‘ With those goo gooey eyes J‘
J‘ Sick sickly smiles J‘
J‘ It just isn't right J‘
J‘ Eaten by the monster of love J‘
J‘ Let it huff, let it puff J‘
J‘ Don't let it get me J‘
J‘ Eaten by the monster of love J‘
J‘ I hate to gripe, but
I just ain't the type J‘
J‘ Don't let it get me J‘
J‘ Don't let it get me, oh J‘
- What do ya think?
- Everybody thinks Tommy is
so tubular and all, ya know?
- So you think I should pick Tommy?
- Um.
Well what I mean is, like, if
you were to get back together
with Tommy, do you think
things'd be better?
- You mean I should pick Randy?
- Well I don't know about that.
What I'm tryin' to say, Julie.
It's really hard for me to
say what I'm tryin' to say.
- Loryn, this isn't helping me.
I don't know what to do about this.
- Me either.
J‘ Don't let it get me, oh J‘
J‘ Don't let it get me J‘
J‘ Don't it let it get me, oh J‘
J‘ Don't let it get me, oh J‘
J‘ Don't let it get me J‘
J‘ Well I know some really
good, good people J‘
J‘ Overcome, and piece by piece J‘
J‘ They were eaten by the monster of love J‘
J‘ Don't let it get me J‘
J‘ And sometimes it takes a nip at me J‘
J‘ But I'm too quick to ever be J‘
J‘ Eaten by the monster of love J‘
J‘ Don't let it get me J‘
J‘ Don't let it get me, oh J‘
J‘ Well, eaten by the monster of love J‘
J‘ Don't let it get me J‘
J‘ Eaten by the monster of love J‘
- Oh shit.
- Mom.
- What's up?
- Like, I got this problem
and I don't know what to do about it.
- Yeah?
That's easy, take it back
and get a more expensive one.
You know, the expensive ones
always fit better, honey.
- Dad.
That's not it?
All right, what is it?
- Well like, ya know, this is really hard.
- All right.
Shoot
- Well, I like Randy a lot, ya know?
Like, he's different.
- What, he was in an
accident or something?
Things don't work the way they should?
No!
- I saw a movie like that, once.
Did you?
- All right, how is he different?
- I don't know.
He for sure doesn't dress like my friends
or even talk like 'em.
- Mm, I see.
Well, is that wrong?
- My friends think so.
- Mm-hm.
And that's important?
- Well sure, I guess.
- I don't wanna lose 'em.
- Of course not.
- And they all want me to be with Tommy.
- Mm-hm.
Well, what do you want?
I wanna be with Randy.
But it's getting hard and
I don't want any problems.
- Yeah, well there's the rub, you see?
Nothin's easy.
I wanna show you somethin'.
Ya see, honey, sometimes
the way things look
aren't the way they really are
or the way they're gonna turn out.
Here.
I don't think ya ever saw these.
- Are these you?
- Yep, that's me.
Who's this?
- She's a friend of mine,
before I met your mother.
Anyway, ya see, not everyone looked
or dressed like that back then.
As a matter of fact, lots of
people didn't look like that.
- Man, I can believe that.
I don't think Randy's
ever looked this bad.
- Yeah, well, the point is,
what difference does it all make?
The way ya look, the kinds of
clothes ya wear on your body?
It's what you are that
counts, what's inside you,
what ya stand for, not what
other people wanna make you.
Ya see, honey, there are
lots of people out there
who just ain't happy unless you live
and think the same way they do,
and if ya don't.
Ya dig what I'm sayin'?
- I know all about that stuff.
But like, which one do I pick?
Oh, Randy or Tommy.
Beats me, love, but let
me know when you decide.
Okay?
- Okay.
- Hi, Julie.
- Hi.
- How are you?
- Good.
- Hi.
- Hi, Julie.
- Look, this has been too tough, you know?
I mean, it's not really fair.
It's either Randy or you guys.
- Well life's not fair.
- Randy is totally special to me, Stacey.
And I don't understand why.
I mean, he doesn't do
the things we like to do,
but, uh--
- Julie, ya left out one possibility:
totally gnarly sex.
- It hasn't gotten that far.
I know everyone is counting
on me to do the right thing.
- So did you?
I don't know.
But it was fun while it lasted.
- So you've done the right thing.
Oh, I don't know, you guys,
like, being popular can be so lonely.
- It doesn't have to be, Stacey.
- Well, like, what am I gonna do?
I kissed Tommy off in a major way.
- Forget that.
I mean, Tommy is such a hunk.
He told us he still loves you a bunch.
- Ow!
- He did?
When?
- Well, he just sort of, like,
said it one day, ya know?
- Just make up with him.
He'll take ya back.
- He's gotta be bummed to the max with me.
He'll get over it.
Hey, ya know, like, why break up
the most bitchin' couple at school?
I mean, Tommy can't be king
of the prom going stag.
He's got his position to worry about.
- Okay, I'll talk to him.
Are ya sure he wants me back, though?
- Julie, of course, I just told you so.
- Hey, Julie, I asked Arthur to the prom.
- No, what'd he say?
- He goes, "Okay."
- Skip hasn't yet.
- Oh, he will.
- Hi, Tommy.
- Don't worry about it.
- Hi.
- I'm so bummed.
- Oh Julie, I gotta go.
I've got all this homework I forgot about.
Like, not funny.
Come on, Loryn.
- See ya, Julie.
- Bye-bye.
- Bye, Julie.
- I'll see ya.
- Hi.
- Hey.
- How you been?
- I've been getting by, I guess.
You?
- All right.
- Yeah, so, how's your new
boyfriend, what's-his-name?
- It's over.
- Well he wasn't mean to you, was he?
'Cause if he was I'll go
kick his ass sideways.
I did it once, I'll do it again.
- No, no it wasn't that.
It was just that he was
different, that's all.
- Is this what you want?
Listen, Doug's got his
dad's Mercedes tonight.
We're gonna cruise Van Nuys, you wanna go?
- Sure, yeah I guess.
- All right.
- Can I have some of your hamburger?
- Yeah, it's, sure ya can.
- Okay.
Mm.
Mm, good.
- Hey, babe.
- Randy.
- What's the matter with you?
- Why didn't you call me first?
- Well ya know, it slipped my mind.
I really didn't think
it was that important,
but I will tell you what I'm gonna do.
I'm gonna reach in my
pocket, I'm gonna get a dime
and I'm gonna go down to the phone booth,
I'm gonna make a phone call,
come right back up and talk to you.
- Damn it, why do you
always barge in like that?
- You shouldn't talk like that.
- Don't tell me what to do.
You have no control over my life.
I could see anybody I want to, okay?
I'm sorry.
I didn't think it was that big a deal.
- Look, I have to go to bed now.
- Hey, come over here.
Hey, I love you.
That's all I wanted to say.
I love you.
So, when can I see you.
Hey, hey.
When can I see you again?
- You can't.
- What?
- Don't do that to me!
You can't see me anymore.
- Is it your father, is it your mother?
Just let me talk to them.
I can really fix things.
- No, there's nothing to fix.
It's not them.
It's not them at all.
It's me, okay?
I can't see you anymore, okay?
- Okay.
Okay.
I know what it is.
I know what this is.
It's your fucking friends, right?
Shit, Julie, I mean what is this?
This is between you and me
not between the rest of the
fucking world, so fuck off!
It's your friends.
Well fuck you!
No, fuck off, for sure!
Like, totally!
I don't fuckin',
I don't give a fuck.
I don't fuckin' care, man.
And ba! Ha ha!
- Randy?
- Hey.
- You look like shit.
- How you doin', Lou?
- You know I shouldn't
let you in here.
- You been doin' good?
- Come on.
- All right, that's what I want.
J‘ And now you're out there on your own J‘
J‘ You say your goodbyes
and broke all the ties J‘
J‘ Just don't be dumb and
think I'd try for you J‘
J‘ Tonight you can feel
the season changin' J‘
J‘ You'll never change but you're
no better than the weather J‘
J‘ You're cool but there's
rain in your heart J‘
J‘ You're blown like a feather J‘
J‘ And that's the oldest
story in the world J‘
J‘ Ya lost the key to paradise J‘
J‘ That's the oldest story in the world J‘
J‘ Did we have it made J‘
- You feel so good.
J‘ Somehow I thought we could remain J‘
- Hello, Samantha.
J‘ If nothin' lasts J‘
J‘ There's no one to blame J‘
- I've been lookin' for you tonight.
- Liar.
You haven't been looking for me
and I haven't been lookin'
for you in two months now.
- You're right, but here we are.
J‘ Lost the key to paradise J‘
J‘ That's the oldest story in the world J‘
Did I ever
tell you how good you feel?
You did tell me that.
J‘ That's the oldest story in the world J‘
J‘ You'll hear again and again J‘
- Let's make up.
Do you wanna make up some more?
J‘ Somehow I thought we could remain J‘
J‘ 'Cause if nothin'
lasts no one's to blame J‘
J‘ Can't look back to where you J‘
- Your place or mine?
J‘ It's the oldest story in the world J‘
J‘ So then we gotta make it right J‘
J‘ 'Cause that's the oldest
story in the world J‘
J‘ Just like a rollin' stone J‘
J‘ That's the oldest story in the world J‘
J‘ You'll hear it again and again J‘
J‘ That's the oldest story J‘
- Oh yeah.
J‘ 'Cause that's the oldest
story in the world J‘
How about a cigarette?
You got it.
- How about a sip?
You see that?
Who's that?
Don't know.
Okay.
J‘ Just like a rollin' stone J‘
Keep goin'.
J‘ I started driftin'
to a different place J‘
J‘ I realized I was fallin'
off the face of your world J‘
J‘ And now's there nothin'
that could bring me back J‘
J‘ I'm a million miles away J‘
J‘ A million miles away J‘
J‘ I'm just a million miles away J‘
J‘ And there's nothin' left
to bring me back today J‘
Go home, Randy.
Want a light?
- Hey, fuck you, scum!
Get outta the car.
- Hey, you bad you think?
- Yeah, I tell ya I'm bad.
- You bad and shit?
Get out of
the fucking car, shit.
Are you bad, man?
- Get outta the car.
- I'll show you bad.
- Let's go!
- You wanna suck this thing?
- Come on, keep goin'!
Come on.
Hey, man.
- What are you doin'?
- You're a dumb son of a bitch, man.
Guys like that'll kill you.
- I don't care, fuck 'em.
Just leave me alone.
- What the hell's the matter with you?
- Fuck you, too.
- Hey, man, man who are you talkin' to?
It's me, Bailey.
And you're shitfaced.
- I don't feel so good.
I'm gonna be sick.
Go on, leave me alone!
Go on, man, leave me alone.
Leave you alone, why?
So you can feel sorry for yourself
because some little Valley chick
wanted somebody else, is that it?
- God.
Hit me with that brick.
I'm dyin'.
Just put me out of my misery.
- Come on, man.
Man, you smell fucking awful.
- Screw it, man.
She made me feel great, huh?
- Come off that, man.
Look, if you want this girl so bad,
why don't you do somethin' about it?
Huh?
I mean, go for the wild, crazy stuff.
- Wild and crazy.
- Yeah.
- Just don't tell me that.
- Come on, man, it's romantic shit.
Girls love that stuff, ya know?
- Yeah.
- Hey trust me.
It never fails.
I know.
Hi.
- Hi.
- Hi, hi.
Hi.
- We have to talk.
- I told you we can't.
- Young man.
- What is it?
What?
Are you being held prisoner or what?
What is this?
Gimme a signal, Julie.
- Get outta the car.
- But I love you!
- Get outta the car!
Let's go.
You've
just heard Men at Work.
We have more dedications
that go out tonight
to Billy from Deena.
She says, "You're a fox."
Andrea to Doug, she'll do
anything to get you back.
To Julie, his favorite Valley girl,
Randy his sends his undying love
and says, like, come back soon, ya know.
J‘ In your lips I sense a danger J‘
- I gotta get to Algebra,
I'll see ya later.
- Okay.
- See ya.
J‘ In your lips I see a danger J‘
J‘ You've got the eyes of a stranger J‘
Enjoy the ride.
- Oh, bitchin', is this in 3D?
- No, but your face is.
- Oh, like, I hate 3D.
- What?
- Gives me a headache.
- It's not in 3D.
- Have a nice flight.
Back with them!
Oh good, check this geek out.
- Oh God.
- Look at this guy.
- Yeah.
And I guess these go right back
down there, now don't they?
Okay.
How ya doin' down there?
- Where's my Coke?
I want my Coke.
- It appears as though you
forgot our french fries
and our Coke, fish head.
- Oh, well Peter Piper picked
a pepper, I guess I did!
Whoa! Oh I'm sorry.
That guy is nuts.
- What a geek.
- Oh my God.
- Naw, Julie, don't do that.
Come on, Julie!
Don't do this.
She's out there somewhere.
Yup.
But what you're doin' ain't workin'.
We need a good plan.
- Oh, I didn't know that.
- Hey listen, if you're gonna
have that kind of attitude,
I won't even tell ya.
Just forgot I ever tried to save ya
from your miserable existence.
Okay, I'll tell ya, twist my arm.
Now listen.
I got a plan that's gonna get you in solid
with the love of your
life, and at the same time
achieve the grandest form of retribution
against the guy who kicked your ass.
Well, so he had a little help.
- Oh, man.
- Thanks.
Like hey, where are you and Arthur goin'?
We're goin' straight to the Hot Tub Club.
- No!
- No, no, no listen.
We were on the waiting list, and I got in.
I knew this guy and I got in.
- Oh, my gosh.
- Where's Julie goin' with Tommy?
- I heard that,
I heard that Tommy made
reservations at the Valley Sheraton!
- No.
- Yes.
- Does she know?
- No.
- No way!
- Far out.
This kid doesn't miss a trick.
Sarah, you gotta see this.
Sarah!
- Somebody's here.
- Lancelot's here!
- Not so loud, dear.
- Look at me.
Look at me, I think I'm
probably more nervous
than the kids are.
I mean, look at these hands.
- Steve, I don't understand
what you're so nervous about.
You're acting like
you're going to the prom.
- I don't know.
I mean, feel these hands, they're wet.
Oh wow.
- Look at her.
- Look at you, honey.
Oh wow.
You look lovely, darlin'.
Look at her.
Beautiful!
- Oh, oh, that's Tommy.
Quick, get the camera.
- All righty.
- We can't miss
a moment of this, hurry, hurry.
- What's the deal with him?
- I think your father has
just faced his mortality.
And both in pink, both in pink.
You just look beautiful.
Steve, hurry up, dear, Tommy's here!
Steve!
Are you all right, honey?
I'm c o ming !
Coming I'm looking for the camera!
- Just wait two more minutes.
Steve'll be here in just
one minute with the camera.
- Okay.
- We have to get a picture of this.
We really, really do.
Steve!
Hurry up, dear!
There he is.
- Hey, here we go.
Hi Tommy.
How ya doin', man?
- Hi. Good.
- Will you look at them?
Are they a picture?
- Yeah, we gotta get a picture of this.
Ya know, I still got film
in here from the wedding.
What wedding?
- They were married last September.
Newlyweds.
- Can't be too careful.
Okay, let's get some snapperoos here.
- Dad, Earth to Dad.
- Imagine that, the old lens cap.
Okay, here we go.
- Closer.
- No stoppin' us now.
Get a little closer.
Gotta give us a big smile,
Tommy.
- Smile, come on.
- That's it, buddy.
- Closer.
- Not too much.
- All right, we gotta go.
A little goes a
long way with some people.
- I gotta go.
- Oh.
- Okay.
- You look beautiful.
Have a wonderful time.
- Trust me?
- Yeah, me, too.
- Bye!
- Come on, let's go see it.
Her first prom.
Yeah, far out.
- Feeling better, dear?
- Yeah!
Ya know, Sarah, maybe we shoulda gone.
I mean, how bad could it have been?
- What?
- How bad could it have been?
- Your prom.
Hey, what is this, Bangkok?
I don't need a massage.
- Well.
- Come on, honey.
- Do you have any of that stuff for me?
- Yeah sure, come on.
We'll light the hummer up.
- Are you ready to party?
Yeah!
- Sure!
Here's Josie Cotton
and the Party Crashers!
J‘ Yesterday I met a guy J‘
J‘ The kind I dream about at night J‘
J‘ He said come on lets take a ride J‘
J‘ And I said okay, yeah J‘
J‘ Every movie major's really hip J‘
J‘ He's hip uh huh J‘
J‘ He could be the one to come
and steal my heart away J‘
Hi.
- You think this is something,
you wait 'til later.
- What do you mean?
What do you mean?
J‘A one, a two J‘
J‘ A one, two, three, four J‘
- I can't believe this.
- No shit.
- Well I guess we Should've
shined up the wagon
or at least cleaned out
the back seat.
- Come on,
I'm doin' the best I can.
- What is this, Fred?
Did you clip the wings off of butterflies
when you were a kid or what?
Maybe you still do.
- Listen, I told you, I've got a plan.
Enough said?
J‘ Now I'm so glad that the summer's past J‘
J‘ And school is in at last J‘
J‘ School is in J‘
J‘ Get me back J‘
- Hi, Julie.
- How are ya tonight?
Scott.
J‘ Don't ya know it, oh yeah J‘
J‘ Yeah, school is in J‘
J‘ Now you may think I'm
nutty and tellin' you lies J‘
J‘ But I'm goin' out tonight
and buyin' my school supplies J‘
J‘ Cause this semester's gonna be a gas J‘
J‘ I said school is in at last J‘
J‘ Tell me about it J‘
J‘ Oh yeah J‘
- No.
This is it, Fred.
I'm rushin' that birthday cake.
- Are you crazy?
Listen.
I'll have you know this is
all going like clockwork.
I'm getting very excited about this.
So just hang on.
- This will be a night we'll never forget.
- Come on, what is it?
- You'll see.
J‘ School is in J‘
J‘ Oh yeah J‘
- They really are rather
disciplined today.
- Moving on.
- Where are the cups?
Ms. Liebman, do you
know where the cups are?
- Cups?
- Cups.
- I don't know where the cups are.
Mr. Bennett?
- Yeah, the cups.
- Mr. Cook, do you know where the...
- I haven't seen cups all evening.
- Oh, Suzi was, like,
supposed to bring 'em
and she never even showed up.
- Oh.
- Whatever.
J‘ Up to the head of my class J‘
J‘ I washed the dishes,
I scrubbed the floor J‘
J‘ And taught baby brother
how to count to four J‘
J‘ Yeah I'm so glad that summer's past J‘
J‘ And school is in at last J‘
J‘ School is in J‘
J‘ Tell me about it, oh yeah J‘
- Oh my goodness.
Um, I think we should get out of here.
- Like, Arthur, let's,
like, wait until after
they announce the king
and queen at least, okay?
- Okay.
J‘ Don't ya know now J‘
J‘ Tell me about it J‘
J‘ Oh yeah J‘
J‘ Yeah, yeah, yeah school is in J‘
J‘ Tommy was the deal, boy J‘
- Boys, how we doin'?
- Mr. Brooks.
- Hi, Mr. Brooks.
- How's that punch?
- It's bosco.
- Gee, I'd like to try some.
Where are the cups?
- Wow, there's no cups.
- No cups?
Come on, let me in.
A little flat.
J‘ Now I gotta know J‘
J‘ Johnny are you queer J‘
J‘ 'Cause when I see you
dancin' with your friends J‘
J‘ I can't help wonderin' J‘
- She's there.
- Suzi, like, where have you been?
Everybody's been, like,
waiting for the cups.
Skip, where have you been?
What have you been doing?
Have you been getting laid, Suzi?
- Loryn, just!
J‘ Oh why are you so weird, boy J‘
- Oh, where's Ralphie?
- Indian wrestling with the boys
or something totally grody like that.
- Oh wow, sorry.
- Oh, like, it's cool.
Ya see, like, I'm not
gonna eat anything now
so when we go to La Serre I
can scarf up half the menu.
- Wow, all right.
- Okay, bye.
J‘ I can't help J‘
- Ah!
Stacey, check out this, dude.
- I don't wanna see Stacey.
No, that's it, Bailey.
I've had it with you.
- What? Now wait a minute.
I didn't think her haircut was so bad.
- What do you mean, her haircut?
I just wanna know what the rest
of this big plan of yours is.
- What do you mean, "the rest"?
This is it.
Simplicity at its finest.
J‘ Why are you so weird, boy J‘
J‘ Johnny are you queer, boy J‘
- Simplicity at its finest?
Well at least you got me here.
J‘ Johnny are you queer J‘
Crush that fly.
J‘ Johnny are you queer, boy J‘
- Hey Johnny?
Johnny are you,
J‘ Johnny are you queer, boy J‘
- You know.
J‘ Whoa Johnny J‘
J‘ Johnny are you queer, boy J‘
J‘ Oh Johnny J‘
J‘ Johnny J‘
J‘ Are you queer, boy J‘
J‘ Hey Johnny J‘
J‘ Johnny J‘
J‘ Are you queer, boy J‘
J‘ Johnny are you queer, boy J‘
J‘ Johnny J‘
- Is this on?
And now, students, the moment
that you've all been waiting for,
The announcement
- Tommy.
- Of the king and the
queen of Valley High.
What is being king and queen all about?
Is it about who wears the nicest clothes?
I think not.
Is it about who's dating the
captain of the football team?
Or who's seeing the head cheerleader?
I don't think so.
Is it a popularity contest?
- No, okay?
I doubt it.
- I'm gonna give you
- Although,
the chance you never gave me.
- One can't help but--
- When one is honorable,
when one is disciplined,
when one is school spirited.
Yes, kings and queens,
they don't grow on trees.
- Hold on to this.
Everyone
can't be a king and a queen.
- Let's go, boy.
- Now students.
- Get up.
- I remember my prom.
I wanted to be the queen.
I wasn't.
What are you doin', huh?
Watch this.
- Who have set an example
for our whole school with their behavior.
They need no introduction
because they are not
just the king and queen of Valley High,
they are Valley High.
Your king.
Your queen.
J‘ Yesterday I met a guy J‘
J‘ I'm gonna dream about tonight J‘
J‘ He said come on, let's take a ride J‘
J‘ And I said okay J‘
J‘ Every move he makes is
really hip, hip, uh-huh J‘
J‘ He let me down and threw my heart away J‘
J‘ He could be the one J‘
J‘ I like his style J‘
Get your hands
off me, you fuckin' dick.
J‘ He could be the one to make
it all worthwhile, yeah J‘
Hey, Julie!
Hey what's goin' on here?
Oh!
J‘ He could be the one,
he could be the one J‘
J‘ Yeah, oh J‘
J‘ The one, yeah J‘
J‘ He could be the one,
he could be the one J‘
- That must be some party
you got goin' there.
- Yeah.
Valley Sheraton?
Sir?
- Yeah.
J‘ Moving forwards using all my breath J‘
J‘ Making love to you
was never second best J‘
J‘ I saw the world crashing
all around your face J‘
J‘ Never really knowing it
was always mesh and lace J‘
J‘ I'll stop the world J‘
J‘ And melt with you J‘
J‘ You've seen the difference J‘
J‘ And it's getting better all the time J‘
J‘ There's nothing you and I won't do J‘
J‘ I'll stop the world and melt with you J‘
J‘ You should know better J‘
J‘ Dream of better lives
the kind which never hate J‘
J‘ You should see why J‘
J‘ Trapped in the state
of imaginary grace J‘
J‘ You should know better J‘
J‘ I made a pilgrimage to
save this humans race J‘
J‘ You should see why J‘
J‘ Never comprehending the
race has long gone by J‘
J‘ Let's stop the world J‘
J‘ I'll stop the world and melt with you J‘
J‘ You've seen the difference J‘
J‘ And it's getting better all the time J‘
J‘ Let's stop the world J‘
J‘ There's nothing you and I won't do J‘
J‘ I'll stop the world and melt with you J‘
J‘ The future's open wide J‘
J‘ Let's stop the world J‘
J‘ I'll stop the world and melt with you J‘
J‘ I've seen some changes J‘
J‘ But it's getting better all the time J‘
J‘ Let's stop the world J‘
J‘ There's nothing you and I won't do J‘
J‘ I'll stop the world and melt with you J‘
J‘ The future's open wide J‘
J‘MmhmhmJ‘
J‘MmhmhmhmJ‘
J‘ I'll stop the world and melt with you J‘
J‘ Let's stop the world J‘
J‘ You've seen the difference J‘
J‘ And it's getting better all the time J‘
J‘ Let's stop the world J‘
J‘ There's nothing you and I won't do J‘
J‘ I'll stop the world and melt with you J‘
J‘ Let's stop the world J‘